I had a dream...
Yuko.
Heed me, Yuko.
Thou must awaken.
Who are you?
Thou hast inherited the blood of the dark ones.
You must vanquish a Magical Girl who lives
in this town, and restore our clan to its former glory.
Uh, no can do. Too sleepy.
Wait. Hello?
Wakey-wakey.
Good morning?
Hey, wake the hell up!
You sorry excuse for an heir!
Jeez, that dream sure took a turn for the scary...
My head feels heavy...
My name is Yuko Yoshida.
I'm just an ordinary 15-year-old girl.
Mornin', Sis.
Huh?
Good morning, Ryo...
What're these?
Something very abnormal
is popping out of my very normal head.
The Demon Girl Next Door
Yuko Awakens!!
For Family Reasons You're Now a Demon Girl
M-Mom!
Don't make so much noise, Yuko.
Help, I've grown these weird horns! And a tail, too!
I can feel them like part of my body!
I can move them, too!
Just calm down.
Load, fulcrum, effort...
my brain just bounced like a seesaw...!
It seems this day has finally come.
Hey mom, what are those really chic things
growing out of Yuko?
Really chic
Yu and Ryo, listen to me. I must tell you about
the ancient secret of the Yoshida family.
Oh jeez, why did this have to happen
on a Sunday morning of all days...?
Sunday Morn
The truth is, neither of you are ordinary human children.
Uh-huh, that's cool mom.
We're not ordinary...
Wait, what?!
I heard that piano drop just now.
The Yoshida family has been sustained
by the power of darkness since ancient times.
We are descendants of the "Dark Clan"
that were banished long ago.
Wow... "darkness," huh? This is too surreal.
I must still be dreaming, so back to bed with me-
Don't try and run from reality.
SWSH
My brain is bouncing around again!
So, our whole family are "Descendants of Darkness."
Forget that for a minute,
you still haven't cooked our breakfast rice.
We've run out of rice for this month.
More importantly, there's something that I must tell you.
The reason that we live in poverty like this
is because of our mortal enemies, the "Light Clan."
"Light"?!
War of Light and Dark
*Visualization
Our battle with them spanned across centuries,
but they successfully sealed
all our power and luck away.
That's why we look like ordinary humans now.
YEN
In the end, they put the "$400 Per Month" curse upon us.
They've taken nearly everything from us.
That curse really hit where it counts. Seconds please.
There was nothing else
they could have sealed away, I suppose.
Anyway, it seems that you've
somehow caused a lapse in the seal.
Those horns and tail you've grown were part
of the trademark appearance of our ancestors!
GREED
You must fully break the seal to gain control
over the evil energy and then master it.
Money! Power! Delicious food!
But doesn't that make me the bad guy?
What good is gonna come from doing that?
If you manage to break the seal,
you should get a little taller.
And our financial woes will certainly improve.
We'll be able to go to one of those
all-you-can-eat-and-drink buffets!
Will that include one of those tower of pancakes?!
IT'S A
FEAST!!
It's a feast!
Then I'll do whatever you want me to, Mom!
We can build a library in our house.
So, what exactly do I need to do?
Get some!
Get some!!
So, what exactly do I need to do?
You must defeat a "Magical Girl," one of the priests
of the Light Clan that sealed away our powers.
One, two, three! One, two, three!
Defeat a Magical Girl? Roger that!
One,
two,
three!!
One,
two,
three!
Then you must drain their blood and offer it
to the Demon God Statue of our ancestors!
"Blood"?!
DEMON GOD STATUE
"Demon God Statue"?
Where the heck do I find that?
You know, that thing I always use to prop the door open.
Mom, open up.
We know you're in there taking a nap.
The doorstop?!
DEMON GOD STATUE
A wicked stone statue that harbors the
banished souls of the Dark Clan!
It's super sinister!
Looks like it might fall apart
Demon God Statue! This is the object
that the spirits of my ancestors are drawn to.
My mom thought it was just the perfect weight
and size, so she used it as a doorstop.
That was just a camouflage.
What are you doing, Mom?
I found the statue.
I need to submit this form to notify
that you're now active as a Demon Girl.
Submit it to who?
The Demon Directory
The Demon Directory.
The Demon Bakery?!
THE
DEMON
BAKERY?!
She said, Demon "Directory."
THE
DEMON
BAKERY?!
The Demon Directory
Aghestoise
Yanderella
Loaded Luatic
Shadow Mistress Yuko
Your Demon Girl name will need to be something fitting!
What about these?
Huh?! I want some time to think about it.
Actually, these are all terrible!
Okay, I'm putting down
"Shadow Mistress Yuko." Fax sent!
A corny name sent by an even cornier machine!
"Shadow Mistress"...
Does this mean you're going into business
as a sadistic seductress?
How exactly am I going to defeat a Magical Girl?
Since you've grown horns and a tail, it means the powers
of our ancestors have somewhat returned to you.
Can you feel any of the dark energy flowing within you?
I don't even know what that would feel like!
The only thing I feel is hungry!
Don't you feel like you've gotten stronger at all?
Actually, these horns are so heavy I feel like
I'm on my way to becoming a hunchback.
Perhaps nothing substantial has actually changed.
I think that my center of gravity has changed,
and it's making me dizzy!
If anything, I'm weaker now!
Yoshida
Household
BANDA TERRACE
Mom, if I'm going to fight,
then do I get some kind of equipment?
You know, like in video games and stuff!
I bequeath you this staff and these herbs.
For real?
For
real?
Unfortunately, modern society dictates that anyone
walking around with weapons will be arrested.
It's a harsh reality.
But then...
That's why... I've prepared this!
A splendid weapon capable of shredding apart
even the most well-cooked of eggs!
I'm very familiar with it!
And take this, it should help to camouflage your weapon.
Handwipe
Feels like I'm ready for a picnic!
I'm heading out!
Good luck, Sis!
And so, I proceeded forth on my quest despite
being unsatisfied with the parameters of my character.
Wait, I'm getting ahead of myself here.
I'm supposed to splatter her blood
all over this statue, right?
But I hate icky horror films
and I have the worst grades in gym class.
This is impossible.
I have no idea where to find
one of these "Magical Girls" anyway.
FREEZE
Hold on, I had a dream this morning.
You must vanquish a Magical Girl who lives in this town,
and restore our clan to its former glory.
Uh-huh...
What was up with that?
Mumble
"Lives in this town"? I wonder where, exactly?
Horns?
Mumble
Horns...?
Sigh...
My head is so heavy now...
It feels like someone just glued two dumbbells on it.
Ah.
Oops, oops, gah...
Eeeek!
Oh no! My sealed ancestor's spirit!
Oh, that's good. It's not broken.
Actually, I think that all broke ME instead.
WORN OUT...
W-waaah!
Look out!
Seconds
Huh? What? Wh-where did that dump truck just go?
Are you all right?
She stopped it with one hand?
Are you okay, mister?
I stopped the truck as gently as I could.
Y-yeah.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Right, well then...
Make sure you watch where you're going from now on.
O-okay. Sorry.
Droop...
Please be a cosplay!
Um, are you cosplaying?
Nope. I'm a Magical Girl.
Drooooop...
That figures...
You stopped that truck with one hand, after all.
I've found my target...
Gulp!
It's been a long time since I've had to transform, though.
Actually, those horns of yours seem like...
U-um...
What? Are you hungry?
SNEAK
You can have this.
TUNA & ONION
DANISH
What exactly is this?
It's bread? A sandwich?
I'm confused. Why give me something like this?
Huh? Well, you looked like you were hungry.
And because you're short.
Oh, I see!
She's taking pity on me!
OUTRAGE!!
Outrage! Outrage!
I've never had an experience so humiliating before!
Huh?
G
R
Snicker.
You really are starving, aren't you?
Ugh!
Don't think this means you've won!
But I really appreciate you saving me!
She's a weird one.
Outrage!
Don't give up, Yuko! Use this experience
as your first step to becoming a great demon!
Outrage!
BANDA TERRACE
Monday Morning
I'm heading off to school!
Thou hast inherited the blood of the dark ones.
Vanquish a Magical Girl
and restore our clan to its former glory.
I ran across a Magical Girl! She actually saved me!
And took pity on me...
Boy, that sure was a weird dream I had yesterday.
Growing horns and finding out
that I'm the descendant of demons...
then leaving to find a Magical Girl to defeat.
Yuko!
G'morning!
Good morning, Anri!
You're up really early today.
We've got a soft tennis tournament coming up this week,
so I've got practice every morning.
Oh?
Yeah, our team actually just got
a new manager and they're super funny.
Really?
Sorry to be rude, but are those horns?
I suppose I can see how they might look that way!
That's what they are!
Horns and a tail, right in front of me!
It wasn't a dream...
Morning!
I'll be honest, these things just suddenly grew in...
and I have no idea what I should do with them.
I bet you could hang your umbrella
or gym clothes from them, no?
That would make life easier.
Well, I'm not really worried about
how to make my life easier...
Actually, I think that would make
paying for stuff or eating on the go a real cinch!
Your arms will be free!
Yummy
Yummy, yummy, yummy...!
Your arms will be free!
Now that you mention it, that's true!
They could be really handy!
Definitive
Dictionary of Kanji
Let's give it a try.
Um, huh?
Definitive
Dictionary of Kanji
Here.
Um, huh?
Oh... it worked.
Never mind! It's way too heavy!
Sorry! I forgot that you're not that strong.
Load, fulcrum, effort... Load, fulcrum, effort...
Yuri-yuri?
I prefer Masashi.
When's season 2?
Hm, so those horns and tail
just kind of sprouted over night?
I'm embarrassed to say it,
but there's a lot going on in my family.
SHY
Apparently, because I grew these horns
it's my destiny to find and murderize a Magical Girl.
Wow, really?
I'm totally jealous. Having a destiny is so cool.
Can I touch your horns?
Me, too!
Sure, go for it.
Whoa. They're exactly what I thought
horns would feel like!
They're so stylish. Totally fitting for a Demon Girl.
They've got a nice feel to them.
This may seem strange to say,
but I'm surprised you're both taking this in stride.
Well, there's a lot of weirdos in this town.
SMOOTH
"Weird"...
Oh! I didn't mean you!
Don't try and hide them, they really suit you!
They're super cool, they look like giant croissants!
Croissant
Crescent shaped bread is really yummy.
Croissant...
Right now, I need to focus on finding a Magical Girl!
I have to offer their blood
to this Demon God Statue of my ancestors!
Uh, isn't your ancestor a little broken there? On the top.
Fortunately, I know there's one in this town.
I will hunt down that Magical Girl!
Fwip
Oh yeah, there's a Magical Girl
in our school. Class A, right?
Ah, the super strong one.
Oh? Is that so?
Wait! What the heck is up with this school?!
Sakuragaoka High School
This is Sakuragaoka High School.
Yuko and her friends are students here.
That's Momo Chiyoda.
We went to the same middle school.
I see you over there!
Oh no, you spotted me!
I can't see anything now.
Huh? That razor-sharp look...
I've seen it somewhere before.
Ahh!
It's that girl who stopped the trunk
with one hand the other day!
You know her?
Dealing with her was aggravating in more ways than one.
Outrage...!
Tuna & Onion
Danish
I heard that six years ago,
she actually saved the whole world.
She's known worldwide?!
I... I never would have guessed
I was tangling with someone that amazing.
I wonder if a lowly neighborhood demon like myself
stands a chance against a world-renowned magician.
Does this string phone work?
I can hear you.
I wonder if there's any other information
I can find about her.
Hm, she doesn't really talk about herself much.
Oh, that's right. One time during our fitness exams...
Excuse me. I can't get an accurate reading
on grip strength because I maxed out the dynamometer.
Everyone kind of flipped out when she said that.
In the end, they had to use three dynamometers
together to get an accurate reading.
Is she really a "Magical" Girl?
Are we sure she's not just a "Tangible" Girl?
Then on the lung capacity test,
she totally maxed out the counter.
Is that something that even has a maximum?!
It made a really cool sound.
Grr...
GRR...
Meanwhile, I have to rest at least once when carrying
even a small bag of rice home from the store!
I think you could be a bit more athletic than that.
Well then... I guess I'll go show her who's boss!
I forget, is grip strength proportional to punch strength?
FREEZE
Recess will end in 3 minutes.
Recess is about to end, so we should
probably head back to the classroom.
You've got 3 whole minutes,
that's plenty of time to pick a fight!
FWIP
Get out there, girl!
I have to find a place to hide and launch a sneak attack.
Hey Chiyoda! Yoshida from Class D is a descendent
of the Dark Clan and has something for you!
You backstabber!
Oh crap, she's coming. She's coming!
What?
Sh-she's huge! A whole head taller than me!
Come on, Yuko. Give it to her straight!
Oh, you're that little girl from yesterday.
Gah! "Little girl"?!
Growl... snarl!
Whoza callin little! Punkimma grow way tallrthen u!
Yuko! Your brain and your mouth
can't keep up with each other!
Who're you callin' little?! Don't get cocky, you punk!
I'm still young enough to grow way taller than you!"
That's what you meant to say!
Yeah, what she said!
Sorry, I didn't mean to offend you.
I just objectively thought you were on the short side.
Outrage! Outrage! Outrage...!
That doesn't change anything!
If she's trying to pick a fight, then she's got one!
Outrage!!
I am Shami...
Uh-huh.
Shadow Mistress Yuko!
To restore my ancestors to their former glory
and to conkeer... ahem, conquer the world of darkness...
Inhale
...I've come to end the life of a Magical Girl!
Uh-huh.
Huff...
Out of Ammo
...and that's the deal.
I see.
You flubbed up twice, huh?
Because you kept interrupting
and throwing me off my pace!
Want to try again?
No interruptions this time, okay?
Okay, give it one more shot. "Shamiko," was it?
No! I am Yuko Yoshida, also known as Shami...
Shadow Mistress Yuko!
Outrage!!
Snicker
So, you are "Sha-mi-ko" then.
Don't laugh!
Don't worry about sounding cool, Shami!
Thumbs up!!
Stop helping that nickname catch on!
No big deal!
Shamirin?
Huh?! What did you say?
UGH
Nothing.
UWAA! PREPAAAAREEE YOURSEEEEEEEELLLLF!
Get her!
Go!
Take this, and that, and this, and that...!
BONK      BONK      BONK      BONK      BONK      BONK
B... BONK... BONK...
BO...
Sigh...
M-my sides hurt... and my wrists, too...
She's a bigger wimp than I thought.
Are you okay?
A Demon Girl is attacking you
and yet you won't even transform...
Why didn't you try to dodge at the very least?!
Because I didn't deem it necessary to avoid your attacks.
That's right. I forgot this girl
stopped a truck with one hand.
I never thought my first battle would go so poorly.
I should have eaten more to give myself extra energy.
Is that really the problem here?
If you want a pastry, I've got one.
A pastry?!
If you take any more pity on me,
I think I might cry, so just stop!
I see some tears already, no?
No, I stopped them before any could actually come out.
Oh really?
Do you have a minute?
Huh?
Can you stand?
SHAMIKO'S PERSPECTIVE
Come on, get up.
...Come on, get up...
EEEEEEK!
SHAMIKO'S PERSPECTIVE
Eek!
What are you...?
Don't tell me, she's going to throw me with all her might?
IMAGINATION
Nooooo!
Demon Eradication Attack!
Nooo!
I'm doomed, I should have accepted
that pastry when I had the chance!
I...
I'm bewwy sowwy!
She's emotionally weak, too!
SHIVER
The way you throw punches needs some work.
Bwuh?
Unless you put your thumb here like this, you'll get hurt.
Don't just use your arm,
you have to swing your whole body like this.
SWISH
This is an odd sight for a school hallway.
You should aim for the chin or the stomach. Give it a try.
Huh? What?
Just give it a try.
BRING
IT
ON
Okay.
POOOOOOOW!
It made a different sound this time.
Waaaaaah
Waaaah
It sounded a lot stronger than before!
Your style...
...or form, rather...
Well...
Uh....
Yeah...
Sigh
You might want to consider using projectiles instead.
D-d-d...
Don't think this means you've won!
Waaaaaah
That's that. See you later, Chiyoda.
Uh, sure.
Don't give up, Yuko!
Waaaaaaaah
Train your entire body until you're strong enough
to become a great demon!
Sniffle     Sniffle
Sniffle, sniffle... Sniffle, sniffle...
JAGATARA CHIPS
TUNA, SEA URCHIN,
& FISH EGG FLAVOR
Yeah, these are good.
I think I'll buy some more.
Did you see the new dance?
Yeah! Yeah!
I watched it the other day!
It was so awesome.
I know right?
Oh, hey Ryoko!
Huh? You're just going home now?
WEAPON
ENCYCLOPEDIA
That's a huge book you've got there.
That looks like a pretty complicated book.
I just borrowed it from the library.
See you tomorrow!
Later.
Hi-yah!
Huh? I know that voice.
Hi-yah! Hi-yah! Hi-yah!
HI-YAH!
Ouch, ouch, ouch! Owww, my sides are killing me...
Hey, Sis.
Oh!
Hey, Ryo.
Crap, my sides...
Tama Sakura Shopping District
You caught me doing something
really embarrassing, Ryo.
You aren't wasting any effort in your quest
to become a great demon, huh, Sis?
That's right! I'm going to give it my all from here on out!
You've made your first step on the path
to becoming the leader of the demon horde.
Hehehe... I'm not so sure about that.
It's Mom.
Welcome back.
Were you spending time together?
I met up with Sis on my way home.
Were you out shopping, mom?
Yes! You wouldn't believe it!
Brown Mushroom
Enoki
Mushrom
I got two extra stamps for my lottery card
by buying some mushrooms today!
That's a big haul!
Make sure you stick them in the fridge later.
BANDA TERRACE
Mushrooms are yummy.
I'll be sure to season them a bunch.
Sounds like it will go great with rice.
This is the tale of a girl
who received demonic powers over night,
and must rise up to defeat a Magical Girl
in order to save her family from the grips of poverty.
Or something to that effect.
The Demon Girl Next Door
Preview
I'm Yuko Yoshida! Today I became Shami...
Shadow Mistress Yuko, the Demon Girl.
But this is where I'm supposed
to talk about the next episode, right?
Shamiko, let's do some proper warm-ups next time.
Uwa! The Pink Magical Girl
Preview
How Sporty Are You?! Everything is Fluctuating
is headed straight my way again!
We've got to find a proper weapon for you, too.