I asked you for a retake
on my Crisis Management form, didn't I?
And that's exactly what I did.
What part did you actually change?!
The first time you transformed,
you told me that your stomach felt cold, so...
...I fixed up the area around your belly button
and thighs with some warmer fabric!
You hardly changed anything!
That's not the problem at all!
It's embarrassing for me to show so much skin!
I'd prefer to just use my gym clothes!
They're easy to move in and plenty warm!
But why?
That's my line. Why is this so hard for you to understand?
The fact is that we gain more power by showing off
more skin, it's an issue in our bloodline.
Who came up with that idea?!
This is becoming a big pain, so I'm just going
to revert it back to normal next time.
When I have to rush to transform you, it's easy to
screw up how many parts there are and where they go.
Don't get so irritated! Please do your best, Ancestor!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Taiyou mabushisugite
(Chikachika me o kosutta)
Omowazu tobidashita yo
(Dokidoki no hajimiari sa)
Yurayura yureru maegami hidarite de osaetara
Itsumo no keshiki ga kirameku yo
(Three, two, one)
Ima sugu tsutaetai futari no himitsu
Watashitachi nara dekiru yo
(Itsumo tonari ni ite)
Kitto
(Shijiteru kara)
Machikado de mitsuketa daiji na takaramono
Tatoe kimi ga tooku hanaretemo kanarazu oikakeru yo
Zutto kagayaiteru mirai wa koko ni aru
Otanoshimi wa kore kara
Final Exams!!
Today I'm One of Those Brainy Demons!!
Shamiko! Is something on your mind?
Yeah, I'm having trouble.
Let me guess... by the look on your face,
you're having trouble deciding on what to eat first!
That's not it!
I was thinking about what ways I could get Momo
to acknowledge me as a strong ally.
I get the feeling that she's taking me too lightly.
Wow. You sure put a lot of thought into things, Shamiko.
But I haven't made much progress
on building my stamina, so I still have a long way to go.
It's true that you don't have much stamina, but I think
you have a lot of room for improvement elsewhere.
Like up here.
Up... here?
Presenting: Stag-Beetle Shamiko!
Presenting: Stag-Beetle Shamiko!!
You mean grow out my horns more?!
Nope.
I'm telling you to use your head
to become a brainy demon.
Final Exams
Hey, Momo!
The final exams before summer vacation
are coming up, so I demand that we have a duel!
A duel?
I thought we had a ceasefire right now.
Our bloody feud with each other is in
a totally different category from a friendly duel!
Shamiko was telling me that she feels depressed
because you haven't been taking her very seriously.
So, she wants to beat you in a duel of wits
and get you to think better of her!
Shamiko was crying about it earlier
while poking at her lunch of plain rice.
She said, "I get no side dishes and no love!"
I said no such thing!
Stop blowing everything out of proportion!
Okay, but just so you know my grades are pretty good.
What is that?
It's my scores from the midterm exams.
I left it crammed in my desk.
Wait, you just let your exam scores
get crumpled up like an accordion?!
So careless!
I don't think the inside of your desk
is in any better shape, Shamiko.
96 points, 90 points, 88 points, 100 points?!
Points
All of these high scores in the science sections...
So there's more in that head of yours
than just protein and chicken.
It's weird because you're normally
such a huge mess otherwise.
Was that your impression of me this whole time?
So, you want a friendly duel?
If I win, will you give up on having a fun summer
vacation and immerse yourself totally in training?
Momo, are you mad at me?
Not at all.
Hey, Shamiko. What were your scores like
on the midterm exams?
Well... I tried really hard on all the fine arts sections
and got around 70 points.
But for the sciences, I totally bombed.
Uh, that's bad.
Say Momochi, are there any subjects
that you're bad at?
I suppose out of all of them I'm lacking most in history.
I got about 75 points there.
Okay, how about you make
this a duel based on your world history scores?
Roger
that!
Roger that!
Hmmm...
To make up for the handicap, Shamiko will agree to
dumbbell lifts 100 x however many points she loses by!
That sounds fair.
I don't think we should be putting any bets
on a friendly duel!
I can't believe Momo has good grades...
I never would have guessed.
It's fine, all you have to do is win.
If you go into this thinking that you're going to lose,
you really will lose!
The topics for world history on the final exam will be:
Ancient Egypt, Mesopotamia, Greece...
Did you say Mesopotamia?!
Egypt and Mesopotamia are right up my alley!
Back then I was at the peak of my glory days!
It was just around when I got sealed away,
so everything felt fresh and I wasn't such a sore loser!
That's what you consider your glory days?
After I was sealed away, my statue was passed around
to a lot of folks and I got to explore the orient!
My powers were nearly drained
so I spent a lot of time sleeping, but...
I was pretty famous around those parts!
Just looking at this textbook, I can tell you
I was friends with this guy and that guy!
Th-that's incredible!
What kind of person was this guy like?
He used me to hold down a stack of papyrus...
Sob, sob.
Sob, sob, sob.
Don't cry, Ancestor!
I agree with what you said before!
I can't go into this thinking that I'll lose.
All I have to do is win, it's simple!
Yep, yep!
Dog
Tomorrow is the test, but I haven't been able
to remember anything.
Good grief, you really have no idea
how to be efficient about anything.
Do you want me to pitch in and help?
All you have to do is take the test while I
communicate with you in your head, just like this.
Is this telepathy?
Indeed. And I know all there is to know
about Mesopotamia and Egypt, remember?
Just smuggle my statue into the test with you
and I'll help you get the answers!
We'll call it... Operation: Ancestor Answers!
ANCESTOOR!
ANSWERS
That's not an operation, it's just plain cheating!
No way!
It's a perfectly valid way to apply
your unique powers as a Demon Girl!
Not happening!
Cheating is something we must never do!
You haven't forgotten that we're Demons, right?
We're aligned with the darkness. Chaos is our
fundamental source of nourishment that gives us power.
I-is that really true?
When you said that you wanted to make Momo
acknowledge you, I thought it was a good opportunity.
You can overwhelm Momo and totally unsettle her.
If you do that and manage
to strip her heart free of its armor,
it will ultimately make it easier to use our clan's power
to invade her dreams!
All you have to do is cheat, I mean,
use your totally natural Demon powers!
Then it will bring success in the future, ensuring
the revival of our clan and your family's happiness!
"My family's happiness"?
Don't you want your little sister to live a life of luxury?
Don't you want to get air conditioning in this apartment?
Consider your mother and our entire clan... just do it!
Tomorrow you will claim victory against Momo!
Refreshing
Shiso Tea
Heh, heh, heh...
Refreshing
Shiso Tea
This is the perfect cosplay for me.
How did I let myself get dragged into this?
Oh, it's Momo. Good morning!
Good morning.
You seem kind of sleepy,
are you making sure to eat properly?
It's because I stayed up late last night.
Huh?
Shamiko...
I think you got the wrong impression somehow.
I have never taken you lightly.
Also, I don't like losing.
So, let's do our best today.
Okay, I'm coming around
to collect your phones and other devices.
Excuse me, Shadow Mistress?
Could you tell me what that is?
Um, this is... well...
Refreshing
Shiso Tea
Shamiko, just stick with the plan
and tell her that I'm a thermos.
This is...
...my precious and irreplaceable Ancestor!
It's very important to me,
so please keep it someplace safe.
Shamiko?!
Why, Shamiko?!
Why didn't you tell her I was a thermos?!
Ancestor, I'm sorry.
I'm going to fight this duel fair and square.
SOME DAYS LATER
Momo.
Name: Shadow Mistress Yuko
World History Final Exam
How did you do on the test?
95 points.
I lost...
700 dumbbell lifts...
You don't have to go that hard.
It's an exorbitant amount anyway.
Don't patronize me! But at least let me
split it between multiple days!
By the way, Shamiko.
Have you seen the list of top scorers on the final exams?
1st) Sion Ogura - 1190 points
2nd) Kumi Shirozaki - 1185 points
3rd) Lilith, the witch who governs over darkness - 1181 points
4th) Mika Kajitani - 1172 points
5th) Mai Kuramoto - 1164 points
Huh? Ancestor?
Why are you on the list of top scorers?
Well, your teacher was quite accommodating.
Ms. Lilith, are you a fan of Mesopotamia?
Would you like to take the test yourself?
Certainly!
And so, I ended up taking the same test
as the two of you did.
While I was at it, I took the tests
for all the other subjects, too!
What do you think? I've got a pretty good
head on my shoulders, huh?
I lost to Shamicen...?!
Huh?
Momo, are you freaking out?
Wait, I know! Ms. Lilith is always hanging out
near Shamiko's bag,
Looking for a home
Please take this bird
REQUIRED EXTRA LESSONS
ENGLISH
Shadow Mistress Yuko
so all of the textbooks and handouts
for the test were offered to her!
She must have cheated during the test by looking
over all of those for the answers in her sealed space!
Isn't that what you did, Ms. Lilith?
To be honest, that idea never even occurred to me.
You're way more of a schemer than I am.
Yikes...
That reminds me, Shamiko.
Yes?
You told the teacher that I was your precious ancestor
and not just a paperweight.
Oh, yeah.
As a Demon Girl you may be pretty weak, but out of
all the people I've met in my life you're the most...
Well...
...you're really bad at living life!
Make sure you eat more food! And get more sleep!
And above all, avoid getting yourself sealed!
R-right!
Your failure has further postponed my great revival
and planned tour of the world's hot springs!
Hold on a second, Ancestor! Is that why you were so
insistent about make me cheat and do other bad stuff?!
I had already heard as much from Anri, but...
...you really can't bring yourself to be underhanded, huh?
That's not-!
D-don't laugh at me!
But in the end, I did lose to Ms. Lilith in the test overall...
Oh, is that a complaint?
I bet you must be frustrated, Magical Girl!
It's not frustrating or anything, really.
Shamiko might not be very strong,
but she's really brainy for a demon!
None of this is going like I had hoped...
Don't think this means you've won!
Hey... ugh... I'm not a... gah...
dumbbell for you to... ugh... lift like... gah! Ugh!
Don't think this means you've won...!
Don't give up, Shamiko! Keep your will as tough as
your horns, but aim to be a really openminded demon!
You said that I was something very important to you.
Even if that was only flattery, it made me really happy.
I wasn't just trying to flatter you.
You're the most precious thing in the world to me.
Shamiko...
Hey, Shamiko...
You already left for school, but you forgot your gym
clothes, your pen case and your most precious thing...
You're just a forgetful little scamp, aren't you?
The New Refrigerator Dance
Slide and spin.
Spin, spin, spin!
And then stop.
And finally...
Hooray~!
Mom's excited because today
the new refrigerator is coming.
You're in high spirits today.
Well, refrigerators these days are simply incredible.
The inside is so spacious! And it'll automatically
make all the delicious ice you want!
And it even has a mysterious function
that somehow keeps the vegetable drawers all moist!
I'm going to be able to make
so many wonderful meals ahead of time!
Ding-Dong
I'm sorry, Miss. There's no way this unit
is going to fit through your door.
You're going to have to consider
downsizing to a smaller one.
For the rest of the day, all mom did was cry.
And our ancestor got dragged
into drinking a bunch of sake with her.
Tama River
Good morning!
Good morning, Mikan.
Huh? Isn't Momo with you?
I talked Momo out of training so that
we could take a break just for today.
Huh?
There's something I want to do together with you
in secret from Momo.
Don't tell me... we're doing this in secret because
she's going to pound me down like a pot of tea?!
Oh, ho, ho! Take this! Demon Brewtalizer!
How many pots are you planning to use me for?
At my house we usually reuse the leaves 7 or 8 times...
Why did the color just drain from your face?!
Sakura Cinema
This is a...
It's a movie theater, Shamiko!
I didn't invite you here for fun, you know.
I want you to help me gain better control over my curse.
Look, this seems like it'll
be scary based on the title alone.
Cossack
Dance of the Dead
Double Feature with
Zombie's Summer Vacation
This is just a way of training ourselves
to be stronger mentally!
Cossack
Dance of the Dead
Cossack Dance of the Dead.
Double Feature with...
Double Feature with
Zombie's Summer Vacation
Zombie's Summer Vacation.
Cossack
Dance of the Dead
Double Feature with
Zombie's Summer Vacation
If we spend time getting used to things like this,
then we'll be able to stay relatively cool in bad situ-
Sorry, I have't met my quota of dumbbell lifts for today!
Ah, wait a sec!
Gah!
Your tail really is convenient.
It's inconvenient!
And it's surprisingly soft.
Zombie Shark
vs
SUSHI SHARK
Why did you have to invite me though?
Because I know that doing mental training
would benefit you, too.
It would?
Shamiko... Shamiko... Shamiko...!
Those who are strong and steadfast
have access to more stable magic.
But...
...this is clearly a horror movie!
If you start getting nervous during the showing,
then your curse will take full effect, right?
*Whenever Mikan becomes
distraught, her curse
{brings great misfortune upon
the people around her!!
Whenever Mikan becomes distraught, her curse
brings great misfortune upon the people around her.
In that case what's going to happen to me
when I'm sitting right next to you?!
I'll pay for your ticket and you can eat
whatever you'd like. I'll even take you to the hospital.
Does that mean a hospital visit is guaranteed?!
The Warring States Era
of Cuteness
A Wonderful Gathering
101 Mascots
Zombie Shark
SUSHI SHARK
Please just come with me! I don't want
to cause any more pain and trouble for Momo!
I promise I'll do my best to stay in control!
Mikan...
But even I might have an anemic panic attack
if there's lots of gore.
I've gotten used to ghosts lately, though.
Wait, so ghosts don't scare you at all? That's surprising.
Yeah. They don't scare me
because they're just like my Ancestor.
Shamiko?!
You haven't had a proper physical body
for a long time, right Ancestor?
But you always appearing in my dreams and
the way you talk seems like an auditory hallucination.
This girl... she's totally put me into the same category
as a ghost that needs busting.
Hey, Magical Girl.
Are movies more fun than watching a DVD?
If you enjoy films then I think you'll have a lot of fun.
The screen is huge and the sound system
makes for a totally different experience.
"Popcorn"?
Popcorn
What is this? Is it yummy?
It's one of the most delicious things you can get
at the theater. Plus it goes great with cola!
Do you want to try some? Here!
Can I make an offering just like this?
Yeah, thish doesh go great wiff cola.
This is just salted, but they have
a premium version with melted butter.
Hey, Shamiko! Thish can be another part of your training!
Ancestor!
I'm really relieved that you're coming to see it with me.
I was afraid to go all by myself.
No problem. This is actually my first time
seeing a movie at the theater.
Although it's not a genre I particularly like,
I'm still pretty excited!
Grain Sentai:
Suihanger The Movie
Here, I got us tickets.
I wonder if we need one for your Ancestor, too?
I'll pay the price for my Ancestor.
I have enough money from working a part-time job.
Excuse me, one ticket for seniors please.
Shamiko... are you saying that you think I'm a senior?
Huh? Seniors are those older than 65, right?
Well, yeah, but...
There's nobody in here except for us!
This theater doesn't get a lot of traffic.
On weekday mornings it's pretty much like
you're renting the place out.
I made sure to research it ahead of time!
Now we're free to make any reaction we want
and not get in trouble!
Yeah, but if you react, then doesn't that mean
your curse activates?
It's okay. Like those famous
martial artists say, "Be as water."
Although I may seem jumpy on the outside, I promise
you that my heart will be as still as a fish in water.
I really think I've gotten the hang of- EEEEK!
BUZZ!
Mikan! You're going to rip my tail off!
Oh, I'm sorry! I couldn't help it!
Gotta focus.
Gotta stay focused.
Do you mind if I hold your hand?
S-sure.
Mikan, are you holding your breath?
I'm holding back the flow of my magic.
Hey punks, make sure
you turn off those cellphones. Got it?
Free
Yourself
From Your
Phone
Damn, enough ringing already.
I'm trying to finish this announcement!
Oh crap, I just answered the phone I should've turned off!
That's why you've gotta totally kill the battery on these things!
Mikan's been holding her breath for over 6 minutes now.
I'll just go ahead and keep
a constant check on her pulse...
Damn zombies.
Whole town went to hell on my day off.
Why don't any of the bullets actually
HIT the heroes?! It's totally unfair!
Just accept it, Shamiko.
That's how the world works in movies.
Don't give up, Zombies!
The protagonist is hiding under the tank!
Shamiko! Your tail is blocking the screen!
Huh? This is actually fun!
Meanwhile, Mikan had quietly fainted
and lost consciousness.
Yuko! I actually kept my composure!
I was unconscious for part of it, though.
Wait, why are you crying?!
What's wrong? Did you hurt yourself?
I don't think it's possible for my curse
to attack your stomach or anything!
That's not it.
I'm just so touched...
All of the zombies and ghosts,
even though their guts were hanging out,
they really tried their hardest to overcome
the ridiculous strength of the heroes.
That was the side you were sympathizing with?!
Mikan, I just want to say I'm so happy you invited me.
I was scared at first, but I ended up getting so much
out of this experience once we dived in.
O-oh, really? I'm glad to hear that.
I haven't really made any friends since I came here,
and I've been so distressed over my curse.
But today I managed to keep it under control.
And that's all because you stayed with me, Yuko.
Um!
From now on, I think you should call me "Shamiko"!
Huh?
Because that's my proper Demon Girl name.
Well, a nickname born from it anyway.
Next time, let's go see a movie
that you would actually enjoy instead.
Like this mascot character one.
The Warring States Era of Cuteness
A Wonderful Gathering
101 Mascots
Mikan and Shamiko, what a surprise.
Huh?
Momo! Why are you here?
And what is up with that headgear?
Don't tell me my curse caused this?!
No, I'm wearing this because I chose to.
Did you go see the mascot character movie?
Yep. I had nothing else to do today.
Are you a big fan of Miss Tama Sakura?
No.
It's not like I'm in love with her or anything.
I would just say I feel a strong sense of duty
to support her financially.
Even though you're wearing that fancy light-up hat?
Because Miss Tama Sakura is trying really hard,
but she's still a relatively minor character.
She's an official city character, but only has 80 followers.
What's a "follower"?
But anyway...
I'm glad to see that you two are getting along.
I suppose you came here to hang out together.
No! We weren't here to hang out!
I didn't want to cause any more trouble for you, Momo!
It's fine. I've done nothing but push you to train every
day. I didn't consider that you might want some time off.
The battery on my sun visor is going to die soon,
so I'm going home.
What kind of reason is that? W-wait!
Why do all of my attempts to do what feels right always
end up going the exact opposite of how I intended?
Whoa-whoa-whoaaaa!
Mikan, please just stay calm! It won't stop! It just keeps popping!
The Magical Girl later took responsibility.
and paid compensation for the broken popcorn machine.
The extra popcorn was gathered up by the Demon Girl
Do you think they'd mind if I ate some? Whoaaa!
who took it home and happily ate it for days after.
Whoaaa! Whoaaa! Whoa-whoaaaa!
Look, I didn't leave you out
because I wanted to go and have fun.
I'm not bothered by it at all, honestly.
But your eyes look way more dead
than they normally do!
Excuse me, but the cabbage is cooked now.
Would you like me to serve it up?
Hey, Shamiko. Make an offering
of ponzu sauce to me, would you?
You used to be a lot more energetic back in the day.
The tofu is also ready to eat, by the way.
What happened to you over the last few years?
I should probably get going.
Wait, Shamiko! Don't go yet!
I have to attend extra lessons at school tonight.
The time hath come.
It's totally fine, really. Let's just start eating.
Don't give up, Shamiko!
Navigate your way through touchy situations and
Wow. Looks delicious.
become a Demon who knows all the best ways to react!
Momo! The hot pot is on this side!
If you don't pay attention, you're going to burn yourself!
Well, tonight's lessons are over.
Just a little longer, then summer vacation will start.
Huh?
That's weird. Maybe I just imagined it.
I thought I felt someone's eyes on me.
Oh! Shamiko!
Hello, Ogura.
Did you have extra lessons tonight, Shamiko?
Yes, I did. What about you?
I was just working on some magic in the lab.
Oh no! I can't say anything yet!
What's the matter?
Sorry, I can't explain yet. I have to keep it secret for now.
Oh, but maybe just sharing a little would be okay.
Ah, just forget it. Don't mind me. See you again!
Bye for now, Shamiko!
Sure, see you later.
I forgot that Ogura from Class C
is in some sort of weird club.
In fact, the other day...
I'm going to be late for the ritual,
so do you mind taking these out, too?
...she said something like that.
At the time, I wondered
what "ritual" she was talking about,
but I figured it would probably be best
if I just ignored that.
Plus, the main theme of that episode was cleaning up
all the garbage and dealing with Mikan's problem.
Besides, it's better if mysteries like that
just stay mysterious.
Hey, Shamiko.
What's on your mind, Ancestor?
Today was sure a whirlwind, but I greatly enjoyed
the excitement of a movie on the big screen.
I'm so glad that you had a good time.
Indeed!
I wouldn't mind if you took me back again sometime.
That special little seat they had just for me was fabulous!
I was able to make out every minor detail
on that huge screen!
Apparently, there are other theaters
that offer these things called 3D and 4D,
where the screen pops out at you,
and the seats move, and even water shoots out on you!
I'm not sure I'd want the seat to move.
I get dizzy really easily.
Oh, that's a really good point.
The Demon Girl Next Door
Sassouto shobu shite
Yatchau kedo makechatte
Fugainai nai ne
Shoushin tenshin
Kibun wa sunsun demo
Shippo de henji shiyou
Chounai de waiwai shite
Inu made bow-wow de
Tende meimei de
Shunka shuutou
Shippai shita tte waraitobasou
Ano koro to onaji you ni kokoro tsumuide
Kono machi de deaeta kiseki
Kanaete yo
Zenkai da wa tire shou ippai
Warning mada kikikanri enjoy
Toridori saita iro canvas kakenuke
Sunset da wa, kangaete bakari ja
Sou, mae!
Hora, donna iro datte yume kasanete
Motto asobou ne
Preview
Next time, I get invited to Ogura's laboratory
where she apparently is doing research on demons.
Shamiko, do you realize what she's going to do to you?
I'm coming with you.
Is she really going to make a new vessel
for me to inherit? What's it like? Tell me!
Hey Sis, the laptop we borrowed from Momo
The Ancestor Evolves!! A Pair of Glasses Reflect Within a Dark Lab
has been acting up recently.
The next episode is packed with content as usual.
Momo stole my closing line!