Salutations, everyone!
It's me, Shami- I mean, Shadow Mistress Yuko!
A few days ago, somehow or another
I ended up taking lessons from Momo
to learn how to use projectiles
and she really put me through the grinder!
A lot of things led up to it, but I went with Momo
to an abandoned factory that she owns
and that's where my training began.
I was totally thrown for a loop!
Momo was so gung-ho about it, she made the training
extra hard and it left me super sore and frazzled!
Thanks to her and the motivation of 100% beef for dinner,
I was able to shoot out some of my own magic.
But it was too weak, so the magic just came back at me
and it hurt as bad as an intramuscular injection?
Major ouchies...
Hallelujah, amen.
What are you doing?
Making an offering!
CLASSIC
MILD
TEA
This is a statue of my ancestor who was sealed away,
the founder of the Dark Clan!
Oh?
I was told to leave some delicious treats
and magazines as offerings.
Shamiko! We brought some offerings, too!
I found a nice little something after looking around.
CLASSIC
MILD
TEA
I hope your ancestor enjoys it.
As you can see, everyone is helping me out!
She's been making a lot of offerings lately.
So that's why you always carry that around with you.
Oh right, I hadn't explained any of this to you yet.
I see.
All this time I thought it was just some rock
you scavenged to add extra weight on yourself.
I was impressed you would train like that.
I didn't scavenge it and it's not for training!
TEA
The magic it gives off is really weak,
I can hardly even sense it.
I think it weighs about 2 pounds.
Don't use it as a research subject!
Huh?
What's this on the bottom, Shamiko?
A switch...?
Why?
This is the tale of an incompetent Demon Girl
who gets bamboozled and falls into the debt of her rival,
while also learning to grow and mature as a person.
Or something to that effect.
The Demon Girl Next Door
Sharpen Your Mind!!
The Newly Awakened Powers of the Magical Girl
Ms. Sata and Ms. Ogura, would you mind stepping back?
I never realized that there
was a switch on the bottom of it...
Sure thing.
Just call me "Anri."
Did you just flip it on without warning?!
Why would you do that?!
There's no one else in the classroom right now.
And if there's some sort of evil gimmick built in,
then the safest place to test it is a place where
I can deal with it if necessary.
What were you planning to do
if an ogre or a snake popped out of it?
I would obliterate it into nothing.
Then we could just forget about it.
Ruthless!
It might be a secret weapon meant for me...
But... now...
Shamiko?!
Don't tell me...
She was finally reduced to eating off the street?!
I think you've totally got the wrong idea.
Even Shamiko wouldn't go that far, you know!
Is it safe to join you over there now?
Ah!
Huh?
I felt my consciousness slip away really fast and then...
Where am I?
Am I dreaming?
Who goes there?
I know that voice!
Oh... long time, no see.
My ancestor is in lounge mode.
Oh it's just you, Yuko?
Would you mind waiting just a moment?
Sure.
Shuffle. Shuffle. Shuffle. Shuffle.
Shuffle
Heave-ho!
Oh crap, my belt!
I guess I don't need the shoes!
Well then, my cute little descendant...
GLIMMER
...welcome to the sealed space within my statue!
I'll help you find the rest of your outfit.
Forget it! This is just my sense of fashion!
But you're one to talk,
what is that gaudy thing you've put my statue in?!
CLASSIC
MILD
TEA
It came free with a bottle of tea.
The statue of your ancestors
should be revered and respected!
Where is your sense of dignity?!
This is so uncool it hurts to look at!
B-but, it's my absolute favorite bag
and the softest one I own!
I dropped the statue the first time I took it outside...
...and I felt so bad about it!
But if you think the bag is uncool, then...
It's your favorite...?
Yes!
I was just kidding! That bag is just fine!
Thinking about it, this symbol makes it look
super cute and eco-friendly!
TEA
Or, you know, you could just wrap it up in a towel
that you're not going to use anymore!
What a relief! I'm so glad you like it, too!
Totally!
Anyway...
The fact you were able to come here
means that you've met all the requirements.
"Requirements"?
Yep!
A moderate signal
Step 1: A moderate signal!
Good Weather
Step 2: Good weather!
The perfect amount of calories per offering
WALKING SHARK ZOMBIES
SEASON 3
PLAIN YOGURT
Step 3: The perfect amount of calories per offering!
And also... flipping the ancestor switch on!
When all of those requirements are met,
it enables me to borrow the body of a descendent
and wage our war in their place!
Wh-whaaat?!
This'll be my first outing in a long time!
Then what am I supposed to do in the meantime?!
Take a seat under the kotatsu
and just relax here for a while!
Whoa... she's out cold, but her eyes are still open.
It's almost like her soul is missing, I hope she's all right.
Get back, you two!
It's been some time
since I last felt the wind across my skin.
This aura is different... she's not Shamiko!
Indeed!
I am the witch who governs
over the eternal powers of darkness! Lilith!
I've supplanted the soul of my descendant
to borrow their body and slaughter a Magical Girl!
I'm Shami! I mean, I'm the great ascendant
of Shadow Mistress Yuko!
Shamiko's "ascendant"...?
So, "Shami-cen"?
Hey, don't give me any corny nicknames!
Momo Chiyoda! I know all about you!
Don't think so highly of yourself!
I've watched you bully my adorable little descendant
and I'm going to make you pay for it!
Um, although her presence has made Shamiko cry
before, Momochiyo has never actually bullied her.
In fact, I would say that she's helped Shamiko grow.
She even baited her with food.
Shamiko has actually started to look healthier lately.
O-oh, is that so?
You have my thanks for that, then.
Shami-
I mean, I also owe you for saving
Shadow Mistress Yuko from that dump truck!
In honor of that I'll make sure you die
without any suffering!
"Shadow Mistress" is pretty tough to say
without flubbing up, right?
Snicker.
Snicker
I changed my mind!
I'm definitely going to grind you into dust!
You may think you have it easy right now,
but soon your face will be twisted in unbearable pain!
Whaddya doing?!
I'm worried that you're going to fall.
I-I won't fall! Even if I did, I certainly don't need your help!
Just ignore me and keep giving your speech.
And don't pretend it's so easy
to slip through my defenses!
Huh?! Even though you're
pretty much totally unguarded?
I'm sorry, I should have been more sensitive about it.
Okay, that's it! This means war!
Oh wow, this has all the broadcast channels.
But nothing good is on right now...
Are you ready to say your prayers?
When the seal is finally broken,
I will ride the local bus to every nearby hot spring,
Madam Lilith!
This is a famous hot spring!
and enjoy them all to my heart's content!
Then after that, I'll just conquer the entire world
whenever the time seems right!
I think you should come up with a more meticulous plan
for that second half while you have the chance.
You're really starting to get on my nerves!
Let our battle begin!
Hiyaaaah!
What the...? How is it THIS heavy?!
This is amazing! You can play
with the console we have at home in here!
Time out for a sec. I totally have an invincible barrier up
right now, so don't attack okay?
Uh, okay.
Wh-what is wrong with this body?
I barely even move and it feels like
my balance is totally thrown off.
Not to mention I run out of breath!
It's hard to summon any real strength,
and my neck and shoulders feel way too stiff!
Plus my vision seems more than a little blurry!
Um, Ms. Lilith?
I think that body can't keep up with all the movements
that you're attempting to perform.
Does that mean this body is an absolute hunk of junk?!
No, uh...
I would say it has reflexes that are hard to ignore
and is currently dealing with a lot of stress...
So, uh....
Your awkward explanations never help!
Fine, then I'll just have to beat you with magic!
Huh? Why is it coming back at- OW!
Hey, you commoners! No laughing!
I'm not... laughing... at all...
I can hear you doing it!
If you keep using Shamiko's body like that,
it's only going to cause her pain later.
S-stay back!
I have to find a place to hide and regroup!
So, am I right to assume you won't be able
to get very far without this?
Cease, commoner! How dare you pierce
my magnificent statue! Give that back!
Sorry, don't take it personally.
We prefer the regular old Shami over you.
Curse you!
Don't... Don't tell me...!
Shamicen Eradication Attack!
She's going to throw me with all her might?
Do... Do I get one last wish before I die?
She gives up way too fast!
Where am I? What happened?!
What is this?! What is this?! What is this?! What is THIS?!
This is the Tama Health Spa.
We came here to fulfill your ancestor's last wish.
It's a hot spring paradise.
Oh, Momo is still alive.
Does that mean my ancestor lost?
Did she put up an awesome fight?!
Yep, she sure did.
That's great.
Gah... my whole body is sore.
Your ancestor pushed your body pretty hard.
You can have this back now.
It's still too early for your body to take the strain,
so I blocked off the switch with some epoxy adhesive.
What the heck is "epoxy"?
Also, Ms. Lilith had a message for you.
Don't think this means you've won!
But tell Shamiko that I'm sorry!
She said something about coming back
after considering a new method of attack.
Oh, so my ancestor's name is Lilith?
By the way...
Receipt
Ms. Shadow Mistress Yuko
$17.20 (1,720 yen)
Charges for last wish
Tama Health Spa
She didn't have any cash to pay for the spa,
so she asked that I add it to your debt, Shamiko.
Tama Health Spa
Now that you're awake,
how about you go get in the hot springs?
I'm going right now! I'm going to get my money's worth!
Don't give up, Shamiko! When your body feels sore,
that's the time to drink milk and build muscle!
I owed her $4.50 for the train fare,
and now another $17.20 for the spa.
But she's renting me this spare school uniform for free.
What's wrong?
My debt to Momo more than tripled
after what happened the other day.
Yeah, it really snowballed out of control. This happens
every time you fall for one of Momo Chiyo's tricks.
You've gone totally snowballistic!
Debt
"Snowballistic"?!
At first, I was experiencing a fiery bankruption
but now I'm totally snowballistic...
...I'm both burning and freezing.
If you ask me, the best option is just to pay
it all back in one go. Don't you think?
Huh?
Just between you and me, I know a great job
that can earn big bucks in just one day.
Shopping Center Maruma
Food Staff Wanted!!
You're freaking me out.
Hey, Mom!
Can I work a temp job for just one day on the weekend?
At this rate I'm going to be snowballistic for life!
"Snowballistic"?
Well, I don't mind so long as you
got permission from the school.
But don't forget about the curse of the Light Clan.
You mean...
"The Yoshida family is cursed
to survive on only $400 a month."
Any money that's saved over that amount
is fated to slip right out of our hands.
Congratulations
Like when I have to send congratulatory money
to friends who suddenly got married.
Donation Box
Or when I throw some change into a donation box and
accidentally end up throwing my whole purse instead.
Or when my purse falls straight into the gutter.
More than half of those are just you being a klutz, mom...
When a huge bird snatched a paycheck straight
out my hands, I have to admit I laughed a little.
A bird?!
I sobbed afterwards, though.
But we've managed to survive oddly well
on only $400 a month.
Especially since Sis and I both go to school.
My body is really frail, so I end up
going to the hospital a lot, too.
Medical bills, school bills, and heating bills
are all exceptions that I can save extra money for.
This curse is oddly specific!
I'd really like to meet the Magical Girl
who came up with such a ridiculous idea!
Anyway, the point is that if you save up too much money,
then it will find a way to disappear,
so don't get too greedy with work.
A few days later
If you can just pay back your debt
and make progress with your goals,
I think that would be for the best.
MARUMA'S MEATS
I've gotta protect my cash and watch out for birds!
We're selling pork, not chicken, Shamiko.
Today I'm going to have you help me
by passing out some wiener samples.
Okay.
You really do have horns coming out of your head!
Just like Anri said!
But you know, this is just a normal job.
Are you okay with that?
Are you sure you wouldn't prefer
something more sinister?
Huh?
Anri told me...
The daughter of a distinguished family of darkness
has suffered a blow from her mortal enemy,
she was tricked into a monetary debt
comparable to the budget of a small city.
At least, that's what I heard.
My family is undistinguished, if anything!
Anri really embellished the story way too much!
Extra
Serving
I laid it on extra thick!
Listen closely, Shamiko.
If you cut the wieners like this and fry them up...
Ta-da!
They become little octopuses!
I-Is this magic?
You're such a sillybilly, Shamiko!
While we've got the chance, do you want to taste test?
Can I really?
Thank you so much!
These are garlic flavor.
And what you've got is the basil lemon flavor.
Do your best to promote them, okay?
What's a "basil" anyway?
Whoa! Yummy!
How can something be so delicious?!
How can something be so fresh?!
It's so salty and sour!
Out of this world!
I'm gonna work super hard!
For now...
I'll work hard to repay my debt, then challenge Momo
and undo the seal on my ancestor!
Then after that... uh...
Huh?
What exactly do I want to do
once I defeat a Magical Girl?
I'd never really considered it up until now.
Shamiko, you're doing great work!
Huh?
If we make good sales today, then I'll let you
take a bag of wieners home with you.
Really?!
Okay, I'll be in the back if you need me.
Once I beat the Magical Girl, I'll sell more wieners.
I'll release the seal,
then sell wieners and get more to take home!
Sell some, then take some home!
Sell some, then take some home...!
What're you doing?
Oh! A customer!
Help yourself to a free sample of the super,
ultra-yummy wieners we're selling!
Momo...?
Thanks.
Ga...
Gaaaaah!
Momo! What are you doing?!
Sorry, after I bit into it,
I realized that one wasn't quite ready.
So, what exactly are you doing here Shamiko?
I'm working hard to pay back all the money I owe you.
Normally you're my mortal enemy,
but today you're a customer.
Please try one of our samples.
I recommend the basil lemon flavor!
Wow, I'm impressed that you actually
know what basil is, Shamiko.
That's rude!
Of course, I know what basil is!
Where does basil comes from?
Well... it's an edible plant.
It's one of those plants you can eat, right?
You're not wrong, but...
Why are you making that face?!
What about you, Momo? Did you come to shop?
Great deal!!
Minced meat
$5.34 (534 yen)
Minced meat and... canned food?
Don't get hung up on details like that.
But this is amazing. You're so admirable, Shamiko!
Huh?
Even though you've awakened as a Demon Girl,
you've remained calm and collected.
Doing proper work in order to pay back your debt,
it's almost too pure.
Aren't you setting the bar a little low there?!
You haven't tried to rob any banks,
or even brainwash one of the world's billionaires.
I'd never do anything like that!
What kind of crazy things
did you get caught up in before we met?!
B-but that's not all!
I'm selling these wieners
to pay you back and then after that...
I'm going to fight with you...!
Seconds
0.0080 Seconds! She just set a new personal best!
Oh no, not the cute little octopuses!
Huh?
But how? All the octopuses are arranged on the plate
with a clean toothpick sticking out of each one!
Somehow, I managed to get them all
without dropping a single one.
You transformed?!
Uh, yeah...
You didn't burn yourself or anything, right?
I'm fine!
But why did you choose right now to transform?
You didn't even transform when I was beating up on you!
To be honest... I don't have very fond memories
of my time as a Magical Girl.
So I've avoided transforming as much as I can.
But...
I didn't want to see all of your hard work
go to waste just now.
Momo...
Considering the limits of my current power,
your punches are totally negligible,
but I definitely couldn't handle
all of those octopuses without transforming.
Huh?
Did I just hear you drop
a totally unnecessary comment in there?
As the octopuses fell to the ground,
I had to stab them all with a toothpick individually
and then make sure they made it safely onto a new plate.
Super Slow
It's the first time I've ever performed movements
so quick and complicated.
In the past, I was the type who just
bulldozed everything down with force...
I feel like I entered into a zone that I was never able
to even see back when I was in active service.
This whole experience has made me stronger somehow!
Thank you, Shamiko!
Is... Is that so?
A "zone," huh?
She just became even harder for me to beat...
Juicy Delicious Wieners
Basil Flavor
Garlic Flavor
I'm going to buy some of your wieners.
Uh, are you sure you want to buy that many?
Yeah. They were yummy.
Momo!
Don't think this means...!
No, that's not what I want to say.
Thank you very much.
Right back at you.
Amazing work today, Shamiko!
Our sales were through the roof!
Wow, really?
But I'm sorry...
Why?
We sold so many that there aren't
any wieners left for me to give you to take home!
Huh?
PLAIN
YOGURT
I'll give you these instead, okay?
PLAIN
YOGURT
Curse you, Momo!
Curses!
Wh-what's wrong?
Don't think this means you've won!
Don't give up, Shamiko! That yogurt is also yummy,
but in a completely different sense!
Curse you, Momo!
I curse you!
Momo Chiyoda, eh?
COLA
FRUITTY MILK
PLAIN YOGURT
Don't think this means you've won!
But tell Shamiko that I'm sorry!
COLA
FRUITTY MILK
PLAIN YOGURT
Well, she doesn't seem like such a bad rival.
Oh! They're covering the Beppu Hot Springs today!
I'm jealous! I'd love to visit the Hells of Beppu!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Preview
Hi, I'm Ryoko Yoshida.
In the next episode, I receive an amazing item
from my big sister Yuko's best friend, Momo.
Shamiko, she called me your "best friend."
Please just go along with it for now!
Shamiko's got more than one best friend!
Don't forget about me, Anri!
A Towl Full of Traps?! The Demon on the Brink Awakens a New Ability
I'm Sion Ogura.
I've always wanted to have a close
and personal chat with Shamiko!