The demon power of my ancestors
was awakened within me
and I challenged our mortal enemy,
a Magical Girl, to a round of fierce combat.
One day has passed since our grand duel ended!
G'morning!
Too bad about your utter defeat yesterday, huh?
That's not what happened at all.
We were locked in combat...
Huh? That's not how I remember it.
If you think about it like a soccer match,
SHAMIKO'S PERSPECTIVE
you got absolutely wrecked 7 points to 1!
IMAGINATION
Nooooo!
Are you really saying that I scored a point?
I don't have to be the one to lie to myself?
Yeah! You're my friend, so I put in one point just for you.
That's great, Yuko!
Yes... I'm really glad to have Anri as a friend!
This is the tale of a girl
who received demonic powers overnight,
and must rise up to defeat a Magical Girl
in order to save her family from the grips of poverty.
Or something to that effect.
The Demon Girl Next Door
Just How Sporty Are You?!
Everything is Fluctuating
Classic
Mild
TEA
It's true that I was crushed yesterday
because I went in totally unprepared and untrained.
But at least now I know it's impossible
for a level 1 Demon Girl to fight a level 99 Magical Girl!
For now, I'll just have to train myself until
I'm strong enough to beat that Pink Magical Girl.
Or search for another one that might be weaker!
Just FYI, I'm relatively weak
compared to other Magical Girls.
Oh, is that so?
Tap
Huh...?
Wassup!
The Pink Magical Girl is back again!
I've been here for a while now...
Pink Magical Girl! Why are you here?!
You're in Class A aren't you?!
Sometimes girls who awaken to demon powers
get swallowed by the darkness
and become a monstrous problem,
so I came to check up on you.
DARKNESS
Sploosh!
What do you mean a "monstrous problem"...?
Wait, did you just say that you were "relatively weak"?
Yeah.
But I heard that you saved the world once...
That's because I had very strong allies.
So aside from the Pink Magical Girl, there are even
stronger ones just lurking around every corner.
Hey, you don't have to keep describing me like that.
You can just call me "Momo."
From the looks of it you don't seem like
you're going to get swallowed up by the darkness.
Such horror...
Right, Shamiko?
It's Shami- Shadow Mistress Yuko!
In other words, "Sha-mi-ko."
Curse you, Pink Magical Girl!
Just call me "Momo."
Before that weird nickname catches on in the
entire school, I'm going to drain all the blood from you!
Today, when class ends, I will defeat you
at the riverbank behind the school!
Just you wait, and keep that precious blood pumping!
I'm not really interested, to be honest...
I'm through with doing all the Magical Girl stuff.
Hmph! Is your fear getting
the better of you, Pink Magical Girl?
It's "Momo."
Are you planning to finish your training
before school ends today?
Can you really get that much stronger in just six hours?
How about sometime during the afternoon
this weekend instead?
All right. Afternoon this weekend.
Training Room
ENDURANCE MONTH
Build your brawn and become
a tough young woman.
Let your muscles do the talking for you.
Ugh... I should have planned better,
the deadline for my training just became this weekend.
How heavy do you want your dumbbells?
1 pound please!
I already got permission to use
the training room from our teacher!
Let's get down to business!
So, the Pink Magical Girl also uses that training room...
Here. I think you could train
just by using water bottles instead.
Right! With just 1-pound weights it doesn't make sense
to even bother with the training room!
Let's get down to business!
Battle with the Pink Magical Girl
Beat the Magical Girl!!
Training Menu
(Make sure to do everything!!)
Plank - 30 Seconds
Squats - 15 times
Take a 30 minute break
Lift Dumbbells - 5 times
Punch practice - 10 times
So, the day has finally arrived!
Well then, I'm off to murderize the Magical Girl.
Good luck out there, Sis.
Tama River
I guess your fear didn't get
the better of you today, Pink Magical Girl!
Call me "Momo."
Wait, huh?
TANNED
Have you always been that tan?
You said "weekend" but didn't specify
Saturday or Sunday, so I waited here yesterday, too.
In the hot summer sun?!
I'm so sorry, I should have specified.
No worries, it didn't even
cross my mind until Friday night.
But it would really help if I knew
how to get a hold of you in times like these.
Oh, um...
My number is 042...
New Contact
Shamirin
I told my mortal enemy my phone number.
Enough! I've been waiting a long time for this day!
I've spent long hours training
in my house just to defeat you!
I can see that.
It looks like you've lost a few pounds,
and the muscles in your chest are starting to fill out.
Wha... ah... really?
I think the muscles in your triceps
are looking especially nice. Truly wonderful.
I get the feeling you might ramble on
so let's cut this short!
Okay, here I come!
Don't you need to warm-up first?
No thanks!
That's not good!
You really should. Let's do warm-ups together!
Why do you seem so enthusiastic about all this?
BONK      BONK      BONK      BONK      BONK      BONK
At the very least, you should do some stretches.
Sigh...
You hurt yourself before.
You might even tear a ligament in your tail this time.
A ligament in my tail?!
RECORDS OF THE THREE KINGDOMS
Mikan
Just like Cao Cao when he conquered
Northern China after the fall of the Han Dynasty...
I'm sure that sis is engaged in a round of mortal combat
with that Magical Girl right now.
Don't raise your heel in back like that!
Right!
What the heck...?
Okay, you've finished the basics. Now, let's go for a run.
Why?!
Because you really should warm-up first.
Even an absolute beginner
can run 2 miles if they keep a solid pace.
2 miles?!
If you're not coming, then I'll go by myself.
W-wait! You're fleeing from our battle?!
Yep.
Ugh... coward!
For the first mile we'll keep a 12-minute pace,
and for the second mile we'll do 10. Got it?
Right...
What the heck...?
Why exactly am I running with my mortal enemy
along the river bank at sunset?
This sucks...
This sucks, this sucks.
There are people out here? Taking their dog for a walk...
This sucks...
I can see a bridge...
This sucks... this sucks... this sucks... this sucks... this su-
Good evening.
Good evening!
Evening.
It feels like everything is fluctuating!
Shamiko was experiencing her very first runner's high.
The current of the flowing river does not cease,
and yet the water is not the same water as before.
A good run always makes you feel alive.
It helps us forget all the bad things.
The foam that floats on stagnant pools
is also just another part of the impermanence of our-
Remind me, why are we running again?
I don't remember, but...
I've started to sense... my inner potential...
Okay, so how about we keep running
until we hit the ocean.
We're in the middle of the mountains right now, though?!
Rage!
Ah! I just remembered!
RAGE!
Our battle!
And I can't run that much anyway!
Shoot, you remembered.
Well, let's get it over with.
Just finished warming up
Totally burned out
Want to postpone it until after tomorrow?
Yes, please!
Here, take this.
Huh?
It's a sports drink that's been diluted down.
I added some glucose to it, too.
Why diluted?
Sports drinks on the market today are not actually
optimized for the necessary osmotic pressure
needed after completing a workout.
Instead, they're made stronger than necessary
and so by diluting them you can...
Waaah! Forget I asked! But thank you very much!
One thing led to the other and we ended up
running 3 miles. You did great, Shamiko.
Wow, we ran 3 whole miles!
That's the first time I've done that!
Hm? 3 miles...?
3 More Miles (4km)
To get Home
Well, I'm going to keep running for a while.
Wait... Momo!
Please lend me fare... for the train ride back...
Is $5.00 enough?
Air-conditioned Car
Ah, the AC feels great...
Sigh.
Don't think this...
...means you've...
...won...
Thank you for your patronage.
This train has reached the end of the line and...
Deep Inner
Tama Station
Where the heck am I?!
Don't give up, Shamiko! Start out by returning
the $5.00 that you borrowed!
I'm so lost!
YOSHIDA
I'm headed to school.
Have a good day, Ryo.
So tell me, Yuko.
How is progress coming on your mission
to subdue a Magical Girl?
Um, well I found a Magical Girl to defeat.
And I challenged her to combat!
And then?
Huh?
We ran along the river bank!
Hm? You ran...? Why?
I don't really understand why, either!
All of a sudden, I just found myself out on a jog!
Is that so?
You've always been a frail girl since birth,
not to mention stupid.
I figured that going down this path
would not be an easy thing for you, but....
...it seems I'm going to have to provide you
with some assistance.
I noticed you added and tried to cover up
that little insult... but thank you very much.
I'm going to provide you
with extra funds to defeat the Magical Girl.
Your allowance is going up!
Huh?!
Your allowance has always been $1.20 a month, but...
...guess what!
I'm giving you a big boost to $5.00 a month!
Whaaaat?! Is that really okay?
Are you sure that's not too much?!
5 DOLLARS
(500 YEN)
I thought the Light Clan's "$400 a Month" curse
was making us live paycheck-to-paycheck.
It's all right. I've managed to set some funds aside
in a secret savings account.
Mom...
Also, I'm going to quit buying
into those damn lotteries I never win!
But Mom! What about those stamps
you accumulated for buying mushrooms?!
Unless I win, it's just a waste of postage to send them in!
Ta-da! Take a look!
My allowance got raised
to help me beat the Magical Girl.
Check it out, it's freshly minted!
Wow! Congrats, Shamiko!
Now you can buy all the candy you want!
Is that your purse...?
Wow! Congrats, Shamiko!
Now you can buy all the candy you want!
I won't buy any candy!
I will use this to defeat that Magical Girl!
You're really not going to buy any candy?
I will not! I must bring an end to the Magical Girl!
How can I beat her with just $5.00...?
After I eat some candy, maybe I can use
the wrappers to subdue her! Or maybe...
I can Shark Tank my way into getting more funds...!
Shamiko, your willpower is as weak as your punch.
Oh, Momo! What good timing!
Huh?
I'm returning the bottle you lent me the other day!
Oh, thanks. You could have
taken your time though, I don't mind.
You might not, but I certainly do!
I'll never become a respectful Demon Girl if I'm
always borrowing from the likes of a Magical Girl!
That's admirable, Shamiko. Then...
I guess you could return that $5.00 I lent you
for the train, while you're at it.
I seem to have exactly the right amount,
for some reason....
Wait, just forget about it! Sorry, you can keep it.
D-don't insult me! Just take it and don't worry about me!
I don't really know what's going on,
but I can clearly see you crying, Shamiko.
This is just eye juice! They are not tears!
Hey, come on! Just take the money!
Momochiyo, there are some complicated reasons,
but this girl and her family are flat broke.
Look! It's just eye juice! Come on!
That's why she's got so much eye juice right now.
Then let's make it a payment plan
with 10 separate installments. 50 cents a month.
You can't just decide that without the approval
of the person in debt!
But then you can buy candy.
I'll take the payment plan, please!
Although, if we do this it means
you won't be able to fight me for a while.
What...?
Wouldn't you feel just terribad for beating up
the person who you were indebted to?
Not to mention, if you take me out of the picture now,
it's only going to cause you bigger problems.
If I were to die before you paid me back,
you would be haunted by
the lingering debt for the rest of your life.
I-is that really how it works?
Something seems wrong about that.
It's not wrong. If that happens,
you'll become a bankrupt demon for life.
"Bankrupt"...
Do you want to be bankrupt, Shamiko?
I don't want to be bankrupt!
Then do your best and pay me back.
Right!
Wait...
Grr. I feel like I was tricked.
Well, if you ask me the whole thing
was pretty straightforward.
Huh?!
You're really gullible, Shamiko.
But I think that's for the best, don't you?
With 10 whole months, you can train really hard and
become strong enough to give Momochiyo a real fight!
Y-you're right!
For now, I'll use my remaining $4.50
to find an idea to help me win!
You should use it to make a weapon.
Maybe a projectile one.
Great idea!
Hmm... a weapon.
A weapon that works on a Magical Girl...
I'll try using a trail of Smarties
to lure an aggressive dog to her!
Nice! You're still hung up on buying candy, huh?
Is this what a pirate's lost treasure looks like?!
Am I dreaming right now?!
If you want to find a weapon,
then this is the place to look!
But then...
...why is Momo coming with us?!
Because you're not thinking clearly, Shamiko.
I just know you're going to waste your precious funds
to make something super useless.
I'm not THAT stupid!
Then I'll go ahead and ask,
what are those chopsticks and rubber bands for?
There's nothing wrong with making a rubber band gun!
But I'll go put them back.
ONE
HIT
KILL
$35.00
(3,500 YEN)
All the weapons cost even more than I imagined...
UDON GARDEN
Shamiko, check out the food court!
Don't tempt me!
Their self-serve udon is really tasty.
Just stop!
Go, go! Go, go! Go, go!
I refuse to go to the food court!
I bet they have that needlessly
extravagant ice cream! And udon!
I just know it's all delicious food
that doesn't actually make you full!
I totally want to go!
UDON GARDEN
No, that's wrong! I meant I don't want to go!
I can't fight the urge! Anri! Ogura! Momo!
Somebody stop me!
If you want to brainstorm new ideas
then you need carbohydrates!
That makes sense!
Part of your budget should go into food
to assure you have enough energy, right?
That makes sense!
You can take the chikuwa tempura
and add it to your plate, like this.
That makes sense!
Guh... how did this happen?
What's "white meat" tempura?
Chicken, apparently.
Oh? Do you mind if I have a bite?
Is this just another one of the Magical Girl's schemes?!
Go for it.
To get me addicted to this fancy food court
and completely drain my financial resources?!
Then I'll give you one of my fish tempura.
I can't let her manipulate me like this!
Do you want some too, Shamiko? It's really yummy.
If you don't mind trading for my chikuwa tempura...
Wow, it's impressive that you drank all the soup.
It's too delicious to waste!
There were lots of tempura bits at the bottom!
But now I can't even afford to make a rubber band gun...
This udon and chikuwa tempura meal
left me with only $1.20 left to my name.
$1.20
( 120 Yen )
All drinks $1.20
(120 yen)
Shamiko, are you thirsty? You drank so much salty broth.
You won't trick me into buying anything else!
I'm really relieved, though.
Huh?
Your family doesn't seem to have a lot of money
and you always leave so quick after school.
I had a lot of fun watching you
chow down on that udon today!
Anri...
But I'm sorry we pushed you into doing it.
Thinking about it, Anri is always
really busy with her club activities.
Although I usually go straight home after school,
she's always chatted with me even before I grew horns.
Has she been going out of her way
to watch out for me this whole time?
I promise I'll start thinking more seriously
about how to solve your problems!
Huh...? You mean you haven't been...?
I'm surprised that Anri would do
so much just for little old me.
Shamiko?!
Hi-yah!
Okay.
And now...
I chug it down!
Cough, cough, cough... burp! Cough, cough!
To be perfectly honest... burp,
I also... really enjoyed myself, burp!
I'll even come back next month, burp,
if you really want me to, Anri. Burp!
Really? Thank you.
But don't push yourself too hard.
Shamiko has absolutely no money left for the month.
Absolutely No Money Left
But are you sure about this?
You have none of your allowance left now, right?
It's fine. I was feeling thirsty anyway.
In fact, I realized that I've been
making you worry about me this whole time.
Shamiko...
I'll work hard to become a great demon
who notices lots of other stuff too!
I think group outings like these are going
to become how I encourage myself to fight.
Hopefully!
Oh...
Huh?
There's a... free water dispenser?
Don't think this means you've won!
Huh, me?
Do your best, Shamiko! You can save a lot if you
don't spend on drinks and utilize free resources instead!
A dunce... A complete dunce!
How the hell did she end up in such a mess?!
And why does she have
such a careless look on her face?!
She's not taking this seriously at all!
She's just way too pathetic!
It seems I shall have to set her on the right path
personally, with my own touch of force.
Just you wait!
My little descendant!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Preview
Yuko, my adorable descendant.
Ah! Who're you?
I am your great ancestor! The founder of the Dark Clan!
Next time, I'm going to share with you
our many precious secrets!
My ancestor...?
Shamiko, let's go and practice using projectile weapons.
Preview
Your weapon was stolen!!
Oh crap, it's Momo again! I'm going home!
Preview
Nightmare or Forebear?! The Doorstop of Darkness Descends
You're not leaving until you shoot something.