Banda Terrace
An... interview?
Yuko
Yeah. It's my homework, I have to write a report
on my neighborhood and the people in it.
I wanted to start by interviewing
the older sister I'm so proud of!
Yuko's Sister - Ryoko
N-no way...
I'm just a helpless high schooler
who suddenly awakened to the powers of darkness.
I don't think there's anything about me
that you can be proud of, Ryo.
Don't worry about that.
I'm really good at exaggerating the stories I write about.
You're really the best little sister I could ask for, Ryo!
Yes,
yes
Yes, yes.
She is such a reliable daughter.
Yuko's Mother
Seiko
The Demon Girl Next Door
Taiyou mabushisugite
(Chikachika me o kosutta)
Omowazu tobidashita yo
(Dokidoki no hajimiari sa)
Yurayura yureru maegami hidarite de osaetara
Itsumo no keshiki ga kirameku yo
(Three, two, one)
Ima sugu tsutaetai futari no himitsu
Watashitachi nara dekiru yo
(Itsumo tonari ni ite)
Kitto
(Shijiteru kara)
Machikado de mitsuketa daiji na takaramono
Tatoe kimi ga tooku hanaretemo kanarazu oikakeru yo
Zutto kagayaiteru mirai wa koko ni aru
Otanoshimi wa kore kara
A Town Full of Traps??
The Demon on the Brink Awakens a New Ability
I still have a lot to learn as a Demon Girl!
I have to try my hardest to become someone
that Ryo can truly be proud of!
CLENCH
Tremble, Magical Girl...
for I'm finally about to put an end to you!
Hey, Shamiko. Good afternoon.
Good afternoon.
I'm going to repay my debt to you all at once
with this $20 I earned from my job!
Now there is zero debt between the forces of light and
dark! And we can battle without holding anything back!
That's right, you were selling wieners the other day.
I actually have some of the ones
I bought with me right now.
Are all of those supposed to be your lunch?!
Did you want to have some, Shamiko?
I'd love to, but I will refrain!
Shake
Enough! Take the money! And let's battle!
Uh, you know I'd really hate
to just take all of your hard-earned money.
Why don't you use some of it for yourself, instead?
SHAMIKO'S FIRST PAYDAY
CONGRATULATORY AWARD
Don't you want to make a trophy or something
to commemorate the occasion?
You've earned a trophy!
"It's raining octopuses" (Bronze)
Trophy...
I can't spend money on something
so extravagant that has no edible parts!
Then would you settle for a trophy made entirely of ham?
Gulp.
There would be nothing left if I eat it!
That's just barely unacceptable!
You won't be able to trick me with any food this time!
Because I made sure to fill my stomach
before I came to challenge you!
Burp.
You're prepared for everything, huh?
I'll pay off my debt early and then take the next step
on the Demon path by undoing the seal!
I see...
Ah! I see you're conflicted about all this, Momo!
I'm not conflicted at all.
You gave it away by how you're acting!
I didn't give anything away.
This is my fist victory!
I did it! I really did it!
THAT'S COLD!
I-I'm... fweezing...
What's happening, what is this?
It's my frozen water bottle... it's cold, huh?
Excuse me, I got a little carried away. I apologize!
Anyway, even if I pay you back,
I'll still be left with some change.
So I'm going to buy my little sister
something special after school today.
"Little sister"?
What's wrong?
I can't go along with this.
I reject your request to settle the debt now.
Let's continue with the 50-cent payment plan.
Use whatever is left over each month
on yourself and your family.
I won't accept anything else.
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?!
If you agree right now, I'll throw in
a free slice of bread. What do you say?
Too thin! I already told you,
you won't win me over with food today!
Plop. Plop.
Anyway, I've been wondering...
That lunch of yours looks so hastily prepared,
with the uncooked wieners and untoasted bread.
Is your family just really busy or something?
I make my own lunch.
Oh, do you live all by yourself?
I don't have any family...
Um...
I've said too much, just forget it.
I'll take your thin bread!
Just this once, I'll go along with whatever you say!
Huh?
But this won't work on me ever again
unless you bring thicker slices of bread!
Tama Sakura Shopping District
So...
Why are you following me to the spot
where I'm meeting with my sister?
Am I not allowed to come with you?
I thought you agreed to go along with whatever I said?
Just how underhanded can you get?!
Sis!
Oh crap, here she comes!
Just don't reveal your true identity!
I told her that the Magical Girl and I
are always engaged in fierce combat!
So, please!
You heaped it on extra thick, huh?
Not extra thick, just regular thick!
You beat me here, Sis?
Ryoko! You didn't go home first to drop off your bags?
I was doing my homework at the library.
Of course, you've always had
a good head on your shoulders!
Who is this?
This is...
My best friend, Momo!
Don't look so surprised about it!
Follow along!
O-okay...
Nice to meet you, I'm Momo Chiyoda.
I'm Ryoko, nice to meet you.
I called you here today...
...to buy you a present
with the money I earned from my job!
Huh? You shouldn't... really...
Mom told me that the battle you're waging right now
is of the utmost importance.
That's why I'm okay without getting anything.
I want you to buy something useful for yourself.
You shouldn't hold back like that!
Choose anything you like!
Then...
Some bandages and this "Household Medicine" book.
HOUSEHOLD MEDICINE
I'm not going to get hurt, don't worry!
You don't have to become a combat medic just for me!
Then...
SIX SECRET
TEACHINGS
The Art of War...
"New Edition of the Six Secret Teachings:
Learn the art of war to become a superb military leader."
You realize that I don't actually control an army, right?!
Let's look around for a bit
and give you a chance to think it over.
Okay...
Hamburg
Steak
Come on Momo, you, too!
Ryoko, just think about what you want to do
or find something you want to own.
Right...
Hey, Sis.
I...
SUPER EXPANDING
SEAWEED
I want to make the economic choice and buy seaweed.
We'll get more for our money that way.
Don't let yourself be swayed
by our family's nutritional needs!
Shamiko.
Wave
What about... that?
WE BUY
AND SELL
CAMERAS
Ever since we got here, Ryo's been looking at that
out of the corner of her eye.
USB Toy Camera
Hot item
A mini-camera?
2,138 yen
($21.38)
"Toy camera"?
Ryo, is this what you want?
No... I was just looking!
I just thought it was really cute because of how tiny it is!
Because at the library I'm always looking
at camera magazines and stuff!
My eye was just drawn to it, that's all!
You're seriously jonesing for it!
2,138 yen
($21.38)
Hot item
USB Toy Camera
But... it's expensive.
I can do this!
This is like chump change to me!
Let's buy it!
Then you can use it to take some glamorous shots
of your heroic sister!
Sis... Thank you...
Why are you crying?!
Sniffle
Sniffle, sniffle... Sniffle, sniffle...
Because lately it's easy to tell whenever
you push yourself, since your tail goes really limp.
Huh? Is that true?
You never noticed it, huh?
Sniffle, sniffle...
WORRIED
Worried.
UNMOTIVATED
Unmotivated.
NERVOUS
Nervous.
EXCITED
Excited.
And right now, your tail is...
"Just how much has this person been observing me?
It's freaking me out!" Or something like that?
How can you read me like a book?!
Um, Momo...
Huh?
I know that earlier at school I told you
it's best if I paid off my debt ASAP.
But today, when I saw Ryoko's face like that...
I'm glad I was able to do something for her instead.
Yeah.
I will definitely take my time and pay you back in full.
Okay.
Since otherwise...
...I'll never be able to fight you!
You just wait and keep your blood sugar level
as high as it can get!
Uh, sure.
Don't you have a better reply than that?!
Um...
Huh?
The first picture I take should be special,
I want it to be of you two together.
Wha-?!
No, no, that won't be-
Aren't you best friends?
Well, we really have to consider
Momo's feelings in all this....
I don't mind at all.
Hold on, Momo!
Let's go find a stool or something
Shamiko can step on to make her taller.
There was one in front of the bookstore earlier.
That works! Let's head there.
So, is "Shamiko" my sister's nickname?
You two don't need to put any more thought
into my height, thank you very much!
A short time later...
Okay, say cheese.
I wonder how you develop the pictures on this...
It must have film of some kind.
Let me see.
This camera should be able
to print pictures on a computer via USB.
"US"...?
Wh-wha-what? Wh-wha-what...?
This isn't good... I don't even have a passport...
If I could at least swim and knew English then...
You're thinking about the "USA."
I have a printer at home, so if you'll
lend me your camera then I'll print the picture out.
Thank you very much!
Are you good with computers, Ms. Momo?
Like with software and such.
If it's a free version, I should have it yeah.
"Free"...?
Th-Then, maybe you can do
some color corrections on the picture too?
Oh, you're interested in retouching.
If it's just a few simple things sure, but if you want
to do it right then a pen tablet is necessary.
What's a "pen tablet"?
"Retouch"...? "Pen tablet"...?
Dizzy, dizzy.
Don't think this means you've won!
But please teach her more later!
Don't give up, Shamiko!
Make use of the school's computer lab
and become a great demon capable of IT support!
Shamiko! Are you heading home now?
Here, take this with you.
It weighs a ton! What the heck is this?
It's my old laptop. I was thinking I'd let you borrow it.
Why?!
Because it looks like you could use some extra weight.
I'm not asking why you're making me hold it!
Actually, where's that Ancestue of yours?
I forgot it at home today.
But I thought it was an important item to you?
That's right. I definitely won't forget to bring it tomorrow.
You know, I can't bring this laptop home with me!
I've already borrowed more than enough from you!
But I want Ryo to be able to use it.
It's for Ryoko?
I saw the picture Ryo took and I think
she has a good sense for photography.
It would be best for her future if she learned
how to operate a computer like this.
Thank you very much.
Sure, I already installed some graphic software
and it also has the most recent OS that's available.
"OH... ES...?"
Oh yes!
Oh yes! Oh yes! You can do it! You can do it!
I guess for these older laptops you need
a special voice command to activate them, huh?
Oh yes!
Should we chant along with it,
like when you root for the home team?
Oh yes!
Oh yes! Oh ye-!
You're thinking of "Oh yes."
Oh yes!
I'm going to be straight with you, Shamiko.
This laptop is a delicate piece of equipment.
That means if you throw balls at it,
dump water on it, or drop it, then it will break easily.
You have to be careful with it.
Gulp.
Speaking of which,
how much does this laptop cost anyway?
That's a secret.
Don't drop it, okay?
No matter what, don't drop it.
Is that clear? I'm being serious.
You're enjoying this, I just know it!
CHALLENGE 1
SLIP PAST THE SCHOOL CLUBROOM BUILDING
Right now, I am a....
...delivery demon.
My duty is to bring this delicate device
back to my home safely with no problems.
Do your best, Sis!
For my darling little sister waiting at home,
I have to do my best!
Gulp.
The hallway feels much wider and longer
than it normally does...
Everyone... looks like an enemy!
Wassup?
WHAT THE FUWAH?!
A-Anri, what are you doing?!
I was trying to get your attention.
Am I not allowed to play a little prank on my good friend?
Just for today please hold off on the pranks!
What the heck do you think
you're playing with over there?!
Balls, duh! We have a match
against one of the top-seeded schools soon!
I'm gonna put my all into it!
O-oh God, please stop. No more balls.
It will... it will break...
Are you afraid of balls?
They're just like bullets!
You think? Is my handling
of the racket really that impressive?
That makes me so happy to hear!
Just wait, I've got a little trick that will smash a ball
right through anything with a "whoosh"!
What are you, a hired assassin?!
THE SECOND ASSASSIN
SION OGURA ON CLEANING DUTY
Sigh.
S-somehow, I managed to survive that mess.
Oh, Shamiko!
Oh, you're Ms. Ogura. One of Anri's friends from Class C!
OH GOD, NOT A BUCKET!
I've always wanted to have a close
and personal chat with you, Shamiko!
I don't think that needs to be right now!
Actually, I'm trying to create a research group
that focuses on magic and demons.
I believe that what we discover
will definitely be of some use to you, Shamiko!
You'd make a great subject... I mean,
this would be a great chance for us to become friends!
So, if you ever are having trouble with anything,
then please let me know! Literally anything!
Come chat with me!
I get it already, just leave that water on the ground!
Of course.
Clunk
Ah, as proof of our new friendship...
Here, take this.
Gulp.
Wh-what is this, exactly?
It's kind of tasty.
It's an original elixir I made
that's designed to boost magic power.
I wanted to let you test... I mean I wanted to give it to you
as a present, Shamiko. I've always kept it handy.
"Always"?
What is it made of?
Habu, Ge Jie, Yartsa Gunbu, and some other stuff.
If you want to know more,
you should do an image search of those later.
Okay.
It seems like you enjoyed it,
so I'll make some more, okay?
LAST BATTLE?
I finally made it out of the school.
Just a little further, Sis!
Right! Just watch, Big Sis will do her best!
For now, I need to remain vigilant and watch out
for cars making a left turn on my way...
Ah!
That dog!
The whole reason I became indebted to Momo
in the first place was all because...
...of that barking dog!
Gulp.
This is today's...
...last battle!
Maybe I should just wait until the dog falls asleep?
No... my arms will get sore
and I'll drop the laptop before then.
Should I fight it?
No, I'd feel terrible!
And actually, aren't dogs super strong?
I mean, they have FOUR legs!
But the reality is I can't get home without crossing here.
This is how the dog appears to Yuko
What a pickle...
I'm gonna lose for sure!
The dog will bark at me, I'll fall,
smash the computer to bits,
and then it'll snowball even worse
by getting this borrowed uniform all dirty!
Oh, my poor little descendant...
Can you hear me?
Huh?
It's Lilith, your friendly neighborhood ancestor.
I'm talking to you directly through your mind right now.
Huh?
You're in quite the pinch, I see.
However, for some reason your signal
is exceptionally strong today!
The magic inside of you is simply overflowing!
Now is the perfect chance!
Call upon it! Your inner appearance!
Sha...
Shami...
Shadow Mistress Yuko! Crisis Management Foooooorm!
Huh? My body just reacted on its own...
Huh?! What is this outfit...?
No, seriously, what the heck is this thing?
You said it yourself, it's your "Crisis Management Form."
It's the result of my concept of a strong appearance
being linked directly to your consciousness.
Are you telling me that this is my battle form?
I want a retake!
I can't walk around town
in a skimpy and embarrassing outfit like this!
In fact, my stomach already feels like it's freezing!
Seriously?
Aren't you being just a little too self-conscious?
I don't think it's all that embarrassing.
A-are you sure?
Let's go for a walk.
Oh, hello th-
H-hello there...
Hello...
Uhh...
I knew it, this outfit makes people do a double-take.
Ah, I see...
Well, times have certainly changed
since the Mesopotamia era.
Sorry about that, I'll fix it.
DON'T FORGET
THE GOAL STILL LIES AHEAD
YOSHIDA
I'm glad I was able to return
to my normal form right away.
Today sure was a challenge.
I'm home!
Stinky, stinky!
Stinky, stinky! Stinky, stinky!
Ms. Ancestor?
Oh crap, my ancestor fell into the garbage!
Oh my gosh, are you all right?
I feel like my head is spinning...
I'm so sorry.
It's fine, you should check
and make sure everything else is okay.
That's right! The laptop!
Sis! I heard a loud crash!
Oh nooooooo!
Did you get hurt?
Huh?
That... that bag...
Momo's laptop is inside there.
She said she was lending it to you.
Huh? Ms. Momo's laptop?
This is bad. I think I stepped on it!
Even before that, I accidentally
let it drop with a solid "thud."
Are you all right, Yuko?
Come on, wrap a cold towel
around where you hurt yoursel-
Oh crap!
Get a cloth! Get a cloth!
Gotta hurry! Gotta hurry!
What a mess! What a mess!
I let my guard down. I forget that even after I get home,
there are still many dangers to avoid.
SQUISH
Wah! It feels soft and weird!
What's up with this laptop?!
It's all squishy on the outside!
Stinky, stinky!
Gah! My ancestor went into the garbage again!
AND FINALLY
It turned on!
A letter?
Dear Shamiko,
I thought there was a good chance
that you would fall on your way home.
Dear Shamiko,
There was a good chance that you would fall on your way home.
That's why I added a waterproof finish
and put it in a bag that can handle strong shocks.
So, it's probably not broken.
Even if it is, I can fix it myself. Don't worry about it.
So, it's probably not broken. Even if it is, I can fix it myself.
Don't worry about it.
From: Momo
From Momo.
P.S. Don't cry! Stay strong!
Grr... Don't think this means you've won!
Oh yes, Shamiko! Even now, Lilith is diligently working
to create your other new transformations!
Now that I have a camera,
it's time for take two of your interview!
I'm Yuko Yoshida, 15 years old.
Please tell me your most important goal right now.
My most important goal right now is to save some money
to buy a doughnut shaped pillow!
Because my horns really start to hurt when I sleep!
Ryo really is the world's greatest sister.
Are you sure you two are okay with that?
"Incredible performance"...
You're doing that to make fun of me, I can tell!
I won't let you read it, Momo!
But I have the data at home anyway...
D-don't think this means you've won!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Sassouto shobu shite
Yatchau kedo makechatte
Fugainai nai ne
Shoushin tenshin
Kibun wa sunsun demo
Shippo de henji shiyou
Chounai de waiwai shite
Inu made bow-wow de
Tende meimei de
Shunka shuutou
Shippai shita tte waraitobasou
Ano koro to onaji you ni kokoro tsumuide
Kono machi de deaeta kiseki
Kanaete yo
Zenkai da wa tire shou ippai
Warning mada kikikanri enjoy
Toridori saita iro canvas kakenuke
Sunset da wa, kangaete bakari ja
Sou, mae!
Hora, donna iro datte yume kasanete
Motto asobou ne
Preview
Today I was able to accomplish something befitting
of an older sister for Ryo,
and on top of it all, I actually transformed, what a shock!
Shamiko? Did something happen?
I don't really understand it myself,
so let's just move on to the preview.
In the next episode, I'm going to invade
Courage to Face the Future!! The Heavy Roller Won't Stop
Momo's dreams and Momo's house, among other things.
Now is the time!
That sounds suspicious...