Yuko Yoshida (15 years old)
One day, a 15-year-old girl named Yuko suddenly awoke
as a Demon Girl by sprouting a tail and horns.
A RECAP OF THE EVENTS
UNTIL NOW
In fact, her family are descendants of the Dark Clan
that has existed since ancient times.
Thou hast inherited the blood of the dark ones.
Title: Shadow Mistress Yuko
I dub thee Shadow Mistress Yuko!
Thou must vanquish a Magical Girl who lives in this town,
and restore our clan to its former glory!
Charged with the duty of undoing the seal upon her
family by defeating a Magical Girl, she begins her quest.
In the middle of her adventure, Shadow Mistress Yuko
was overwhelmed by fierce hunger and exhaustion.
It was then that a helping hand was offered to her.
Magical Girl
Momo Chiyoda
You looked like you were hungry.
However, that hand belong to none
other than her mortal enemy: a Magical Girl!
DON'T THINK THIS MEANS YOU'VE WON!!
A Reliable Informant
Anri
If you need a job, just say the word!
Sis! Thank you!
A Precious Sister
Waiting in the Homeland - Ryoko
The Eternal Queen of Darkness
Shamiko's Mighty Ancestor
Empress Lilith
Are you shaking in your boots, Magical Girl?
This is the true extent of my power!
Just a Dog Passing By
Daring tactics.
You can't fool me, you assassin!
Deadly struggles.
Let's obliterate them into nothing.
And then just forget about everything!
Or some scenes kind of like that.
Ask me anything you wish!
Fancy action scenes complete with
slow motion and dramatic camera work
that spins around while it happens.
Don't give up, Shamiko!
Your glorious battle has only just begun!
This whole recap is totally wrong!
Well, I wanted to record all of your feats
thus far into my memory.
Did you not enjoy it?
It was a complete misrepresentation!
For starters, I have no idea
where that even took place in!
And I definitely never wore a weird cape like that!
Tama City is just an ordinary residential development!
If a giant mushroom like this grew in the middle
of the city it would be a huge problem!
And there were a whole bunch of parts in the second half
that I don't even remember happening!
Yeah, but didn't it look super cool?
It was cool, but...
GOLD
...the color of the Ancestue
was all wrong for some reason!
Well, the most important thing
definitely needs some bling.
That is so out of date!
It's okay, Shamiko.
This is all just a dream that I made.
Just a dream... just a dream...
Just a dream...
It WAS a dream!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Taiyou mabushisugite
(Chikachika me o kosutta)
Omowazu tobidashita yo
(Dokidoki no hajimiari sa)
Yurayura yureru maegami hidarite de osaetara
Itsumo no keshiki ga kirameku yo
(Three, two, one)
Ima sugu tsutaetai futari no himitsu
Watashitachi nara dekiru yo
(Itsumo tonari ni ite)
Kitto
(Shijiteru kara)
Machikado de mitsuketa daiji na takaramono
Tatoe kimi ga tooku hanaretemo kanarazu oikakeru yo
Zutto kagayaiteru mirai wa koko ni aru
Otanoshimi wa kore kara
The Pink Method!!
The Wheel of Fate is a Round Tire!!
Hey, Shamiko. It was a dream,
but it wasn't just any old dream.
I worked all night to make that wonderful dream
and you just outright rejected it!
I appreciate the thought.
But you took it way too far!
At least I know that my Ancestor
talking to me isn't a dream.
Good morning, Yuko.
Mornin' Sis!
I'm headed to school!
I'm Yuko Yoshida, 15 years old.
I recently became a novice Demon Girl
and set out on a new journey in life.
The record of my struggles you saw that my Ancestor
made was totally blown out of proportion, but...
"Then what was it really like?"
"How much of it was actually true?"
It's hard to answer those so please don't ask.
I WILL say that I'm doing my best in my own unique way.
I think the day I finally make Momo give up
and say "Uncle!" is really close at hand!
Heh
Heh. Heh. Heh.
G'morning.
Magical Girl! Why are you here?!
Are you over your cold already?
Not yet, I just left home to do some grocery shopping.
Extra Whole Milk
CHICKEN TENDER
SANDWICH
Your diet seems way too simple.
I think you should really add-in some vegetables.
I'm not really interested in making more complex meals.
Are you worried about me?
N-not at all!
I'm just concerned I won't be able
to steal as much magic from you!
Oh, I have an idea! I've been learning
how to cook from my mom lately.
I'll use you as my guinea pig.
Heh, heh, heh.
Already Gone
Wait, damn you! Are you running away?!
No.
I'm supposed to be taking a sick day from school
so I shouldn't loiter outside.
But speaking of magic...
Hm? What's up?
Based on how much I lost, there should be other
changes aside from Ms. Lilith getting more annoying.
Huh?
Hello, you've reached the Yoshida residence.
Excuse me, I'm an officer from the Tama City Police.
May I speak with Ms. Seiko Yoshida?
Yes, that's me.
I'm home!
Did something happen, mom?
It all came back.
My purse that fell into the gutter
and the $1,080 that was inside of it!
$1,000?!
Sorry, my entire concept of the universe
was just turned upside down for second.
I think this is proof that the "$400 a Month" curse
has finally been lifted.
Huh?
Coming in contact with a Magical Girl,
one of the priests of the Light Clan...
Yuko, you have made a major accomplishment!
Tonight, we shall perform the "ritual"
long passed down in our family!
ZAP
Mom, you don't mean we're going to do THAT?
I do!
The Yoshida family motto!
"Whenever fortune smiles upon us, that means
it is definitely our fate to sit around the hot plate!"
The power just went out for a second, that was scary...
So without further ado, I went ahead
and purchased groceries for the foreseeable future.
Let's separate and sort them out.
Right!
Cabbage, bonito flakes, flour...
These are ingredients for the okonomiyaki
we're having tonight!
There's wieners and yakisoba noodles, too!
The rest of it is stock for other meals.
Sliced pork, green onions, yellow onions,
bean sprouts, eggs, bean sprouts, carrots, bean sprouts,
pudding, bean sprouts, chicken, chicken, chicken,
bean sprouts, cucumbers and more bean sprouts.
Bean Sprouts
I'm sorry. I just couldn't bring myself
to actually buy the things that are truly luxurious.
Although Yuko did remove part of the seal
placed on our family, we still need to take it easy for now.
Because the truth is that there are still various powers
and fortunes of ours that are being held back.
If we give in to our urges now, we'll only be sad
when fate adjusts to make us pay for it all later.
Gulp.
Fate adjusts to make us pay...
Snap
Oh no, not our one and only pancake turner!
Can we still make the okonomiyaki?!
I'll make do with a wooden spatula!
Hey Seiko.
Huh?
Do you mind if I butt in?
My husband has told me quite a lot about you,
but this is the first time we've spoken directly.
N-nice to meet you! I'm Yuko's little sister, Ryoko!
Yes, I know of you both.
Although not in much detail.
I'm shocked we can hear your voice so clearly now.
Indeed! This means an end to all those days
I suffered as a doorstop and meat pounder!
Monthly Prattle Magazine
Survival Wits Magazine
Special:
Meals Made Just From Weeds
Although, because you would always
leave me lying around like some kind of dumbbell
I was able to learn quite a lot about the modern era.
My apologies.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh...
Since I've now made a mini-revival, I think it's about time
I flex my muscle as the family patriarch.
There's a lot I want to ask you, for starters-
Super Buzz - Mikan Flavor
Oh, dear Ancestor?
We're about to have a little celebration right now
so could you hold that off until later?
What is this?
Just a can of fizzy goodness.
Super Buzz - Mikan Flavor
I've never seen this before,
is it another sweet carbonated beverage?
I have to admit it's pretty tasty, but...
Hiccup!
Ancestor!
Wha... What the heck is happening?!
The world is spinning like a top! Was that poison?!
But it's really addictive...
It's a canned highball.
Ancestor, what did you want to talk to us about?
Hm? Hiccup...
Oh, Ancestor?
SHINSHUU BRAND
DEMON EXTERMINATOR
Squeak!
I prepared you a nice sake bath.
It's the most luxurious thing you can imagine!
Squeak! Squeak! Squeak!
Faint...
ANCESTOR!
It's party time right now, so please refrain from
bringing up any complicated topics of discussion.
I hope we'll be able to get along well as housemates.
Okay, great grandmother-in-law?
Ah... paradise lost.
I think I'm starting to see
the new balance of power in our family.
Mom!
Let me help, I want to learn how to cook.
Okay, then I'll share with you what I know
about making it as yummy as can be.
When you're frying up pork, you should let it
get back to room temperature just beforehand.
You should wait to season it with salt and pepper
until right before you put it on the heat.
Shitake mushrooms shouldn't be washed,
but rather wiped down with a wet cloth.
Wow! You sure keep a lot of different things in mind
when you're cooking, mom!
Well, my biggest goal is for you and Ryo
to grow up nice and healthy
so all of this is just the natural result
of working towards that.
Hm?
Could it be? Did you meet someone
that you want to cook for?!
There's a Magical Girl in the neighborhood
who has a problem with maintaining good nutrition.
Wait, a Magical Girl?!
Yeah, I'm worried she'll collapse from malnutrition
long before I have the chance to beat her!
I hope they're ready soon, I can't wait!
Oh, that's right.
There's been a lot going on lately and I ended up
agreeing to help a Magical Girl out for a while.
Is this the same girl that you ran along
the riverbank with the other day?
That's right! I'll share more details with you later.
I always figured this might be the path you'd take, Yuko.
Instead of just beating the Magical Girl,
you'd befriend her in order to release the seal.
Huh? I wouldn't say I've befriended her.
It's more like there was so much pressure,
I had no choice but to agree to help her.
It was rough.
"Rough"?
Ah, I think the food might be ready now!
It looks so yummy! And it smells great, too.
Okay, then let's split it up.
Here.
Wow! Thanks so much!
And for you.
Thanks.
It's delicious! Super yummy!
I'm so glad my hard work paid off!
From now on, I think I can overcome any mountains that
get in my way by just remembering this okonomiyaki!
I'm so glad to hear you're enjoying it.
It's got mayonnaise, sauce, and bonito flakes on top!
Not to mention it doesn't have a tofu base,
so I can really taste the wheat flour!
Though I won't deny I like tofu, too.
That's not exactly a shining endorsement.
I promise I'll try a little harder
to improve your palette from now on!
I'll serve you up some more, Ryo.
Thanks.
No thanks necessary!
This is all to celebrate your big sister's accomplishment,
so feel free to stuff yourself full!
Ow, hot!
Um, Sis? I want to help you out, too.
Huh?
B-but, Ryo you're still too young.
And I made Momo conceal her identity from you before.
Please? I've been reading a lot of books lately
and I think I could be of some use!
My dream is to become your trusted advisor!
I want to watch from your fortress as you charge
into battle atop a horse, leading an army behind you!
I told you before, I don't actually
control an army and don't have plans to!
It's never going to be like this!
Ancestor, are you okay?
I'll give you some juice and okonomiyaki.
Ugh... is that you, Ryoko?
Pant. Pant...
I appreciate you being so kind
to a little ol' doorstop like me.
When my full powers have returned, I promise you
control over North America after I conquer the world!
Huh? Sorry, I think that I'd prefer my sister
to be the one who holds control over all domains.
Will you settle for just being the conqueror in name only?
Huh?! That's driving a hard bargain, don't you think?
Actually, for someone so modest,
you really don't mince words!
Wobble
Shamiko, would you mind giving me some ice water?
Sure thing.
Huh?
Mom! Something's wrong with the refrigerator!
It doesn't feel cool!
Huh?!
Neither the fridge nor the freezer
sound like they're working.
It is quite old. I wonder if it finally broke down?
That power outage earlier could be part of it.
Is this... fate adjusting to make us pay?
Scrub
It's fine!
You know, I've really been wanting
one of those fancy, new fridges.
I'm actually HAPPY that our old one broke on us!
Mom, have you totally lost it?!
When that lightning came down earlier,
I heard something go ZAP.
ZAP
That must have been the refrigerator's dying breath.
It'll take a week for a new fridge to be delivered. That's a
problem because right now we're at the start of summer.
We have to figure out how to deal
with all the food I bought to stock up.
We cannot let any of it go to waste!
I'm going to start cooking all of it right now
and we'll eat it all by tomorrow! Let's speed eat!
Huh?!
I'm already full to the point that I wasn't
going to eat breakfast tomorrow!
By the way, it took all of our money to buy a new fridge
so make sure you stuff yourselves before we fast!
That's not how humans work, you know!
Time to get cooking!
What's up? Why did you come in the rain?
To do reconnaissance on my enemy.
How are you feeling?
I still have a fever, but I think
I should be back at school by next week.
What's that?
I came to invade your big, fancy refrigerator
and lay claim to some of it with our Demon delicacies.
Does that mean you're sharing your food?
That's another way you could put it!
The bag is filled with a bunch of smaller side dishes.
And the big box has pork, bean sprout and egg stew.
There's also some chicken hamburg steak in it, too.
Wow.
I helped to make some of it myself.
If you put them all in the fridge,
they should last for the next two days.
Thank you.
I normally don't get to eat stuff like this,
so I'm really happy.
Gah...
D-don't get the wrong idea, Magical Girl!
All of this nourishing food is just meant to help you
cultivate more blood so I can steal it later!
And, um...
I can't think of any other reasons!
Take care of yourself!
Be careful with all the rain!
Don't give up, Shamiko!
Pick up the fight tomorrow and work to put
more delicious food on your dining table!
Shamiko.
Momo, you must be over your cold now.
Yeah. Thanks to you.
Come with me.
Soring through with pink logic
Bean sprouts and pork sure are yummy, huh?
I also recommend cabbage and pork together.
Shamiko, raise your arms up.
Huh? What for?
Wha-?
Okay, let's start your training!
Training?! Huh?! What is all this?!
This is a tire designed for large vehicles
that carry heavy things like in mines and...
I'm not asking you to explain what type of tire it is!
It won't come off!
What do you mean by "training"?
I explained it to you before, remember?
I want you to help me keep the city safe.
Because you took some of my blood,
the strength of my magic has fallen drastically.
Right...
That's why I need you to become stronger.
I understand that.
Which is exactly why I made sure to get a really big tire!
THAT'S WHERE YOU START TO LOSE ME!
Hm... how can I best explain it to you?
Do you understand why I'm strong enough
to stop a dump trunk with only one hand?
Because you have the spirit
and muscle necessary to do so.
That's not it.
The moment that Magical Girls
make a contract with the Light Clan,
their bodies get pretty much entirely reformatted
and they become an ether
of incredibly high-density magic.
Thus, the reason I can do stuff like this isn't because
of my muscle, but because of the magic within me.
But I thought that you lost a bunch of your magic power?
Right now, I'm basically making up for that
with my spirit and muscle.
So it's because of your muscles, like I thought.
Even if you're not capable of everything that I am,
you still have your own Demon powers.
You should be able to pull off some similar feats.
No...
That's why my goal is to boost your magic.
Magic is part of your body,
your spirit, your life experiences.
There are a lot of ways to train to increase it.
And we're going to start with the easiest,
which is building muscle.
And while you're building muscle,
you can build some muscle.
And top it off with building muscle.
Th-this is scary. I can't get away because of the tire!
Also, I forgot to mention this,
but we'll also work to build muscle.
Forget is the exact opposite of what you did!
If you ask me, I think you just
love training to build muscle!
That's not right. I just can't help it.
Which means you like it!
From where I stand you seem as strong as ever,
did you really get weaker?
Yep.
Also, I can't untie this.
My maximum supply of magic power dropped, which
means I can't use any of my most powerful techniques.
You have a repertoire of powerful techniques?!
I want to hear all about them!
Hey, hey! Does this include that
"Fresh Peach Heart Shower" thing you mentioned?!
Why did you commit little details like that to memory?
That's just a mid-level technique.
Which means you can still use it even now, right?!
I want to see it! Get on top of the tire!
Get up there and use that technique!
Do it! Go up there and show me!
I don't want you to see, it's embarrassing.
WHAAAAT?!
Huh? What are you two doing over there?
Oh, it's Anri.
Both Shami-cen's horn and heart seem like they might break in two
Is "Shamicen" supposed to refer to me?
Wow, so you're going to be working together then.
We're not working together.
We just declared a cease-fire.
Indeed.
You must be really happy
that you're able to talk freely now, Shamicen.
But you're looking kind of pale in the face. Are you okay?
Yes... I'm recovering from a hangover
for reasons I won't go into.
Is "Shamicen" a nickname for her?
It's adorable.
"Shamiko's ascendant" put those together
and you get Shami-cen!
Would it be all right if I called you by that name, too?
I beg you... can you at least be the one
who shows me some actual respect?
I see how it is.
You're training muscle so that
you can build up your magic power.
But listen, Momochiyo.
As a rule of thumb, humans don't pull tires
that are designed for mining vehicles.
Nod, nod.
Oh, I see.
That makes sense.
I hadn't put any consideration into Shamiko's unique trait
of being unable to carry heavy things.
Right, right. But in this case, that's not unique
to Shamiko and applies to all of humanity.
For now, I think it would be good for her to start with
something that weighs about as much as Shami-cen.
Ancestor!
Having Shamiko start with this giant tire
is making the hurdle too high.
What if you started her out
with something more lightweight first?
That makes sense.
Thank heavens, I'm saved. I can't tell you how happy I am
to have you as a friend, Anri.
Also, hey... when it comes to Shamiko, she's pretty timid
about a lot of things. She's mentally weak and fragile.
Don't you think it would be good to train her
how to be more courageous and gutsier?
That makes sense!
Like going bungie jumping, or standing under a waterfall.
Huh?
That makes sense. Got anything else?
Spending the night in an abandoned
and possibly haunted hotel?
Forget it! Don't listen to any more of Anri's advice!
Later!
Bye-bye.
Thanks.
Oh, that's right.
I have a job that might be the perfect fit for you, Shamiko!
I'll give you the details some other time!
See ya!
She had a lot of great ideas
that I never would have thought of.
Good grief. I never know if she's a friend or foe.
Tell me, what is the one thing that you're most afraid of?
Do you really think I'm going to tell you after all that?
If you want to protect the city, then don't you think
YOU should be working hard to regain your magic?
I promise I'll do my best,
so you tell me what YOU'RE most afraid of.
I took your magic so I don't have a choice,
but we're still in this together.
"In it together"? I hadn't thought about it like that.
I see. You have a point.
Something I'm afraid of... something scary...
I'm scared of stuffed mochi balls.
What...?
I'm not talking about the plain ones, either.
There's a particular shop in the Tama Sakura
shopping district that sells these.
They're strawberry stuffed mochi balls.
The strawberry is abnormally large and the mochi skin
is super thin so you can see the red paste inside
which gives it a really unsettling appearance.
Size Comparison
Plus it's even got a rich cream inside
that makes it the absolute peak of decadence.
I haven't eaten one for years.
Here, take my purse.
Okay, let's start by conquering that!
Quiver in fear, Magical Girl!
Heh, heh, heh, triple heh.
Their evening stock
usually sells out really fast, so run for it!
Roger!
If you can manage it, try and buy two!
Just take a look! The thin mochi
covering the dark red bean paste!
I ran really fast and had to wait in line,
but I managed to get two!
Now, quiver in fear! Embrace the absolute terror!
Come on, come on!
Are you shaking in your boots yet, Magical Girl?
Ha, ha, ha!
HA
Ha, ha... Huh?
Momo?
Here. One of them is for you, Shamiko.
Huh?
You ran really far and fast to go and get them, right?
Having a bit of a sugary snack
after a workout is extra delicious.
Nice running out there. These mochi balls
are the tastiest when you eat them fresh.
You tricked me into all this, didn't you?!
Dizzy-wizzy...
Sh-she pulled one over on me.
Don't think this means you've...
JUMP
It's super yummy!
Yum, yum.
I didn't lie about not being able
to handle these mochi balls.
Huh?
Because they make me remember the past.
That's why I've avoided eating them for years.
My sister used to love the sweets from that shop.
Do you... have a sister?
Yeah. We're not blood-related though.
I don't have any family...
Since you're doing your best to train,
I've decided to face the things I'm bad at.
I'll learn to embrace my past and everything in it.
It might help me get my magic back to normal, too.
I'll take a seat and eat.
Uh, fer sure!
Gah, she caught me off guard
so my reply came out all weird.
I'm just gonna eat the darn thing!
Shamiko.
Huh?
I'm sorry for forcing you to help me out.
Why apologize all of a sudden?
Chew
If you feel bad about it,
then you should tell me something
you're actually scared of next time.
Chew
All right.
Then...
I'm scared of drinking cold tea
together with you, Shamiko.
Roger that!
But you're not going to trick me a third time!
That was fast.
You owe me a dollar!
Please Shamiko... offer me some cold tea, too...
So, are we about wrapped up for today?
Huh? I'd say we're just getting started, don't you?
Huh?
Do you have a curfew, Shamiko?
Let's start with some stretches and squats.
I thought we were putting the muscle building on hold...
It's totally ineffective if you only train your mental muscles
without training your muscle muscles.
Muscle muscles?
There are a wide variety of methods to build muscle
without having to carry anything heavy, you know!
Momo, you're terrifying me!
Twenty-six.
Twenty-six
Twenty-seven.
Twenty-seven
I'll let you go home once you're able to move the tire.
Twenty-eight.
Twenty-nine... Twenty-nine point five...
Don't give up, Shamiko! Train both your body and mind
to overcome all the things that scare you!
Why aren't you going up to thirty?!
Sunday Morn
Yo, Shamiko!
About that job I mentioned to you before,
can you make it today?
Another job, huh?
EVENT: Meet & Greet
with Miss Tama Sakura
This is such a huge help!
Shamiko! Hey girl! Long time, no see!
The person who was originally supposed to do it
suddenly strained their back, so we were in trouble.
Come and sell wieners again sometime.
I don't know if I'm really cut out to handle such
an important role as the person inside the mascot...
You're the only one we can count on, Shamiko!
R-really?
Really! We need someone lit-
I mean someone with a compact form
chosen by God for this important duty!
You were looking for someone little, I get it.
Miss Tama Sakura
A fairy born from within an ancient cherry blossom tree.
A fairy born from within an ancient cherry blossom tree
Specialty: Backflipping Piping Hot Oden Soup.
Specialty: Backflipping Piping Hot Oden Soup
It can produce an unlimited supply
of highly-addictive candy from its oversized teacup
It can produce an unlimited supply of highly-addictive candy
from its oversized teacup to brainwash children
and use it to brainwash children.
"Highly-addictive candy"?!
Even if you don't move around much,
it's a pretty labor-intensive job.
Come to the changing room every 20 or 30 minutes
to take a break and drink water.
Ugh, this thing is pretty heavy and really hot.
I wanna see the backflip!
Give us some of that super tasty candy!
Is it true that you're really good at using nunchucks?
This mascot is pretty well-known in town!
Do that move where you climb the wall
with a ninja dagger!
Candy... please, the candy!
They really laid it on thick with the character quirks!
Aren't you going to do the backflip
into the piping hot oden soup?!
Is that really something
Miss Tama Sakura normally does?!
Candy! Use your ninja dagger! Candy! Give us the candy!
I-I'll admit it's a little fun to be this popular with little kids,
but just passing out the fliers and candy
is causing more than enough chaos!
Be careful!
Are you all right?
You really surprised me
by nearly falling back into the fountain like that.
Huh? Whose voice is that?
I can't see anything!
Come now children, can't you see
the nice kitty is having trouble?
Be good and make an orderly line.
Who is that?
Are you okay? Your head is a little off center.
I'll help you out, so let's get it back to normal.
Thank you very much.
If they pick up on it, some really weird people
might start coming around here.
In the worst-case scenario, you, your family and all
the Demons that live here might end up being hunted.
Can you see properly now?
Yeah.
I can see some clothes indicative of someone
I really don't want to see!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Sassouto shobu shite
Yatchau kedo makechatte
Fugainai nai ne
Shoushin tenshin
Kibun wa sunsun demo
Shippo de henji shiyou
Chounai de waiwai shite
Inu made bow-wow de
Tende meimei de
Shunka shuutou
Shippai shita tte waraitobasou
Ano koro to onaji you ni kokoro tsumuide
Kono machi de deaeta kiseki
Kanaete yo
Zenkai da wa tire shou ippai
Warning mada kikikanri enjoy
Toridori saita iro canvas kakenuke
Sunset da wa, kangaete bakari ja
Sou, mae!
Hora, donna iro datte yume kasanete
Motto asobou ne
Preview
Wha-wha-what? Now there's Magical Girls
starting to pop up everywhere!
It's okay, I called her here.
I don't know what you mean by things being "okay"?!
Hold on a second, I think I should
introduce myself properly first.
Don't bother, the viewers will get all they need to know
in the next episode.
The Cursed fruit!! Beware the Sour Mikan!!
Huh?
You really surprised me
by showing up already transformed!