Banda Terrace
Shamiko...
Shamiko, can you hear me?
My ancestor?!
That's right.
I was able to reach out to your consciousness
with incredible ease this evening.
For some reason, you've been simply overflowing
with magic since earlier today.
We can't afford to let this opportunity go to waste!
Which is why...
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO THE NEIGHBOR'S DREAM
...this is going to be a special episode where you
sneak into Momo's consciousness and control her!
Whoop! Whoop! Honk! Honk!
What the heck is that shoddy prop?!
Whoop! Honk! Honk!
The Demon Girl Next Door
The sun is shining too brightly
(I rubbed my eyes from the glare)
I took off without even thinking
(It's time for us to spark the joy)
When I hold back my swaying bangs with my left hand
These familiar sights start to shine
(Three, two, one)
We want to share our secret, right now
Anything is possible for us
(Always stay by my side)
For sure
(We trust each other)
On that street corner we found a precious treasure
Even if you went far away, I would definitely run after you
Our future is here, forever burning bright
The fun is only just getting started
Courage to Face the Future!!
The Heavy Roller Won't Stop
What exactly do you mean when you say
we're going to "control" Momo? It sounds bad.
Don't worry, you won't have to do anything violent.
You're simply going to use the power of our clan to dive
into Momo's subconsciousness while she's asleep.
Then you'll plant an idea in her mind
that she'll act on immediately after she wakes up.
When you wake up, give your blood to Queen Shamiko.
Top of the morning to you!
Momo's Pure Blood
Queen Shamiko!
Sorry to keep you waiting, here's 10 gallons of my blood!
Yes, most excellent!
Momo would never say something
like that no matter how you try to trick her!
Why do you seem more than a little upset about this?!
HEH
When people are asleep,
they put their guard down against the irrational.
TRIPLE HEH
Even Momo should be totally disoriented!
I'm not so sure about that.
We've gotta make the best of it
while your magic signal has full bars!
You were even able to transform this afternoon!
Transform...? Oh yeah, what the heck was up with that?
Wasn't it just the coolest thing ever?
No, it actually made things really awkward
with the neighbors!
But in that form your physical abilities improve just a bit.
It will come in really handy
whenever you have to flee the scene!
All right, let's get you inside of Momo's subconscious.
But isn't this basically just brainwashing?
Are you not on board with that?
If you ask me, this makes way more sense
than challenging her to a fist-fight.
Besides, you're a total amateur.
Whatever suggestion you plant in her
will wear off really fast.
But...
This method also assures that Momo
won't suffer any unnecessary wounds.
And you'll be able to pay her back in no time
once the seal has been broken.
Oh, that makes sense. I can totally avoid
any direct confrontation.
And if I don't have to fight her for real,
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO
THE NEIGHBOR'S
DREAM
then I won't get roped into any nonsensical running
and won't ever feel my whole body in pain again!
Sorry I put you through so much trouble.
That's a Dream Mirror that I made
by borrowing some of your magic.
I thought it was just a big rice paddle.
What the hell gave you that impression?
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO
THE NEIGHBOR'S
DREAM
Focus your mind and stare into the mirror.
You can see something speeding by really fast, right?
STARE
It looks like... static TV noise.
It's dreams of your family, school friends,
neighbors and dogs... anyone close to your channel.
When you see Momo's dream line up perfectly,
perform a skill stop and smash the mirror to pieces!
Let's warp!
Warp
Let's
What is this, a fighting game?!
More than a hundred different people are flying by
in only a few seconds. This is impossible!
All I can make out are gray afterimages.
Hm, it seems like your frequency
isn't attuned to Momo very well.
Just build up all the dark feelings
you have towards Momo!
If you do that then I'm sure you'll be able
to enter the Bonus Round!
"Dark feelings"?! And what the heck is a "Bonus Round"?!
Momo is... uh...
Darkness... Darkness... Darkness... Darkness...
...the person who saved me from the dump trunk
and also saved my octopus wieners.
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO THE NEIGHBOR'S DREAM
DARKNESS
She also helped me find the thing that Ryo really wanted.
Ancestor! This isn't good!
I can't think of anything dark! I got nothing!
Can we make this my homework
for the week or something?
I promise I'll come up with something firm
by this weekend!
No way! You have to get this done tonight!
There has to be... something I don't like about Momo.
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO THE NEIGHBOR'S DREAM
Do you want some too, Shamiko? It's really yummy.
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO THE NEIGHBOR'S DREAM
Whenever you're around it really
throws my life out of whack! Darn it!
MUCK
Where the heck am I now?!
Everything's covered in muck, did I screw up?!
Huh?
Momo!
Um...
You look...
Uh, you ARE Momo right?
You're kind of tiny though.
I am. Who are you, lady?
Huh?
Maybe Momo doesn't know who I am
because we're inside a dream right now?
Plus, she's tiny and has longer hair.
I was just passing by, I'm Shami...
I mean, I'm a Denizen of the Dark!
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO
THE NEIGHBOR'S
DREAM
I came to get a first-hand look at your dream!
Huh?
So, uh... this is quite the dreamscape, huh?
Seems like you might have slipped in some mud,
or maybe ate some liver...
She's totally shutting me out!
Actually, to be honest with you,
I came here hoping to undo a seal.
I would really appreciate it if you could share
some of your Magical Girl blood with me.
I can't do that. You're a Demon Lady, aren't you?
Besides, I can't afford to just donate my blood.
That would weaken my magic powers.
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO THE NEIGHBOR'S DREAM
And in order to keep this city peaceful,
my magic can't become any weaker than it is right now.
"Peaceful"?
MUCK
But... I've done a really poor job of that already.
Agh! The muck is starting to build up!
Does it just get worse and worse
when baby Momo starts shedding tears?!
These aren't tears, it's eye juice.
MUCK
It's fine, you don't have to force yourself
to lie to me right now!
MUCK
Stand up!
At this rate we're both going to drown
before I can even plant any ideas in her head.
What happens if we drown inside a dream?!
Crisis Management!
Momo! We're going to clean.
This is a compulsory cleanup
of your entire mind, top to bottom.
Please assist me.
Why did you strip off your clothes?
I didn't strip, this is my Crisis Management Form!
No more talk, get to work.
We managed to clear up the majority of it.
It ended up pretty bleak in here, though.
It took more effort than I had expected.
You're starting to look a bit better.
Would you like some cola?
It seems I can only produce things that I've seen recently.
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO
THE NEIGHBOR'S
DREAM
But I'm starting to get the hang of my powers.
Now then, with all of the muck out of the way
I can start planting ideas... Huh?
SNEAK ATTACK!
INTO THE NEIGHBOR'S DREAM
What?
Momo?!
I ran out of time?!
I was so close...
I remember everything that happened in the dream.
But if Momo remembers everything too, then...
I've got you now, Peeping Demon!
You deserve a good smackerel!
Good morning.
I'M SO VERY SORRY!
P-please don't... not the smackerel!
SHAKE
What are you talking about?
Oh, you don't remember...
Huh?
You look really pale in the face, Momo.
And your usually clean-cut hair is a mess, too!
You think so?
Actually, I feel like I may have caught a cold yesterday.
Why do you have that?
I don't really know myself, but for some reason
I've developed a strong urge to drink cola.
Don't tell me, this is because...
And also, I'm... not feeling so great.
Momo?!
Momo Chiyoda won't be able to come today.
5 YEN
(5 cents)
She started feeling really sick on her way to school.
Yes. I'm going to make sure that she gets home okay,
so I'll be coming late.
Thank you, please excuse me!
Could the cause of this be...
...some negative impact from all
the cleaning we did in her subconscious?
Are you okay, Momo?
I had a really weird dream last night.
I don't remember much, but it wasn't pleasant.
Although, I felt really relieved at the tail end of it...
You felt really relieved?
Yeah.
I also vaguely remember it involved an exhibitionist.
I'm not an exhibitionist, that was my Battle Form!
Momo, can you help guide me to where your house is?
She's already half-asleep!
Wait, her guard is down so this might be...
Shamiko...
I'm sorry.
I'll let you off the hook for today!
You're heavy!
Don't give up, Shamiko! Be proud of the fact
that you found a working payphone in this day and age!
Wh-wha-what?!
HUGE
You live in a Community Center?!
This is a house.
Thanks, I can manage just fine on my own from here.
My bag...
Bag
No way! You can hardly stay standing!
I'm worried... no, that's not right.
Since I'm already here, it's only proper etiquette
that I steal some of my rival's secrets!
Let me guess, if I don't step on the right tiles here,
I'll be dropped into a tank of flour!
Those little lamps are suspicious, too!
It's just an ordinary walkway,
so you can step wherever you want.
Then I'm going to take the path
where I only step on the white ones.
The door has an auto-lock.
It will open if you put in the security code.
Why is your house so high-tech?!
Let me guess, if I input the wrong code,
then I'll be dropped into a tank full of lobsters!
They'll clamp their claws onto my nose!
It's an ordinary number lock.
The code is: "Live Chicks n' Jive Tricks Wahoo."
Live Chicks 'n' Jive Tricks Wahoo
What...?
I made a mistake, it's "Five, Six, Five, Six, Two."
"Live Chicks n' Jive Tricks Wahoo"! I've memorized it!
Do you have a thermometer anywhere?
I'm not sure. Maybe in the drawer of the computer desk.
This is super cute!
That's not a thermometer.
That's my Heartful Peach Morphing Stick.
Heartful!
I made a mistake.
That's just an ordinary stick, so go put it back.
You can go home now, I'll be all right.
I'm getting excited, it's too early to leave yet!
I get the feeling I can win the fight today!
Huh?
A kitty!
That's my navigator, Metako.
"Navigator"?
A familiar of the Light Clan.
They provide guidance to Magical Girls.
If you put it in a good mood with toys or something,
it will give you an oracle.
It just spits out holy oracles like a dad telling jokes?!
Gah!
Gritty, gritty. Gritty, gritty...
I feel something really gritty...
Yeah, I thought it might get attached to your tail.
It used to talk quite a lot, but because of its age
and the fact that I've lost my motivation
now it's basically a regular cat 97% of the time.
I'd really like to hear it talk.
The time hath come.
I-I think I just got an oracle.
Even though I'm a Demon.
It does that all the time to the mailman and the vet.
Since it's past its prime, "The time hath come"
is all it really says now, anyway.
Is that so?
I've been talking too much. I'm going to rest for a bit.
Ah, I'm sorry.
You seem in worse shape than before.
Do you really not know where you keep
the thermometer or medicine?
I don't really get sick, usually.
I feel like I last used the medicine box about...
10 years ago.
Then I don't think you need to bother
trying to find it anymore!
The time hath come.
Exactly!
Medicine has an expiration date!
You two became fast friends.
We at least have to find a way to cool your forehead.
Can I open the fridge?
Sure.
Momo, can you tell me where exactly
I can find the ice in here?
Huh?
What is this?
SHOCK!!
Ah, I changed my mind about the fridge!
Don't open the fridge, Shamiko!
Momo!
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
You already found it, huh?
You... didn't want me to see this?
MUCK...
Don't tell me this is a monument you made
from pulverizing Demons?
Absolutely not!
That's... my failed attempt at making hamburg steak.
Something this dark and sinister...
Something this
dark and sinister...
...can only be made from the deep-seated hatred
of a Demon that faced punishment beyond imagination.
It's made from plain old beef!
Why were you making a hamburg steak?
Because I made that promise to you, Shamiko.
Huh? Oh, you mean when we practiced shooting magic.
Yeah. I just kind of blurted it out back then,
but I planned on keeping that promise.
But I only have experience cooking pre-made food...
... and no matter what I did I couldn't make
a tasty hamburg steak.
It would be a waste to throw away,
so I've been eating it myself.
But my heart could never take
more than just one bite per meal...
I'm guessing that's what caused you to get sick.
If you made it for me, then I'm going to eat it!
Gulp.
Gulp
I was really nervous going by looks alone,
but this doesn't taste bad at all!
Y-you think so?
It's hard on the outside and mushy on the inside,
plus I can really taste the raw onions and salt.
I'm not so sure that's a good thing.
It's just fine!
Truly terrible food makes you go numb
the moment you bite into it,
and your throat will force you
to throw it back up right away!
Anything that doesn't cause that reaction is totally edible!
Do you have any clean chopsticks?
Do you have
any clean
chopsticks?
Warning:
This girl has undergone
special training in this field
as part of her family's
circumstances.
Please be very careful
to confirm whether
food prepared and
left out during the summer
is safe to eat.
Warning: This girl has undergone special training
in this field as part of her family's circumstances.
Please be very careful to confirm whether food prepared
and left out during the summer is safe to eat.
You have a large strike zone when it comes to food, huh?
Thanks for the meal!
I'm embarrassed that you ended up seeing my screw up.
If you always live in fear of other people
seeing your weaknesses,
then you'll never be able to make any progress in life.
I've screwed up quite a lot myself, but despite that,
I've made progress a little bit at a time.
I see.
You're really strong, Shamiko.
I guess I'll try cooking it again
and have you taste test it for me.
Please do!
I think you should reduce the amount of salt enough
so that the flavor of the meat actually comes through.
HERE
You went out of your way to use good beef, but all
I could taste was the flavor of salt, onion and charcoal?
I changed my mind. You don't get any
until I've at least made it taste like a proper steak.
Why?!
All you had in your fridge aside from
the hamburg steak was wieners and plain bread.
A diet like that isn't healthy,
even if you do live by yourself.
I have an idea! Why don't you come over
to my house to eat sometime?
My mom's specialty is hamburg steak,
so she might be able to teach you how to make it!
I'd love to... come over and do that sometime.
In our house, the main ingredient in hamburg steak
is tofu, so it's really fluffy and yummy!
It also has some chicken breast meat and onions inside!
Plus, it's covered in a thick sauce
with lots of mushrooms!
Can that really be called "hamburg steak"?
Anyway, I'm going to prepare a wet towel
to cool you off so please go and rest.
I need you to recover and get back to being
a proper Magical Girl, otherwise I can't beat you!
R-right...
Zzz...
Zzz... Zzz...
She's still got a fever,
but I think her breathing has returned to normal.
Looking at her sleep like this,
she doesn't seem very strong at all.
Crap, I don't have time for this!
Don't think this means you've won!
That's not nearly as satisfying to say in a whisper!
Oh hey, we might have a stock of udon
or other soups at home.
She's got a cut!
Did that happen when she fell down earlier?
Wipe
Jeez, Momo is really throwing everything
out of whack for me today!
The time hath come.
What's wrong, Metako?
to get some food supplies
I'll be back soon.
-Yuko
I'm going home
My blood...
Notice it, Shamiko! You've gotten your hands
on various precious things right now!
I wonder if we have an ice pack in the fridge...
I'm home!
Though nobody else should be here right now, anyway.
I'll make some udon for Momo
and then head for school in the afternoon.
I'm feeling an aura of loneliness and pity
coming from somewhere!
Oh crap! The Ancestue!
It's being used as the perfect paper weight
for all the ads and junk mail we're throwing away!
We've just gotten too used to it
being a decoration kept near the front door...
I'm sorry, I'll take you to school later.
I knew I felt more lightweight than usual today.
I hope we have some udon handy.
Huh?
I'm too late...
Momo? Why are you here?
I was finally able to figure out where you live, Shamiko.
As I suspected, there was a barrier keeping it concealed.
When you were taking care of me earlier,
you invited me over. Remember?
I think in order for me to get past the barrier,
it was necessary to have your permission.
Do you know what this is, Shamiko?
Huh?
A designer's door?
You just thought it was a chic decoration, huh?
This is a protection barrier of the Light Clan,
it makes it fate that ordinary people
can't interact with those who live inside.
It has deteriorated, but in order to get through a person
needs approval or be approached by the residents.
It's a pretty complex barrier
that requires an advanced level of...
YOSHIDA
What are you doing?
You're still burning up.
I think your fever has gotten worse!
Now isn't the time to be worried about that.
No! If we're going to talk, at least sit down first.
Do you feel hungry at all?
I do, but now really isn't the time to...
Which do you prefer, a bowl of cold udon or hot udon?
Cold.
It's delicious.
I just boiled some frozen udon and then added it
to a cold noodle stock with some fresh ginger.
What's a "noodle stock"?
Huh? A broth made from soy sauce,
kelp water, and sugar. You can buy it à la carte.
Festival
"A large cart"?
Does everything trip you up when it comes to cooking?!
I guess so.
But you were frying up those wieners
the other day with such ease.
Cooking is the one thing you can do, Shamiko.
What do you mean "the one thing"?!
This reminds me, we had udon the first time
we had a meal together.
Anyway, back to business.
You undid the seal earlier, right?
Huh?
You took my blood when I was asleep, didn't you?
WHAT?
You just realized it now?
So, you undid the seal completely on accident then?
I had forgotten all about it, to be honest.
I mean, you were sick and injured...
Well, whatever.
I can't do anything about it now.
Do you at least know what kind of seal you undid?
From what I've heard, your family has a long history
of having the majority of your powers sealed away.
Shock!
I don't think any serious powers will come back
with just that tiny bit of blood, but...
Why do you know about my family's history?
Anri told me all about it.
Oh, Shamiko? Up until this spring she was always
really sick and had to go home or to the hospital
Oh, Shamiko? Up until this spring
she was always really sick and
had to go home or to the hospital
but after she grew
those horns on her head,
she's gotten a lot
healthier!
but after she grew those horns on her head,
she's gotten a lot healthier!
By the way, her family situation is complicated
and I guess they have to deal with a seal or something,
By the way, her family situation
is complicated and I guess they
have to deal with a seal or something,
I don't really know
all the deatils,on $400 a month.
all the deatils,
but I hear they
can only live
I don't really know all the details,
but I hear they can only live on $400 a month.
Isn't that nuts?! Oh, and she doesn't go
to any after school clubs, either...
Isn't that nuts?! Oh and she doesn't
go to any after school clubs, either....
I just knew she was an assassin!
Anyway, we should figure out
what kind of powers you got back.
That sounds like a good idea to me.
Did you hear that just now?
I did.
You've done it, Shadow Mistress!
I've tasted the sweet, condensed flavor
of the Magical Girl's blood mixed with that musky towel.
It's all thanks to you!
Ancestor?!
Now it begins...
But I'll get sick with the world upside down like this,
so could you turn me right side up?
Ah, I'm so sorry!
What's going on, Ancestor?
Apparently, I can now talk with you directly
in the real world.
Mmmmph
Mmmph!
I've been trying really hard for a while now,
but I can't produce anything but a mouth.
I'd really love some arms and legs, too...
Is that you, Ms. Lilith?
Momo Chiyoda!
I owe you a lot for that trip to the Health Spa!
The only thing that changed
is the statue becoming more annoying?
I had a chunk of my magic drained away just for that?
What do you mean "just for that"?!
Ugh...
You're being incredibly rude right now!
As a result, I've lost a significant amount of magic power.
Shamiko, in exchange for the blood and magic
you borrowed from me
I want you to help me protect the city.
Huh?! Momo, you've been protecting the city?
Yeah.
Isn't it weird for a Demon
to help you with something like that?
It's no less weird than a Demon
going out to the mall for some udon.
Grr...
But I didn't borrow your magic, I challenged you
and then won it fair and square... I think...
Attacking someone you owe a bunch of debt to
while they're sick and asleep is unfair, right?
That's cheating, right?
Are you a cheat, Shamiko?
But I... didn't do it on purpose,
I was trying to tend to your wound.
Whether it was intentional or not,
I lost magic in the process.
Whose uniform are you wearing, again?
Not to mention that laptop.
Until my magic recovers, you're going to help me. Right?
Smile
Th-this is unfair!
Protecting the city would also benefit you, Shamiko.
Huh?
The peace of this city was only held together
by a delicate balance in the first place.
Even losing just a single drop of blood results
in a drastic drop in magic power.
My unstable condition should be delectable
even by those who live outside the city.
If they pick up on it, some really weird people
might start coming around here.
In the worst-case scenario, you, your family, and
all the Demons that live here might end up being hunted.
I want you to protect them and yourself.
My family?! That's absolutely unacceptable!
I'll train hard! And do whatever you want me to!
HEAVY ROLLER
I'll swing a metal bat! Or pull a giant tire or something!
Your idea of training is a tad outdated.
Right now, the majority of Demons
and Magical Girls are peaceful types.
Any sort of incident between them is rare.
But no matter what... I want to keep this one city safe.
Why is that?
Don't get hung up on stuff like that.
By the way, Momo... are you feeling under the weather?
Are you going to be all right taking a hit
to your magic on top of being sick?
To be perfectly honest...
I'm the opposite of okay.
MOMO!
You've gone completely blue in the face!
And your body temp feels hotter than the most intense
hot spring they had at the Health Spa!
The time hath come. The time hath come.
The time hath come.
The time hath come... The time hath come...
Don't think this means you've won.
Huh? Did you say something just now?
For about a week after this,
Momo stayed home from school.
Say, Ancestor? Are a lot of things
going to start changing around me now?
What should I do?
You should handle things at your own pace,
as you see fit, Shamiko.
You already made a huge accomplishment
by enabling me to talk once again.
I give you my thanks.
Great!
I'll put some real thought into what I can do.
For now, I need to report to my mom and Ryo
about the progress I made with the seal.
By the way, is my nickname confirmed to be "Shamiko"?
I think it's pretty fitting, don't you?
Don't give up, Shamiko! Work on gaining a lot of
experience and become the most capable Demon!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Gallantly, I demand a duel
I go at it, but I lose
It's beyond disappointing
Shift away from that grief
Even when I’m feeling curt
I’ll express myself with that tail
There's a party in the neighborhood
Even the dogs are going bow-wow
Each and every last one
For all four seasons
When you fail just laugh it off
Connecting our hearts like that time once before
With the miracle that we met in this town
Grant this wish
Shoulder those tires and go full throttle
Warning, there's still crises to manage, so enjoy
Various blooming colors are spilling off the canvas
Now its sunset, don't bother thinking too much
Just go on!
Come on, our compiled dreams can be any color
So let's play some more
Preview
I was causing major plot developments
without even realizing it!
Yeah, a ton of things happened in this episode.
Thanks to Shamiko, I'm finally able to talk again!
Ancestor, please keep your voice down!
Now that the Magical Girl's blood has partially undone the seal,
And Momo, I really hope you get over that cold quickly!
I know the audience is looking forward to enjoying
all of my wonderful commentary
The Pink Method!! The Wheel of Fate is a Round Tire!!
Next time, Shamiko is going to work an all new job!
as I, the great Lilith, participate even more in the show!
By the way, I called in some help.
Also, I want better offerings fro-