In order to keep this city peaceful,
my magic can't become any weaker than it is right now.
MUCK
But... I've done a really poor job of that already.
My sister used to love the sweets from that shop.
Well, you know that
Magical Girls sometimes dematerialize
if they use up too much of their magic, right?
We have to be sure not to put any more strain on her.
Ancestor, I'm thinking about trying to get Momo
to open her heart to me.
Oh?
I'll get closer to her until she finally drops her guard,
and then seek out the info I need
to compete with her as an equal.
I got the idea from Ryo.
Wonderful, Shamiko! You've finally learned
how to think things through.
So, what exactly is your plan for getting closer to Momo?
Make a delicious lunch to give her every single day.
Thank you, Shamiko! I'm really weak to any attacks
on the bone that's just out of the elbow.
Just like that.
Oh jeez, I take back what I said.
The Demon Girl Next Door
Taiyou mabushisugite
(Chikachika me o kosutta)
Omowazu tobidashita yo
(Dokidoki no hajimiari sa)
Yurayura yureru maegami hidarite de osaetara
Itsumo no keshiki ga kirameku yo
(Three, two, one)
Ima sugu tsutaetai futari no himitsu
Watashitachi nara dekiru yo
(Itsumo tonari ni ite)
Kitto
(Shijiteru kara)
Machikado de mitsuketa daiji na takaramono
Tatoe kimi ga tooku hanaretemo kanarazu oikakeru yo
Zutto kagayaiteru mirai wa koko ni aru
Otanoshimi wa kore kara
Diving into Dreams Once Again!!
Break Through the Pink Defense Line
Hmm... How can I get Momo to open her heart?
Listen, Shamiko. You don't have to use
such roundabout methods to get things done.
You have the perfect ability for times like these, no?
Don't forget you're a descendant
of the great succubus Lilith, dominator of dreams!
All you have to do is dive into Momo's dream
and then implant her with deep affection for you!
Deep affection...
While you're at it, implant her
with a proper sense of respect for me, too!
That girl is always so insolent when it comes to me!
Not to mention that air of superiority she gives off!
If you could make her reflexively drop on all fours
whenever she sees me, that would be great.
I would hate having a Momo like that!
And make sure to implant the idea that she should make
3 spare bodies for me to inhabit every day.
I would also enjoy it if you could....
LILITH'S JOURNAL
OF FRUSTRATING
EXPERIENCES
COLA
...force her to dance and groove to the rhythm!
The world doesn't revolve around you, Ancestor.
But isn't doing that kind of like cheating?
We're at war, Shamiko.
You'll just be disrespecting your opponent if you
don't charge at them with everything in your arsenal.
But...
COLA
Let me guess, you were just putting on a show
with all that tough talk earlier.
The truth is that you're just sulking
because Momo already knows your secrets.
Heh-heh-heh... Heh-heh-heh!
That's not true!
There's no reason for you to be so interested
in discovering her true feelings otherwise.
That's not the case AT ALL!
Fine then! I'll play dirty if that's what it takes!
Excellent! That's the spirit!
Now then, let's hurry and get you to sleep.
I'll act as your support once you start dreaming.
The last time that I dived into Momo's dream,
it ended up being a huge hassle.
Is it going to be the same this time?
Diving into the dream of someone you've already
connected to before is easy, it's a straight shot!
Your magic has also been slowly growing as of late.
That's made it easier for me to connect with you, too.
But just in case...
Canned Peaches
...you should leave some pictures of her by your pillow
to create a stronger connection to her channel.
This is too weird!
You give careful thought to your subordinates
even in your sleep, huh, Sis?
Don't you dare take any pictures!
Huh? Where am I?
Hey, Shamiko.
Ancestor?
You've reached the outer-most region
of Momo's subconscious.
The outer-most region?
I'm certain that she has some sort of guard
built around her heart, so go smash it to pieces!
Smash it? But I haven't brought
any tools or weapons with me.
Listen, you're a succubus.
As a demon of dreams, you can conjure up
whatever weapons you want!
Any weapon I want, huh?
I think you can make more creative choices than those...
This sucks, I was able to go
straight to the center of her dream last time.
The ease of which you can enter dreams
depends on the physical state of your prey.
Momo is probably in better condition
than the last time you came.
Why would she be in better condition than before?
1 Head of cabbage
per person
Oh! It was me!
I was giving my mortal enemy nutrients
that made her stronger!
I want to conserve as much of your magic as possible,
so I'm cutting our connection.
Oh crap! I screwed up! Gah!
If you get into a pinch,
feel free to rely on the Ancestor Telephone.
"Ancestor Telephone"?
Anyway, I wish you the best of luck!
Huh?
Ancestor...
I guess all I can do now is look for the entrance...
Who art thou?
A-a cat-man?!
Wait, is that you Metako?
Oh, and it looks like there's an entrance behind you.
Nay, I am not Metatron.
I am naught but one of the 365,000 eyes of Metatron.
I stand watch over pure souls of the Light Clan priests
and assure no vermin defile them with their filth.
I am one of the angelic order!
Just looking at him is so overwhelming
that my brain can't even process what he's saying.
Oh, he stopped glowing.
Metako, I want to get inside of Momo's heart.
Please let me in.
Deliberating.
I am uncertain.
Thou doth emit an aura of darkness, however I also
sense a trace of my former master, Sakura Chiyoda.
"Sakura Chiyoda"?
Who art thou?
What is thy purpose here?
I am Momo's mortal enemy!
My plan today is to invade her heart
and then go from there!
Exterminate!
It was worth a try! Crisis Management!
Oh, that's right! I should be able
to conjure up some weapons in here!
Um, something strong... I need something strong!
Okay, how about one of those pistols I saw
in that movie recently?
Wait, what was the trigger supposed to look like again?
Maybe a missile...
but what are those actually made out of?
Crap, my mind can't help
but imagine a daikon radish instead!
My imagination is so terrible
I can't conjure up anything useful!
Whatever, anything will help at this point!
Something that left an impact on me recently which
seems strong, tough and has a really simple shape!
I summon you! New Ancestor!
Scuttle, scuttle, scuttle...
Hm? That looks like...
...a delicious bug!
That takes care of that problem but... what the heck...?
I ended up creating a really surreal dream.
I finally made it to the entrance.
GACHUNK
Huh?
It won't open. But why?
Grr
Oh, I know!
There's a number lock!
"Live Chicks n' Jive Tricks Wahoo."
I'm one of those brainy demons!
BUZZ
Huh?
Fine, I'll just force my way in
with the closest thing to a weapon I can get!
Take THIIIIIIS!
SNAP!!
What do I do now?
This door might be made so that
a Demon like me could never open it.
If I knew I would end up feeling this hopeless,
I should have tried harder in the real world instead.
I'm not going to give up just yet.
I summon you! Lunch box!
Momo? I brought you some food.
Please let me in!
Pretty please!
Shamiko?
Momo!
Come on in.
You don't have to tell me twice!
The Momo that exists in her dream
is welcoming me inside!
What a relief... thank you, Momo...
I was scared, so scared...
I wasn't sure what to do!
Right.
I was so worried that I couldn't
open the door no matter what I tried.
I see.
But that puts an end to my suffering for today!
Now I can launch my campaign
to implant your head with-
Nope. What's about to happen
is you getting a harsh scolding.
I can tell you're the real Shamiko and not just
a figment of my dream. What's going on?
Huh? This isn't like the last time I was here!
Um... well, you see...
Oh! Now's a good time to use the Ancestor Telephone!
I'm in trouble, Ancestor! What's going on?!
I've got bad news, Shamiko. It seems that Momo's
consciousness has awakened within the dream.
What the heck does that mean?!
It's what they call a lucid dream.
The Momo inside of this dream
is now aware that she's dreaming.
And she's got a tight hold on your tail right now,
which means you can't make a break for it.
Then... what do I do?
It's a raw deal, but I'm stuck behind my seal
so I can't help you.
Oh, the magic we use to talk is about to run out!
I'm rooting for you, Shamiko!
Ancestor!
Cola is the best!
Let's have a chat while we eat the food you brought.
Lunch box!
AWKWARD   AWKWARD   AWKWARD
When did you figure it all out?
I was watching Metako chomping down on a Shamicen
with long legs, when I realized that this was all a dream.
The dream Ancestor I conjured up got eaten in the end...
I was just about to wake up
when I heard you shouting, so I went to take a look.
D-don't think this means you've won.
Bye.
You can't go until you've answered all of my questions.
Huh?
Oh, there's only one pair of chopsticks here.
Please let me out of here!
Shamiko, can you conjure up another pair of chopsticks?
Ancestooooor!
Don't give up, Shamiko! Next time, make sure
to review the things you want to conjure before you go!
Within Momo's Dream
So, you can dive into
and manipulate other people's dreams?
I can't believe you never mentioned having such
an incredibly powerful ability like that.
Now Momo knows about
my one and only secret weapon.
Is my ability really all that incredible? Isn't it kind of dull?
It's very powerful!
The fact you haven't realized how dangerous it can be
means that you really have no combat sense at all!
I can come up with 100 or 200 different ways
to abuse that power for evil, easily!
But aren't you supposed to be a heroic Magical Girl?!
By the way, which of those methods
did you think would work the best?
I won't tell you, because it'll be a bad influence!
Oh?
You really aren't suited to being a fighter, Shamiko.
Why do you keep pushing yourself to fight despite that?
I'm not pushing myself!
I'm really not.
I... When I was young...
...my body was really weak
and I was always in the hospital.
Even after I was discharged,
they told me I shouldn't run or exert myself.
That and my eyesight was terri-
You weren't supposed to run?!
But I've forced you to run quite a lot, haven't I?
I would be upset if you held back on my account,
and I've actually been healthy ever since I grew horns.
Are you really that stupid, Shamiko?!
Why wouldn't you tell me something
so important about yourself?!
Well you've been keeping
plenty of secrets of your own, Momo!
Huh?
Mikan told me all about it.
She said that Magical Girls
who lose their magic can disappear.
Uh, I just didn't think that was worth mentioning.
Does that mean you only think of me
as an insignificant filler villain?
You've got the wrong idea!
I really want to beat you,
but I don't want you to disappear if I do!
Then I'm only more confused about
why you're so persistent about fighting me!
Didn't you want to undo the seal upon your family?
That's neither here nor there!
I'm not giving up on the seal,
but I'm going to find another way to handle it!
I want to undo the seal.
My mom won't admit to it,
but I think my father is unable to come home because
he's working to pay off the debt from my treatment!
That's why I have to do everything I can!
Your father is working away from home?
Do you know exactly where he went?
Yeah, according to my mom...
Until recently, your father was a squid fisherman
on a nuclear-powered submersible aircraft carrier,
and now he's a crewmember responsible
for buying air purifiers onboard a space battleship!
Amazing!
Squid fishing usually happens at night...
But wait, that's not the real problem here...
Huh? Momo, are you getting worn out?
Somehow that managed to give me a headache
inside of my own dream.
Your lack of knowledge
is just too overwhelming, Shamiko.
I'm starting to understand that you were raised
by a very protective family.
Remember the piece of paper
that was taped onto your front door?
That's a barrier designed to protect Demons
from being hunted by Magical Girls.
Protect them from being hunted?
Being a Magical Girl works on a point-based system.
The more Demons we hunt, the greater return we get.
Although these days, there aren't many of us
who hunt so incessantly.
So, you mean...
ALL BATTLES ARE
MADE BY APPPOINTMENT
NO RAIDS
-THE DEMONS
...that paper on our door has the same impact
as those "No Soliciting" signs meant for salesmen!
That's not quite right! Actually, you're way off base!
Do you know who made that barrier, Shamiko?
The fact that paper is on your door probably means that
your mother is hiding something important, Shamiko.
Huh? But my mother isn't a bad person!
She's always so nice
and has suffered so much because of me...
Right, but there's still something strange going on.
I'm sorry to say it, but I also think she lied about
your father being away from home for work.
Are you saying that he's not actually on the crew of a
space battleship?! What about the squid fishing?!
Squid
Fishing...
What I want to know is why you never doubted it!
Even the nuclear-powered submersible aircraft carrier?!
Even if it did exist, they wouldn't use it to fish for squid!
It seems likely that your mother is the key to all of this.
My mom is?
Momo?!
Mikan...?
It looks like she's having a terrible nightmare!
Hey, are you okay?
Her timing couldn't be any worse...
I'm a little busy inside of my dream right now,
so don't wake me up.
But I'm worried because your face looks incredibly pale!
And also, Metako ate something weird
off the carpet that I couldn't identify!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! I'm starting to panic!
Nice timing on that friendly fire, Mikan!
Is the dream world just going to fall apart like this?
Shamiko!
Huh?
I get the feeling that there's some
secret hidden in your house!
I'm going to head there as soon as I wake up!
You need to start being more upfront about everything!
Your family... specifically your mom...
you should grill her...!
"Grill"...?
Oh, Momo! You finally woke up! Are you okay?
Hinatsuki Brand
Mikan Buns
Would you like some mikan flavored buns?
Huh?
Mikan...
I completely understand that you shook me awake
because you thought it was for the best.
But it backfired.
What? Did I screw up something important again?!
Yuko! It's already noon!
Huh? What was I just doing?
I remember diving into Momo's dream
and then getting captured...
Your mother... needs to be grilled!
I'm coming to your house!
Grilled... grilled... She's gonna eat her?!
GRILL
(TO COOK)
She needs to be grilled!
Did you sleep in because you feel sick?
Mom! Ouch!
That Magical Girl I mentioned before
is coming here right now!
Oh dear, really?
The only drink we have available is barley tea
that I just started to steep, so it still looks like water.
That's not the problem! She's coming here to grill you!
You have to hide!
Yuko?
Crisis Management Form!
Shamiko.
Momo...
P-please just leave us alone.
Why did you transform? Are you actually an exhibitionist?
Look, I know that you're here to go after my mom!
GRILL
(TO COOK)
You said you were going to grill her!
Yeah, I really think you should give her a good grilling.
GRILL
(TO QUESTION)
You're her daughter, after all.
Tremble
Do children normally ever want to... grill their parents?
GRILL
(TO EAT)
Why do you seem so scared by the idea?
TREMBLE
Who wouldn't be absolutely terrified by the thought of it?!
My mom isn't a bad person!
Even if she's not bad,
we know that she's hiding something.
And that's enough of a reason to grill her?!
GRILL
(TO EAT)
EEEEK!
You're better off doing it than not.
I know you're not good at holding people's feet
to the fire, Shamiko. So I'll help you out with this one.
You're really serious about
making this happen, aren't you?!
Hey girls, I get the feeling
that neither of you is on the same page here.
Scuttle, scuttle.
SHUDDER...
SPARKLE
ANCESTOOOOOOR!
Oh God, my body just threw Ms. Lilith totally on instinct!
My power to dive into her dreams
ended up working in a weird way!
Shamiko... let me through.
Absolutely not!
I'm doing this because I'm worried about you, Shamiko!
Yoshida
Oh, in times like these...
From now on, I think I can overcome any mountains that
get in my way by just remembering this okonomiyaki!
Yeah, okonomiyaki!
Huh?
The very first time I came to your house with food...
...all of the food that you thought was delicious
is something that my mom taught me how to make.
I don't care if she keeps secrets
and no matter how illogical it may be,
I want to protect my mom, Ryo, and this house
that my father will someday come back to!
Magical Girl, Momo Chiyoda!
If you want to get into this house,
then you're going to have to defeat me to do it!
You've been misunderstanding each other
this whole time and I can't stand it anymore!
We'll continue this chat once you come inside!
Mom?!
Yuko has always been frail and for a long time,
she was educated inside the hospital.
This is the first time she's ever brought a friend home.
She's not my friend, she's my mortal enemy!
I have a lot of things I would like to ask you.
Yes, I'm sure that you do.
Yuko is a much stronger girl than I ever imagined.
I know that I have to tell her the truth.
Though there are many things that I find difficult to say.
For starters, Yuko...
I think you should avoid wearing that outfit
you had on earlier outside from now on.
You'll catch a cold.
Please direct your complaints about that to our ancestor!
Now then... where should I start?
When Yuko was very little,
my husband and I moved to this city.
The Magical Girl in charge of the city helped us
secure this apartment guarded by the barrier.
BANDA TERRACE
The situation for Demons back then
was much more brutal than it is now.
Yes, I knew about all of that already.
The Demons in this city are all protected by a barrier
that was set up by the Magical Girl before me.
Oh! Was she a girl named Sakura Chiyoda?
How do you know that name, Shamiko?
I heard it from a super muscular Metako
in your dream earlier!
Super muscular?
The Magical Girl known as Sakura Chiyoda
was both my teacher and sister-in-law.
Your sister?
Yes... and she went missing over 10 years ago.
Miss Seiko, please tell me everything you know
about what happened back then.
Your family and Shamiko have been
the only lead I’ve found in all those years.
Sure, I’ll explain everything to you
in the order that it happened.
Yuko was born with an incredibly frail body
and terrible luck.
It’s possible that Yuko inherited
most of the demon blood in the family,
and thereby suffered more from the effects of the curse.
In fact, her younger sister Ryoko
hardly seems to be affected by the seal at all.
It’s true that compared to Ryo,
Shamiko is pretty much a waste of space.
So, all of her natural talent
has just been drained by the seal.
Momo! What happened to you phrasing things nicely?!
Not quite! Personally speaking, I think part of it
is that she’s grown to take after her mother.
To be honest, I was very klutzy before I got married!
Tee-hee
Please don’t crush my hopes and dreams, mom!
Seiiki
Memorial Hospital
Thanks to the continued efforts
of my husband and Ms. Sakura,
Yuko was ultimately saved and her health improved.
Back when we first came to this city,
I was pregnant with Ryoko.
Yuko was in very poor condition
and got placed in the same hospital that I was.
My husband went to meet with Ms. Sakura,
thinking that she could help Yuko somehow.
Apparently, she agreed to interfere
with the curse placed upon our family.
So, my sister...
Dogs
Lottery Luck
Traffic
Sports
Economic Fortune
Health
Ms. Sakura wracked her brains to find a way,
and managed to swap our family’s remaining economic
fortune for an increased blessing of Yuko’s health.
Somehow, she rebalanced all of the resources
that fate left us so we could survive, which resulted in...
...the "$400 Per Month" curse falling upon us!
So that’s why the curse is set at a rate
that matches the modern era!
So basically, Momo’s sister messed with the curse
upon me and that’s why I ended up becoming healthy?
It didn’t fix everything though, which is why
you stayed in the hospital for a while afterwards.
My sister was extremely proficient
when it came to manipulating magic.
But I think that interfering in an ancient seal
would be difficult even for her.
That was what I heard.
The cost for countering a multilayered seal
from ancient times was very heavy.
From what I heard it soon became difficult for
Ms. Sakura to protect the city due to the loss of magic.
That’s why my husband struck a deal and ultimately
ended up cooperating with her to keep the city safe.
Um, so is there any truth to Shamiko’s father
being away from home for work?
I suppose I should explain.
I think it’s time for me to come clean
with Yuko about everything.
Huh?
After it became clear
that Yuko would be able to live her life...
...my husband was sealed away by Ms. Sakura.
What?
The truth is that he is sealed
within this mikan box, at this very moment.
Huh?
Your father...
...is in a sealed space...
...within this mikan box!
WHAAAAAT?!
BANDA TERRACE
But why?! How did things end up like this?!
I was in the hospital at the time so unfortunately,
I don’t know all the details of what happened.
MIKAN
After Yuko and Ryoko were both in good shape,
I took them back home with me and...
I'm sorry.
While I was protecting the city,
Mr. Joshua got caught up and ended up
being sealed away in this box.
...I found this box placed next to our door
along with a handwritten note.
My sister... just left this box...
...I mean, Mr. Box, alone with you and your two kids
before she up and disappeared. Is that right?
You don’t have to call him "Mr."
We’ve put really hot plates and bowls
right on top of this box, you know?
And even used it to reach things that were too high up!
This box is covered in a magic coating
that makes it incredibly tough!
It’s resistant to heat, oil, and even heavy impacts!
Oops, I dropped it!
That reminds me, I tripped over it earlier!
That is everything I know about what happened.
I understand.
Regardless of how it happened, my sister stole away
the father of this family for over 10 years.
And I never had even the slightest idea, this whole time.
But Ms. Sakura made such great efforts to help us,
even though we were total strangers to her.
Please... give me some time to think all of this over.
Momo?
It seems... I really was your mortal enemy
this whole time.
I’m going home now.
Momo!
Momo...
The Demon Girl Next Door
Sassouto shobu shite
Yatchau kedo makechatte
Fugainai nai ne
Shoushin tenshin
Kibun wa sunsun demo
Shippo de henji shiyou
Chounai de waiwai shite
Inu made bow-wow de
Tende meimei de
Shunka shuutou
Shippai shita tte waraitobasou
Ano koro to onaji you ni kokoro tsumuide
Kono machi de deaeta kiseki
Kanaete yo
Zenkai da wa tire shou ippai
Warning mada kikikanri enjoy
Toridori saita iro canvas kakenuke
Sunset da wa, kangaete bakari ja
Sou, mae!
Hora, donna iro datte yume kasanete
Motto asobou ne
Preview
I’m going to chase after Momo!
You need to become strong in order to protect yourself
if you want to pave a path into the future.
You’re my descendant and you have the ability
to get into people’s hearts and freely manipulate them.
Why won’t you just rely on me, Momo?
I thought we were friends.
I’m also Momo’s friend, I mean her mortal enemy,
Feelings to Convey!! A New Leap Forward for Demonkind!!
so I have the responsibility to go and find her!