Last time on The Demon Girl Next Door.
I encountered a new Magical Girl character
while out working a job.
SHAMIKO
SHAMIKO IS PARALYZED WITH SHOCK...
Don't tell me...
Please don't tell me that outfit means...
Hey, does that flyer have a map on it?
Can you give me one?
OKAY!
This is where I'd like to go,
can you tell me how to get there?
That's the plaza you're actually in right now.
Oh, really?
It looks pretty different from how it used to,
so I didn't even notice.
Um... are you on a casual cosplay vacation?
Nope.
I'm just a Magical Girl passing through.
Oh crap! Oh crap! Oh crap...!
Are you okay?
Did you bump your head or something?
If you want to put it that way, I just bumped into
the one thing that I really didn't want to bump into!
What brought you all the way here in that outfit?
Please tell me it's sightseeing!
Not at all. I'm actually on patrol right now.
From what I hear, the Magical Girl in this city
had a bad confrontation with a Demon.
Yeah...
Apparently, she was severely injured after their
fierce battle and had the magic drained from her.
And now she's become a slave to that Demon.
What the hell?! I don't know
who gave you that impression!
WHAT
THE
HELL?!
Does that mean you're familiar
with what's been happening?
Uh, um, not really!
I just think whoever gave you that info
must only explain things in super broad strokes!
To be honest, I really didn't think the Magical Girl
of this city would ever get beaten like that.
I totally agree! Whatever you heard is fake news!
That's why I'm on the lookout
for a Demon that fits the bill.
I figured I would start by gauging their reaction
after a pound down.
"Pound Down" Definition 1:
To strike heavily or repeatedly.
"Pound down" Verb (transitive)
Definition 1: To strike heavily or repeatedly.
Or to reduce to pulp by beating.
Example: "I want to pound that Demon down."
Definition 2: Slang for to drink or consume something rapidly.
Example: "Hey cutie, why don't
we pound down some tea?"
Example: "I want to pound that Demon down."
Definition 2: Slang for to drink
or consume something rapidly.
Example: "Hey cutie, why don't we
pound down some tea?"
Hey, is it just me or are you acting a little strange?
No...
If I take off this costume, I just know
she's going to throw me with all her might!
The Demon Girl Next Door
The sun is shining too brightly
(I rubbed my eyes from the glare)
I took off without even thinking
(It's time for us to spark the joy)
When I hold back my swaying bangs with my left hand
These familiar sights start to shine
(Three, two, one)
We want to share our secret, right now
Anything is possible for us
(Always stay by my side)
For sure
(We trust each other)
On that street corner we found a precious treasure
Even if you went far away, I would definitely run after you
Our future is here, forever burning bright
The fun is only just getting started
The Cursed Fruit!!
Beware the Sour Mikan!!
I finished handing out all the flyers, but I can't quit yet.
Because this girl who wants to throw me into oblivion
is following me all the way to the changing room!
Hey, you've been acting pretty suspicious
for a while now.
Now she even suspects something!
Sorry, but would you mind taking off that costume?
Huh?! B-but Miss Tama Sakura isn't a costume, tee-hee!
Okay, I get you're really dedicated to playing the role.
But you've got sweat leaking out
from just about everywhere.
This is just Tama juice!
"Tama juice"?
I knew it, something is really off about you!
Your voice is quivering way more than it was earlier.
Come back here with me!
Things are just getting worse!
Huh? Was that Miss Tama Sakura?
Strip it off, right now!
I-I won't do it!
If it's difficult to get off, then I'll help you.
I won't do it!
Strip.
That's enough, it's coming off!
If we keep shouting stuff like this in a back alley,
then people will definitely get the wrong idea!
Horns...?
I... don't want the pound down.
C... C...
Crisis Management!
Are you a Demon Girl?
I managed to transform on impulse.
Is this because of all the training that I did with Momo?
But this is bad, I have zero ideas about what to do next!
So, hey...
Maybe I gave you the wrong impression somehow.
I was being harsh on you earlier because I thought
you might be suffering from heatstroke.
I didn't want you to actually strip down to nothing.
I don't really know what's going on with you,
but please accept my apologies.
She gave me something to cover up with out of pity!
Sob.
A-aren't you going to pound me down?
Sob...
I would never pound down on someone
so weak and defenseless!
Do you know how to revert your transformation?
I'm afraid I have no idea.
Um, well... you need to loosen up mentally,
like make your brain go limp.
"Go limp"?
What are you doing back here?
Shamiko and... Mikan?
Ah! Momo!
I'm here just like you asked!
I want to see you bow your head so far
in appreciation that it melts into the ground!
A friend of yours?
She's a friend, but I'm still debating about
whether to call the cops. What is going on?
Don't! This is all a misunderstanding!
This is Mikan Hinatsuki.
She's a Magical Girl I called in to help us out.
Things got really complicated
while I was waiting for you around here.
Momo Chiyoda (Fresh Peach)
A demon stole my magic.
Huh?
I need your help.
I temporarily lifted the barrier, so you should be able
to pick up on the Demon's presence.
I temporarily lifted the barrier,
so you should be able to pick up
on the Demon's presence.
Hold up, I don't know what you're talking about.
Hold up, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Do you have a place to stay?
Actually, your explanation lacks way too much detail!
Do you have a place to stay?
And stop ignoring my messages
after I know you've read them!
Scary, scary, scary, scary...!
SCARY!
You had me thinking something
horrific like this was on the loose!
SCARY!
A Demon that lost their heart
and became just like Baphomet!
SCARY!
You got the wrong idea.
Well I was really worried that was what happened!
SCARY!
Sorry.
For
Safe
Childbirth
I even went out of my way to buy a good luck charm!
SCARY!
Here
you
are
Oh, I also brought you a gift.
SCARY!
Hinatsuki Brand
Mikan Jam Wafer Cakes
Let me stay with you tonight.
I don't have a spare futon.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
Oh, this person actually seems pretty nice.
Well she's certainly no Baphomet, but I don't know
what was with that getup Shamiko was wearing earlier.
I'm going to need you to explain that to me later.
Uh, right.
I'm so sorry I scared you,
especially since you're still young.
What? No, that's... huh?
How old are you now?
I'm a first-year in high school, just like Momo.
You can feel free to rely on me for anything,
like an older sister!
D-don't think this means you've won!
Dooooonnnn't!
What?
That girl is the same age as us.
Huh? Seriously?!
I'm sorry!
Event:
Meet & Greet
with Miss Tama Sakura
Don't give up, Shamiko!
Become a great Demon with many allies!
It took a long time to finish cleaning up around here.
That's for sure. Good work today.
All members of the Sports Day Planning Committee
please report to the school athletic field.
Oh, I need to get going.
Sorry Shamiko, do you mind handling the rest?
Sure.
SPIN
Anri is super busy as usual.
Oh!
There you are, how convenient.
You're the only one with horns around here,
so you must be Yuko.
What's with the confused look on your face?
"Yuko..."
Oh wait, that IS my name.
I thought we were about to have
another misunderstanding.
Sorry, my mom is the only one who seems to call me
by my actual name these days.
If I remember correctly, your name was Mikan. Right?
Yes.
I was with Momo until just a few minutes ago,
but it seems we got separated somewhere.
I'd like to find her as soon as possible.
I need to throw away all this trash first,
but I can help you look for her if you'd like.
Really?
Nothing good will happen
just because you're nice to me, okay?
Though, I don't mind helping you
take out some of this trash.
U-um, that's not trash!
Out of all the bags of trash here,
you didn't hesitate to single me out.
I'm sorry, I didn't intend to confuse your ancestor
with the burnable trash.
Tell me, are you a Magical Girl from some nearby town?
You seem like one of the peaceful types,
so why are you here?
I'm here to pick up the necessary forms
to transfer to this school.
Is that so?
Wait, transfer?!
I mean, I was asked to safeguard Yuko...
is this really that surprising to you?
Your reaction was enough to make me jump,
so please cut it out.
Transferring to a different school
means making a huge change in your life!
You would do that just for our pitiful clan of Demons
whose statues get mistaken for burnable trash?
I was the one in the wrong here,
so don't degrade yourself over it!
Momo reached out to me for help,
so I want to do everything that I can.
There's still some trash lying around here.
Hey, Shamiko. Is it just me or does this Mikan girl
seem a lot more levelheaded than Momo is?
But it's possible that she's hiding an obsession
with training or something.
Excuse me, Mikan!
Which do you prefer: a dumbbell or a flower?!
Where did that come from all of a sudden?
I suppose I'd prefer a flower...
You're an ordinary girl!
Wh-what do you mean by that?
And why are you crying?
Well...
Momo told me that most Magical Girls out there
aren't very pleasant to deal with,
so I was a bit concerned.
But you seem like a really nice person,
so I'm just relieved.
L-look, nothing good will happen
if you keep smooth talking me. Okay?
I'm really not as reliable as you may think that I am.
Huh?
In fact, Momo may be having trouble right now
because of my power acting up.
Momo's in trouble?
Yes, she might be wandering around town right now
in a state that would get her questioned by the police!
That's why we've got to find her ASAP!
What exactly is your power anyway?
RED TEAM
WHITE TEAM
Oh, Anri...
Yellowtail Prize
Japan's #1
Party Rocker
Sorry to be so abrupt, but have you seen a girl
wearing a different school's uniform around?
OAK
LEAF
MOCHI
Momochiyo! What is up with that outfit?!
Snapshot!
You're like a walking billboard!
What's up? Are you going to a party?
This is the result of me being caught up
in various disasters because of Mikan's power.
OAK
LEAF
MOCHI
I'm in a hurry, so let's just put aside any questions
about why I look like this for right now...
I'm not mature enough to just ignore everything
that's going on with you right now!
I'm Birdtaro!
I have a certain power that is
very difficult for me to control.
Excuse me, are you the student
in charge of trash duty today?
Sorry to bother you, but could you take out
all this trash from the shredder for me?
Oh, sure.
Shamiko!
I'm going to be late for the ritual,
so do you mind taking these out, too?
They're full of chicken feathers and a bunch
of other junk leftover from our club activities!
What kind of club activities are you doing
that produce trash like that?!
Did that elixir I gave you before have any effects?
Wow, it's so light.
Tell me! Tell me!
It really must be full of chicken feathers.
Let me research you more thoroughly sometime, okay?
Later!
Okay.
This place was looking pretty clean earlier,
but now it's just a mountain of garbage.
I knew it...
Even now, the curse
isn't being held back strongly enough.
"Curse"?
Maybe I'm just too nervous
being in a place I'm unfamiliar with.
Oh crap, my heart rate is about to shoot the roof!
This isn't good, this isn't good!
Yuko, make a break for it!
Huh?
You have to run away from me
before my power goes out of control!
What?!
It looks like I was too late.
Momo!
What happened this time?
The garbage bags exploded and sent chicken feathers,
leaves, and shredder scraps flying everywhere.
I'm sorry...
I guess I really haven't been able to overcome the curse.
What curse?
All right. No problem.
Let's clean this place up
before the trash starts spreading out even further.
Right.
Um, so what exactly is this curse that Mikan has?
It's the after-effect of an incident
that I was once caught up in.
Whenever I become distraught, the curse rains a series
of misfortunes upon the people I'm connected to.
MESSY
But it's okay because Mikan
is really thoughtful and a strong ally.
Even so!
It's my fault that since this morning
you've been covered in wet cement
and had the pet bird of a millionaire
suddenly thrust into your care!
And things seem to have only gotten worse
after we got separated, ugh...!
Yeah, a lot of stuff happened
but it's okay because I found you again.
Are you sure you're okay?!
The curse can activate anytime
that I get too excited or flustered.
So please don't heap any unexpected praise on me,
like "she's a good girl" or something.
Well, it mostly won't be a problem.
I made sure to bring lots of good luck charms
and CDs that calm me down!
I'm not sure all of that will help too much.
But putting the curse aside, Mikan is a really
reliable friend. I just know she'll be a big help.
Ugh!
Nothing good is going to come
from flashing your happy smile at me out of nowhere!
There's a huge gust of wind!
It's sending the trash everywhere!
Shamikooooo!
Are you really sure it was okay for me to come and help?
A curse...
I think her situation is pretty similar to my own.
Um!
Uh, I t-tend to forget sometimes,
but I'm a Demon Girl who targets Magical Girls!
So, I think it's really great to have
a somewhat inept Magical Girl around town!
HEH
Heh, heh, heh, heh...!
I'll be watching closely for any openings
to steal away your magic.
So just detox your blood and wait for it!
Ugh!
Nothing good will happen if you awkwardly
try to cheer me up like that!
This is harder than I thought!
Shamikoooooo!
I'm sorry...
The curse is really coming on strong today.
Normally I'm much better at holding it back.
I think it's natural for you to be unstable
in new surroundings.
I'll support you as best as I can
until you've gotten used to this city.
I'll do my best to keep my heart rate under control, too.
But you're going to transfer to our school right, Mikan?
Are you sure you won't get too nervous
giving your introduction speech?
Can you handle it?
I wonder what class you'll be in?
Momo! At least have the decency
to spare her your silence!
NON-BURNABLE TRASH
BURNABLE TRASH
Well, we separated and threw out all the trash we could.
Are you sure you don't want us to wait for you?
It's okay. You've done more than enough
to help, thanks so much.
Okay, then we're going to have a strategy meeting.
"A strategy meeting"?
Yep.
CLEANING SUPPLIES
Ancestor, I'm really glad
that Mikan seems like a nice person.
Shall we head home now?
WASSUP!!
GREEN TEA
Wassup!
Huh?! This isn't my Ancestor!
Shamiko! Help me! Shamiko! Help me!
Where did the real statue go?!
Huh?
SHAMIKO
HELP ME!
Shamiko! Help me!
SHAMIKO
HELP ME!
Don't think this means you've won!
Don't give up, Shamiko! Do your best at keeping things
tidy and become a virtuous Demon!
Grumble, grumble, grumble, grumble...
Gaaah!
THE SECRET OF THE FRESH PEACH TRANSFORMATION
Momo's total transformation time
is roughly 0.01 seconds!
In this anime we show it to you in super slow motion!
TAMA RIVER
Recently, Momo has started
to kidnap me after school every day.
Or rather, she calls me to come and join her for training.
Grumble...
But why is Mikan coming along, too?
By the way, Shamiko. I wanted to ask you
about your eccentric wardrobe the other day...
The other day?
When you and Mikan met each other for the first time.
Oh, you mean my Miss Tama Sakura costume?
No. For starters, Miss Tama Sakura is not eccentric at all.
In fact, as far as mascot characters go
she has one of the most orthodox appearances.
But that's not because they were lazy
with her design or anything,
rather they were aiming for a simple standard
that eliminated the fluff as much as possible.
They held nothing back, but never added too much
and when the big mascot character craze is over
Okay, that's enough! I'm sorry! Please calm down!
And actually, what is up with all this passion you have
for Miss Tama Sakura?!
she will avoid falling into the pitfall of quirkiness
and break through with a straight punch that-
So, what did you mean by eccentric wardrobe?
You were naked back at the shopping mall, weren't you?
"Naked"?
Why would you phrase it like that?!
I wasn't naked! I was half-naked if anything!
There's no point in arguing semantics here.
Don't try and give me that crap!
There is a very stark difference
between naked and half-naked!
Is that supposed to be your Battle form?
It's my Crisis Management form.
I don't really understand the specifics myself, though.
Would you mind doing the explaining for me, Ancestor?
It's an optimal form that I produced which is designed
to strengthen the latent powers of our clan!
Does that mean she's powered up while transformed?
Slightly more than normal, yes.
Okay.
If she wills it, would Shamiko be able
to transform at any time?
My name is Shadow Mistress Yuko, 15 years old!
I'm just your friendly, neighborhood pervert!
In the morning, at night, during class...
could she even stay transformed around the clock?
If Shamiko managed to have enough focus, yes.
Stop consulting over these terrifying ideas!
Okay, Shamiko.
I want to test your abilities in your
Crisis Management form, so try transforming right here.
Right out in public like this?!
I refuse! That's too embarrassing!
But if either you or the city end up facing danger,
then it won't matter if you're in public or not
because you'll have to transform regardless.
Seriously...?
Fine. I'll agree to transform,
but only if you do it with me, Momo.
Not up for it? Heh, heh, heh.
Okay.
All done.
Your turn Shamiko, let's go.
I totally forgot. Momo is totally the type
to transform wherever.
It's been such a long time
since I last saw Momo's Battle form!
She is just such a cutie patootie!
But have you stopped doing that thing you did
back in elementary school?
You would always do those adorable spins
during your transformation, right?
Don't you think that was better?
Mikan...
"Spins?!"
Mikan, tell me more!
Back in the day, Momo would often spin around
and wink during her transformation. It was SO adorbs!
But after making various adjustments,
her transformation time became so fast, it's all just a blur!
Really?! That's such a waste!
I know, right?
During her transformation you usually get to see
smiles like this that are just bursting with joy.
Mikan!
It burst for real!
What's wrong?!
Was that the famous Fresh Peach Heart Shower?!
No, that was just a normal punch.
But we won't be buying dinner tonight,
I'm going to cook instead.
Uh, maybe I shouldn't have mentioned all that.
WEAPONIZED FOOD MANUFACTURING PLANT
Please give me more details later, Mikan.
I want to hear all about your memories of little Momo!
Sorry, I remember a bunch of things but I just
forgot them all to avoid the pain of "Momo Food."
By the way, why are you joining us for training?
It's not a problem, right?
I have a lot of time to kill
until my transfer to your school is done.
I feel you. I totally understand your pain, Mikan.
It's just so sad to be thrown on the floor
of your room and left out of all the fun, right?
Sniff... sniff...! Sniff...
Ugh!
I'm totally not sad or lonely or anything like that!
Oh crap, this isn't good. I need to calm down.
Oh no, Ancestor just got trapped
by this huge snake that was passing by!
I'd feel terrible if Momo ended up
having to run across the desert again.
Wait, did Momo have to run
across a desert to get here today?!
Breathe in. Breath out. Breath in, breathe in, breath in!
It's okay, Mikan. Just calm down.
You don't have to worry at all
about causing any problems for me.
You're more than strong enough to make up for it.
I believe that you'll become
the most powerful ally we have.
Momo...
You're definitely not going
to set my heart aflutter by saying all that!
Gah! ANCESTOOOOORRRR!
Anyway, you made a promise.
Get to transforming. You can do it.
I feel like you're being more pushy than usual, Momo.
Crisis Management!
Good afternoon.
Huh?
Crisis Management! Crisis Management!
Crisis Management?
Crisis... CRISIS MANAGEMENT!
Sorry.
Your apologies only make me feel worse, you know!
I don't understand why I can't transform...
That's because you don't actually feel
like you're in a crisis right now.
One unique trait of that form
is the transformation being triggered
by the strong flow of magic that's created
when you're frightened.
I get it.
EEK!
Why did you tie my tail to the sign?
For your sake and for the sake of the city.
Why are you holding that staff right now?!
If it means you'll be able to grow stronger, then I'm
even willing to use the Fresh Peach Heart Shower.
Somebody save me! Somebody save me!
It's okay, Fresh Peach Heart Shower
is an attack I can stop just before it hits.
B-but it sounds like an attack that you shoot at someone!
Okay, here we go.
EEK!
But I'm kind of excited to finally see it!
Three, two...!
Huh?
I can't do it.
Momo?
The exhaustion from the past few days
is starting to hit me.
Momo, are you okay?
I'm going to sleep for a few minutes.
Lately, I feel like Momo has been even more intense
about getting things done than she was before.
Maybe the drain on her magic is worse than expected
and she's panicking a bit.
I hope I'll be able to at least
take some of the burden off of her...
Behind you! Behind you!
At the very least I'm going to have to learn
to control my anxiety when watching the TV.
You might want to consider just not watching it at all...
Behind you! Behind you!
Things might end poorly if this keeps up.
What do you mean by that?
Well, you know that Magical Girls
sometimes dematerialize
if they use up too much of their magic, right?
We have to be sure not to put any more strain on her.
Hm, I see.
Wait, what did you just say?! They dematerialize?!
Huh? You didn't know?!
Maybe Momo was hiding it from you.
Oh crap, have I screwed up yet again?
Mikan, the curse is starting to take effect,
so please calm down!
Magical Girls have their bodies nearly
entirely reformatted to become an ether of magic.
Are you aware of that much?
Momo did tell me about that.
That's why, when a Magical Girl loses all of their magic,
the bonds holding their body together disappear
and they become unable to maintain a physical form.
They don't die, but their soul just ends up
being scattered apart into the air.
And it's difficult to come back from that on their own.
That means when I took some of her blood before...
It might have been really dangerous
depending on the amount.
It's dangerous for me, too. Although I don't plan
on letting you take any from me.
I had no idea! The priests of the Light Clan
really have it rough these days!
It makes sense that Yuko might not know,
but even YOU weren't aware of it?!
Not at all.
Why didn't she tell me about something so important?
For Momo's sake I want to be more....
Be more...
...more what, exactly?
Oh, sorry. I'm all right now.
Momo!
I'm going to work even harder!
What's with you all of a sudden?
No matter what it takes!
I won't go home today
until I've figured out how to transform!
For now, just think about a way
that we can scare me half to death.
You don't have to transform!
Really, what's gotten into you?
I just...!
I want you to... acknowledge me.
Huh?
I mean, as your adversary! Just as an adversary!
I understand.
I won't enjoy it, but if you insist then I'll do it.
Which do you prefer: a lunging punch,
an ankle lock or a one-armed shoulder throw?
Actually, you still seem really tired,
so let's do this tomorrow.
Take care!
Ugh!
It's okay, I'm more than capable
of physical activity right now.
I'm sensing a sharper bloodlust coming from you
now than when you were transformed!
Just stay calm.
I'll use the backside of my blade, so to speak.
When it comes to your fist that just means
you're going to backhand me!
You transformed. That's great.
Sob, sob...! Sob, Sob...!
Sob, sob...!
Sob! Sob!
I'll get you back for thiiiiiis!
Make sure to remember how you felt just now, Shamiko!
Don't give up, Shamiko!
Know your enemy and know yourself even better.
IMAGINARY DEPICTION
I'll get you back for thiiiiiis!
THE DEMON GIRL NEXT DOOR
"ALL IS MADE CLEAR!! THE SECRET OF THE CRISIS MANAGEMENT FORM"
"All is Now Made Clear!
The Secret of the Crisis Management Form!"
I can't walk around the city dressed like this!
I want a retake done on it right away, please!
Do you really think this outfit is that strange?
The problem has nothing to do with whether
it's strange or not! It's about public safety!
At this rate I'm going to be making my debut
on a wanted poster real soon!
Be on the lookout for suspicious persons!
But whenever you're in that form
all of your abilities are slightly enhanced.
Huh?
You could finish a whole 50-yard dash
in just over 9 seconds.
Wow! Amazing!
And with some practice,
you could even do a handstand forward roll!
If I could do a handstand forward roll,
then I wouldn't have to suffer the pain
of falling flat on my back whenever we practice
on the mat in gym class.
Blegh!
Oh, but is it really okay to go to gym class in this outfit?
No, it'd be big trouble!
It also makes you just a little bit smarter,
so it could even come in handy on a test.
But only if you study enough beforehand!
But taking a test in this outfit would be difficult!
Conclusion: It's amazing just how unrelated this form is
to any battles against the Magical Girls.
Just know that it's amazing!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Gallantly, I demand a duel
I go at it, but I lose
It's beyond disappointing
Shift away from that grief
Even when I’m feeling curt
I’ll express myself with that tail
There's a party in the neighborhood
Even the dogs are going bow-wow
Each and every last one
For all four seasons
When you fail just laugh it off
Connecting our hearts like that time once before
With the miracle that we met in this town
Grant this wish
Shoulder those tires and go full throttle
Warning, there's still crises to manage, so enjoy
Various blooming colors are spilling off the canvas
Now its sunset, don't bother thinking too much
Just go on!
Come on, our compiled dreams can be any color
So let's play some more
Preview
I'm Mikan Hinatsuki. That girl eating a mikan
in the opening is me!
Oh, I hadn't noticed.
It's been a long time since I've visited this city.
Shamiko, in the next episode
we're going to compete on our final exams.
Oh and there'll be a huge gathering
of mascot characters.
By the way, I asked my Ancestor for a retake
Final Exams!! Today I'm One of Those Brainy Demons!!
on the design of my Crisis Management form.
Wait, you did?