Momo?
It seems... I really was
your mortal enemy this whole time.
I'm going home now.
Momo!
Momo...
Dad was sealed away...
I'm sorry that I never told you.
Because you're so frail,
I was afraid that burdening you with all this
might cause you to work yourself ragged
and eventually fall apart.
Now that you've awakened your Demon powers,
you need to become strong
in order to protect yourself
if you want to pave a path into the future.
But it was terribly insincere of me to pressure you
to do your best, without telling you the whole truth.
You tried hard to protect me
even though I had been lying to you.
I now realize that I wasn't putting my utmost faith in you.
Mom...
Anyway, starting from today
this will now be known as the "Daddy Box!"
Uh, I think I'm going to need a little more time
to process this revelation.
We can finally make some offerings to him as a family!
MIKAN
The Daddy Box is built tough
and any stains get automatically purified,
so let's continue to use it
as a stool and table just like always.
Are you sure that's okay?!
Your father was the type
that put things to use in any way he could.
BRING IT ON!
Everything okay! Bring it on!
Now then, I have some more things
about your father that I want to tell you.
Listen closely, Yuko.
Okay.
Do you remember anything about your father?
Not much.
That makes sense. You were almost always sleeping
back when he was around.
But I do remember that he used
to pat me on the head sometimes.
Your father had quite the pair of horns on his head.
So this is what he looked like back in the day.
He's so much shorter than mom!
I must have inherited my short stature from him!
I probably won't get any taller, even if I undo the seal!
Are you okay, Yuko?
Doesn't dad seem pretty young here?
He looks around the same age I am!
Your father has always had
an incredibly youthful complexion.
I'll give this back now!
By the way, I've pretty much stopped aging
ever since I became his vassal.
"Vassal"?
A vassal is someone that has forged a bond
with another through a contract...
Wait a second. Maybe it's better to say
that it's a type of blood relation via magic.
VASSAL
A SUBSERVIENT MEMBER OF A CLAN OR FAMILY.
ORIGINALLY USED TO REFER TO EMISSARIES OF GOD.
IT CAN MEAN: RELATIVES, KINSFOLK,
FOLLOWERS, SERVANTS, OR ANY SORT
OF DEPENDENT RELATIONSHIP.
Overload...
OVERLOAD
Are you all right, Yuko?
Um, I'm still in a state of shock to be honest.
So much... so much... so much...
Ever since I grew these horns,
there's just been so much going on.
Scuttle, scuttle, scuttle, scuttle.
I think I've gotten accustomed
to dealing with surprises, lately.
Yuko! You've really started to take after your father!
Bring it on...
BRING
IT
ON
And really...
I'm relieved that dad hasn't died or anything.
And now I know that I'm in good health
thanks to the help of many different people.
I...
I think I've finally figured out a reason to fight.
Mom, I'm going to chase after Momo.
I don't want her to fret over all this on her own.
Momo has been my mortal enemy
ever since the moment I first laid eyes on her.
I'll chase her to the ends of the Earth
until I can finally claim victory over her!
You're going to regret all that time you spent
helping me build up stamina, Momo!
Now I'm going to have my revenge
for the tire and all that other stuff you did!
"Tire and other stuff"?
Mom.
Yes?
Please share some more stories about dad with me later.
I'm headed out!
Sure.
Yuko, I imagine you probably don't remember this...
...but there's something
that your father used to say to you.
She's already gone.
I'll just have to tell her some other time.
The Demon Girl Next Door
Taiyou mabushisugite
The sun is shining too brightly
(Chikachika me o kosutta)
(I rubbed my eyes from the glare)
Omowazu tobidashita yo
I took off without even thinking
(Dokidoki no hajimiari sa)
(It's time for us to spark the joy)
Yurayura yureru maegami hidarite de osaetara
When I hold back my swaying bangs with my left hand
Itsumo no keshiki ga kirameku yo
These familiar sights start to shine
(Three, two, one)
Ima sugu tsutaetai futari no himitsu
We want to share our secret, right now
Watashitachi nara dekiru yo
Anything is possible for us
(Itsumo tonari ni ite)
(Always stay by my side)
Kitto
For sure
(Shijiteru kara)
(We trust each other)
Machikado de mitsuketa daiji na takaramono
On that street corner we found a precious treasure
Tatoe kimi ga tooku hanaretemo kanarazu oikakeru yo
Even if you went far away, I would definitely run after you
Zutto kagayaiteru mirai wa koko ni aru
Our future is here, forever burning bright
Otanoshimi wa kore kara
The fun is only just getting started
Feelings to Convey!!
A New Leap Forward for Demonkind!!
The Demon Girl and the Magical Girl
share a surprising intertwined fate.
Shamiko, now is the time for you
to chase after that Magical Girl!
Where exactly did Momo disappear to?
Maybe I should start by checking out her house.
Shamiko.... Hey Shamiko...
Dog
MUNCH
A-Ancestor!
Ancestor...
PAT
It's my fault that you got all messed up like this!
Did you lose some weight?
PAT
Shamiko, that's a dog toy you're holding. I'm over here!
SUPER MOVE! MAGICAL GIRL HURL!
After being flung away by the Magical Girl
in the last episode, the ancestor has been rescued.
Good work, Shamiko!
Your father was connected
to the currently missing Sakura Chiyoda...
...and the barrier that surrounds this city. I see.
Did you know about what happened
to my father, Ancestor?
Actually, I don't really know anything
about your father or his history.
I was really curious and tried
to bring it up with you more than once,
but every time I was unable to get through Seiko's guard.
Ancestor... if you run your mouth too much
and cause Shamiko to fall sick or get depressed,
I'll send you to a temple
that performs funerals for old toys!
Funerals for old toys?!
Authentic
Japanese Shochu
Glug
If you play your cards right, I'll prepare
a small reservoir of sake for you to partake in every day.
Sake is so tasty...
I just... I couldn't... Sob, sob.
Don't cry, Ancestor!
Right now, I need to focus on cornering Momo.
From what I understood, Ms. Sakura Chiyoda
is the person I owe for making me healthy again.
But... I get the feeling Momo didn't see things that way.
I think that if I just left her alone,
Momo would disappear and I'd never see her again.
Shamiko?
That's why I'm going to return the favor by dragging
Momo back and then helping her search for Ms. Sakura.
But...
TREMBLE
Even if I do manage to grab hold of her,
I couldn't stop her from turning the tables on me...
Worst case scenario,
she flings me as high as the heavens.
Are you telling me you charged out here
with no plan at all?!
I think Momo probably got close to me
to try and get some info about her sister.
But unfortunately, the one lead she finally found
wasn't able to provide any answers.
She must be really depressed
about having been sent back to square one.
I don't think she'll be willing
to work together with me anymore.
Think about it this way, Shamiko. If Momo is feeling down
right now, then it's a chance we can't pass up!
You're my descendant and you have the ability
to get into people's hearts and freely manipulate them.
In theory, anyway.
"Theory"?
It's simple... all you need to do is seduce Momo Chiyoda!
"Seduce"?!
She's not here, either.
No pink heads that I can see.
Oh? If it isn't Shamiko.
Oh! Hello Mikan.
You don't look too good.
You should take a dose of vitamin C!
MYSTERIOUS
Actually, what good timing.
Come on! Just eat this! It's a citrus fruit that I just bought!
Can you tell me the places that Momo might go to?
Huh? What for?
I'm looking for Momo and I have to find her
as quickly as possible.
You're looking for her?
Is that true?
Ms. Sakura disappeared?
Huh? Didn't you know, Mikan?
Th-th-th-this is the first I'm hearing about it!
Uh, Mikan please keep your cool!
Why did Momo hide it all from me?
Mikan... stay in control...!
Why didn't she just tell me?
Crisis Management!
98 cents
(98 yen)
Mikan...
I owe Ms. Sakura a lot, too.
Why won't Momo rely on me? I thought we were friends.
Hey, Mikan.
Shamiko?
As another of Momo's friends-
I mean mortal enemy, I'm equally frustrated
that she's choosing to run away.
Oh no, did my curse hit you again? I'm sorry.
Huh? 98 cents?
Please tell me what you know about Momo!
I have to find her no matter what!
Shamiko...
If it's true that Ms. Sakura vanished over 10 years ago,
that would have been
after she left Momo in a different city.
Even if Momo wanted to look for her,
she wouldn't have any leads to go off of.
Assuming there is a Demon in the city old enough
to remember exactly what happened,
it doesn't matter since the barrier here
prevents Magical Girls from encountering Demons.
Yeah, Momo mentioned that to me.
Huh?
But on the day that I became a Demon Girl,
I encountered Momo right away.
She stopped it with one hand?
Yeah, about that...
...you mentioned earlier that Metako said he could sense
Sakura Chiyoda's presence in you, right?
Right.
Like I said, it's usually impossible for any Demon
and any Magical Girl to cross paths in this city.
Right.
That's why I think your meeting with Momo
must have been some kind of fated event.
A mysterious power might have been at work
behind the scenes somehow.
"Fated event"...
Well, that's just a guess.
It might actually be a simple coincidence.
It's true that the barrier on our house had grown weaker.
I wonder if that was also due to the hand of fate?
Shamiko.
I can think of one place that Momo might have gone to.
But you should go by yourself to look for her there.
Huh? Why is that?
Well, I mean, if I overhear your conversation
then it might make me lose control of all my nerves!
Okay, I get it! You're already starting to lose it!
Tama River
But I want to hear all the details from you afterwards!
Okay, sure!
Shamiko, save me! I'm going to go flying!
I finally found you, Magical Girl!
I'm impressed you knew to come here.
Mikan was kind enough to tell me.
She said that you and your sister liked this spot.
Momo, were you hiding
the disappearance of your sister from Mikan?
Yes. Mikan was one of my sister's disciples,
and I thought she might not take it well.
That's an understatement.
Thanks to you, I ended up
having to endure a very cursed shower.
GRUMBLE
It totally ruined my clothes.
That explains why you chose to come in your battle form.
Just look at what happened to me!
Anyways, why did you come find me?
You know that my sister was the one
who sealed your father away, right?
What reason could you have to be friendly with me now?
Momo, you're my mortal enemy.
Even if we're not friendly, that's more than enough reason
for me to stick close to you.
What's that mean?
I came here because I want to strike a deal with you.
Momo... will you consider quitting being a Magical Girl?
Please make a contract with me and become my vassal!
What are you talking about?
You want to search for Ms. Sakura, right?
But you can't really do anything because
the barrier here obstructs all Magical Girls.
Then the solution is simple:
you just have to quit being a Magical Girl!
Quit? But I can't just...
Actually, you can!
If a Magical Girl overwrites their contract
by forging one with a Demon,
their magic attribute will become darkness
and they will stray from the path of light,
thereby officially making them a vassal of darkness.
I dub this the: "Momo Chiyoda Gets Enticed
by the Allure of Darkness Project!"
Uh oh, sorry about that Ancestor.
So dwizzy...
Ugh... ugh... uuugh...
I finally found a reason to fight.
And that's why I need you to stick around, Momo.
To be honest...
...I think your personality is more suited
to being a Demon Girl than a Magical Girl.
I mean, if nobody watches out for you
then your diet just goes straight to Hell!
And you're really good at coming up
with evil ways to use special powers!
You even exude a way darker aura
than I do most of the time!
You're not pulling any punches...
I don't think that white and pink theme you have
going on actually fits the color of your personality.
If you fall to the darkness, we'll redesign
your battle form with a simple black as the base!
We can even make your weapon
like a dark katana or something.
You're even dragging complaints
about my battle form into this?
Agreeing to become my vassal
is a pretty good deal, you know.
I'll help consider the solutions
to whatever tough problems you face.
And I'll also join you in doing the things
that you don't like to do.
Right now, it seems to me
that you're struggling all by yourself.
It makes me worry about you.
But your mother had to raise
2 daughters on her own for 10 years...
...and on top of that, she had
to lie to you about it the whole time.
No matter what I do, I can't return
those 10 years to your family.
That's why even if you want to strike a deal, I...
So you're just going to give up and run away
because you can't give everything back to us 100%?
I refuse to give up on anything:
My father, undoing the seal, or being with you.
I'm going to find another Demon who lives in this city,
and hopefully through them, get a lead
to find Ms. Sakura, because I owe her so much.
I'll get stronger, become even more capable,
and then get back everything that I possibly can!
I'm going to become a true Demon and live greedily!
But I don't think that I can fight
through all the challenges on my own.
And since we share the same goals,
I would really like you to fight by my side.
Magical Girl, Momo Chiyoda.
It's time for you to put an end to fighting a solitary war!
Embrace your weakness, give in to utter depravity,
and stray from the path of light.
Then let yourself fall into darkness!
Become my...
Become a subordinate of Shadow Mistress Yuko!
There's a lot of benefits
if you agree to become my vassal!
Three meals and one nap a day! And if you agree
to it now, I'll do all garbage removal and dish washing!
Hey Shamiko, you're making a serious commitment
that you can't back out of with all those bonuses!
Gah!
Avoid the effects of the barrier
by becoming a Demon, huh?
Are you the one who came up with this plan, Ms. Lilith?
Not at all.
I did advise Shamiko that it was possible
for you to fall into darkness,
but the rest of it was all Shamiko's idea
that she put into her own words.
By the way, I personally guarantee you won't suffer
any personality changes by falling into darkness.
I see. So Shamiko said all that herself, huh?
I'm really glad.
If this was all just happening according
to Ms. Lilith's script, I would have flung her into space.
Why?! Am I crazy or are you
extra harsh on me all the time?!
Shamiko.
Sigh...
Yes?
I don't need any bonuses
like three meals and one nap a day.
Do you promise that you won't suddenly
disappear on me?
Yes.
Regardless of whatever I do from now on,
or whatever I've done in the past,
will you continue to stay by my side?
I swear on the box of my father.
That's great.
Pause...
No, wait a second.
Something is off here.
Nothing this happy could ever possibly befall me.
Huh? This isn't going as planned!
Thinking about it, Ms. Lilith...
...if I go along with this, Shamiko is going
to become the magic ether that I link to
which means I'll end up really weak, right?
Gah!
Huh?
Is that true, Ancestor?
Dot, dot, dot.
Tch.
TCH...
Yeah, you'll be considerably weaker.
I knew it.
You didn't explain that on purpose, I'll bet.
Ancestor!
Hey Shamiko. Please come and find me
again someday, somewhere.
Ancestooor...!
That was close, I almost totally fell for it.
Wh-whoa...
But you had a good point, I've been fighting
and contemplating this all on my own for too long.
Thank you, Shamiko.
Thinking about it, even if I didn't become a Demon,
you could search the city for other Demons in my place
without being affected by the barrier, right?
Huh?
And in exchange for that, I'll keep you safe
and train you even harder than before.
That's a pretty good deal, don't you think?
I... I'm not so sure.
Maybe... huh?
Is it just me or does that change nothing
from how things are now?
If anything, the burden being put on me
seems a bit heavier.
That's not true. You're just imagining it!
If you agree to the deal now, I'll make
your protein shake after training banana flavored!
But what happened to the idea
of you coming over to the dark side?!
We're putting it on hold.
If I went for your deal and became weaker, it would
be impossible for a lot of things to come to fruition.
Besides, something just doesn't sit right with me
becoming your subordinate.
But why?!
If you want to make me your vassal,
then you're going to have to beat me first.
I have high expectations, Demon Girl.
HEH
So, you're agreeing to become my vassal if I win?
Heh, heh, heh, heh...
Then I'll just dive into your dream
and implant a suggestion in your head and...
That technique is banned.
You have to beat me with only your fists.
That's not fair!
Well that wraps things up, so let's head back.
H-hold on! Nothing is wrapped up!
Are you trying to make a break for it?!
Nope. I won't run away from you anymore, Shamiko.
I'm getting hungry, so let's go back together.
Grr... You always throw things out of whack.
Huh?
Just forget it!
Dog
Oh dear, it looks like your dinner got all messed up.
It's okay, I'll bring you a fresh bowl of seconds.
Sorry, doggie. I don't get to choose where I come down.
I didn't have the courage to go into the store
with this outfit on, sorry.
That's okay. While I was in there,
I bought something for us to share together.
Here.
Double popsicles? Can I really have one?
Yeah.
Let's split it 50/50.
I'll snap it in two!
Just leave it to me!
Hnnngh!
Should I do it instead?
Heh, heh, heh, I haven't gotten serious yet.
You just sit back and watch me use my true power!
Oorah!
Sorry, let me help.
SNAP
We're going back to training starting tomorrow.
Okay, Shadow Mistress?
Grr...
Don't think this means you've won!
Don't give up, Shamiko! Work to defeat your mortal
enemy and one day become a great ruler of darkness!
Banda Terrace
So, everything about your father being away
for business on a space battleship was a lie!
As your mother, I do feel a bit guilty
about keeping the truth from you.
Yeah, I figured.
Huh?
That's the deal.
I knew that dad was in a situation
where he couldn't come home for a long time.
Mom is a terrible liar.
Demon
Space battleships and giant squids.
Who would believe stuff like that?
Huh?
Actually, I'm really into those hardboiled crime novels.
So, I thought that dad may have been involved
in something that required prison time.
"Prison"?!
MIKAN
Actually, I'm relieved to know
that he's a lot closer than I thought.
He was right under our nose the whole time.
CLICK
MIKAN
TRAINING MENU
(MAKE SURE TO DO IT ALL EVERY DAY!!)
PLANK - 15 SECONDS
SQUATS - 15 TIMES
TAKE A 30 MINUTE BREAK
LIFT DUMBBELLS - 5 TIMES
PUNCH PRACTICE - 10 TIMES
You're such a fearless girl, Ryo.
You might take after your father Joshua
in that respect, actually.
"J-Joshua"?!
Our dad had a foreign name?!
Apparently "Joshua" was a very common name
in ancient Mesopotamia.
Wait, so we're half-Mesopotamian?!
Today is just full of all sorts of surprises.
CLICK
But I saw a lot of documents around here
that listed our dad's name as "Taro Yoshida"!
"Taro Yoshida" was a codename
that your father used while working here in the city.
"Codename"?!
We came up with "Yoshida"
by changing a few letters of "Joshua."
You never considered changing more than just a few?
Mikan.
I'm sorry I never consulted with you about my sister.
Even though I knew she was
a really important person to you, too.
It's fine, don't worry about it.
You were just trying to be considerate
by not aggravating my curse, right?
Sometimes you seem apathetic about things,
but I know you're actually quite considerate.
I suppose.
I think you should let your true self shine
a little more from now on.
Keep things simple.
The time cometh.
Go on, have some fruit.
Okay.
These are sour.
That's what makes them so tasty.
After a bunch of crazy stuff happening,
our first semester is finally coming to an end.
Excuse me, Shadow Mistress?
Are you doing your vacation homework already?
No.
This is a letter of challenge.
There's a Magical Girl in Class A, Momo Chiyoda,
who I want to become a denizen of darkness.
So I'm going to challenge her again!
LETTER OF CHALLENGE:
DEAR MAGICAL GIRL MOMO CHIYODA,
TODAY WILL BE THE DAY I DEFEAT YOU AND MAKE YOU MINE.
FUWAHAHAHAHA!
"Letter of Challenge: Dear Magical Girl Momo Chiyoda...
A letter of challenge, huh?
Well, do your best to make it really nice.
...Today will be the day I defeat you and make you mine.
Fuwahahaha."
Though speaking as your teacher,
I'm afraid I couldn't give this a passing grade.
FLAP
CLATTER
Why?!
Because organizing duels is against the law.
GAH!
Gah!
Oh?
Our class is already finished for today.
I came here to see what Shamiko was up to.
It looks like she's practicing
how to write a letter or something.
SCRIBBLE
I think it would be better if you picked some
cuter letterhead than that old paper you were using.
SCRIBBLE
Right.
You should start it with a friendly seasonal greeting
and then at the end write something considerate.
SCRIBBLE
Right.
To: Momo
I finished it!
Gallantly, I demand a duel
I go at it, but I lose
It's beyond disappointing
Um, teacher, don't you think this pushes the envelope
a bit too much for a letter of challenge?
Shift away from that grief
Even when I’m feeling curt
I’ll express myself with that tail
Cute!
But dear, envelopes are stationary.
There's a party in the neighborhood
Even the dogs are going bow-wow
Hey, Momo!
Each and every last one
Oh good, I'm glad you haven't gone home yet.
For all four seasons
You should read this!
When you fail just laugh it off
Huh? Why are you wearing a different color than normal?
Connecting our hearts like that time once before
Am I not allowed to change my wardrobe a little?
I think I like this more than the usual.
To: Momo
Just read it!
A letter?
With the miracle that we met in this town
Dearest Momo,
How is the heat of summer treating you?
You seemed a bit down in the dumps a few
days ago, so I'm showing some demonic concern
for you.
"Dearest Momo, how is the heat of summer treating you?"
"You seemed a bit down in the dumps a few days ago,
so I'm showing some demonic concern for you."
Shamiko, does this mean you're worried about me?
Grant this wish
No! Just stop, I changed my mind!
Shoulder those tires and go full throttle
Don't read it until I'm not here!
Warning, there's still crises to manage, so enjoy
As of now, we're openly
cooperating with each other
to help find your sister.
As of now we're openly cooperating with each other
Various blooming colors are spilling off the canvas
However, you should be aware
that I have not given up on my plan
to make you my vassal!
However, you should be aware that I have not given up
on my plan to make you my vassal!
Now its sunset, don't bother thinking too much
Today is a day of pause, the closing ceremony
of our first semester. I would like you to put
our training on hold for today and instead
surrender leadership to me.
Just go on!
Today is a day of pause,
the closing ceremony for our first semester.
Come on, our compiled dreams can be any color
I would like you to put our training on hold for today
and instead surrender leadership to me.
So let's play some more
Heed me, Magical Girl! The era of depravity is upon you!
Heed me, Magical Girl!
The era of depravity
is upon you!!
Come alone to the riverbank at 3:00 PM this afternoon!
Come alone to the riverbank
at 3:00 PM this afternoon!
Sincerely yours.
The time comes quickly
P.S. It's hot outside.
Please wear something
light and easy
to move in, to avoid
suffering in the heat.
P.S. It's hot outside. Please wear something light
and easy to move in, to avoid suffering the heat.
Oversleeping peacefully
Well, it's fine for now
Going to bed is routine
Sleeping children will grow
I have no idea
what she's trying
to say with all this...
I have no idea what she's trying to say with all this...
Even their horns get tough
HEH...
Heh, heh, heh...
Momo must be reading through
my letter of challenge right now.
The cat corners its prey and bites
HEH...
Surprisingly this is the right way
It happened unexpectedly
HEH...
Just wait, Magical Girl! Today will mark
the beginning of a new kinship between us!
HEH...
A sudden turning
Is this a case of sink or swim?
HEH...
Okay, then let's go along!
Connecting our hearts again like that time once before
I really don't understand.
Oh hey! It's Momochiyo!
What's up? You've got a huge smile on your face.
I'm not sure I'd call this a smile.
The wish we embraced was a miracle
I got this letter from Shamiko, but the contents
are all over the place. I wasn't sure what she wanted.
But I think she wants to skip our training session
and go out for fun somewhere instead.
Oh yeah? That's great!
It shines
I'm so happy for you, Chiyoda.
Transform, blooming in full glory
Jumpin' we join hands and enjoy
Sometimes withering, but still able to bud
Many ages have passed since the era of myth,
yet the Dark Clan have remained oppressed
by the forces of the Light Clan through the current day.
Game set? Not yet!
Connect into tomorrow
And into the sky!
However, one rumor is spreading.
Look, far off dreams sketched all around
That a city exists under the protection of the strongest
Magical Girl who has parted from tradition
and created a special place where both
the Dark Clan and the Light Clan can coexist peacefully.
I'll show you
The colors dancing vividly
It lies somewhere in the far east.
Its citizens are used to all sorts of craziness,
and have the ability to shake off nearly anything.
Always chasing after them
Pure Tea House
Asura
Because I want to grab hold
From an outsider's perspective,
Seiiki-sakuragaoka is quite the peculiar town indeed.
I'm heading out, Mom!
YOSHIDA
Yuko!
Even in adversity don't wind up that tail
Yeah?
I imagine you probably don't remember this...
A twinkling star reaches out sharply
...but there's something
that your father used to say to you.
If I could be a little stronger than I am today
Tama River
I'm impressed you showed up, Momo Chiyoda!
But blow my top and face a tempest of punishment
Today is the day we celebrate your descent
into darkness! The festivities are about to begin!
Disappointed? I'm throwing it again, so enjoy
Da
da
duuuun...
Da, da, da, duuun!
Various blooming colors are spilling off the canvas
What the heck is up with your outfit?!
I thought I told you to wear something easy to move in!
Now its sunset, don't bother thinking too much
Just go on!
Come on, our compiled dreams can be any color
Thought they were
going out to have fun.
going to have a duel.
So keep on going
Don't give up, Yuko.
Become the strongest
and most loving girl in the entire world.