Oh crap!
I overslept! I'm going to be late!
Listen, my cute descendant. Don't forget you have
access to something that makes you run faster!
Oh, that's right! I forgot all about it!
So once again, the day is saved
thanks to my Crisis Management form!
Please write your name on this list of late arrivals.
Why didn't you transform?!
I can't bring myself to do it in the middle of town.
The Magical Girl, Momo Chiyoda,
is obsessed with making me train in one way or another.
SCANNING
Is this some kind of mecha or what?
It's a body composition monitor for professionals.
Muscle Mass
Segmental Muscle Mass
Left Arm
Low
Right Arm
Core
Low
Overall - Low
Right Leg
Low
Left Leg
It doesn't seem like you've been able
to build much muscle lately.
Wait here. I'm going to bring
my special protein drink for you.
Do you have any special attacks of your own, Mikan?
Yeah, "Sunrise Arrow" and a few others.
Th-th-that sounds so cool!
I want to see! I want to see! I want to see!
You seem just a little too excited about this.
Lately, I've realized just how thrilling
the idea of special attacks are!
And unlike Momo, I get the feeling
you might actually show me some of yours!
So please let me see!
Show me your special attacks!
Show me! Show me! Show me!
Enough harassment!
I'm very sorry.
Broccoli. Protein powder. A variety of mysterious pills.
Strips of chicken meat warmed up by the Magical Girl
until they turn a strange color.
Seconds
Her time beyond the fifth decimal place
is rounded for convivence!
SHAKE
This completes the specially made, pink protein shake
designed to help Shamiko's muscles grow fully!
Gulp. Gulp. Gulp. Gulp. Gulp.
This is great! It goes down smooth
and tastes like it's really nutritious!
Really? I'll make some more later.
Gulp. Gulp. Gulp. Gulp.
Why exactly is it glowing like that?
A THK Special
Simply Incredible
The Miraculous Human Body
When humans push the muscle tissue
of their body to its absolute limit,
their cells begin a new evolution.
Go! Go!
Come on! Come on!
Hey! Hey!
Hey, you!
One more! One more! Come on!
That's interesting. Hey, Shamiko.
Huh?
Dash
I thought you weren't going to transform
in the middle of town?
I felt my life was in serious danger!
The Demon Girl Next Door
The sun is shining too brightly
(I rubbed my eyes from the glare)
I took off without even thinking
(It's time for us to spark the joy)
When I hold back my swaying bangs with my left hand
These familiar sights start to shine
(Three, two, one)
We want to share our secret, right now
Anything is possible for us
(Always stay by my side)
For sure
(We trust each other)
On that street corner we found a precious treasure
Even if you went far away, I would definitely run after you
Our future is here, forever burning bright
The fun is only just getting started
The Ancestor Evolves!!
A Pair of Glasses Reflect Within a Dark Lab
Hey, Shamiko!
What's up, Ogura?
I heard all about it! You've been doing training lately
to become stronger, right?
Well, I can make you immensely powerful!
You want that, right?
Okay, then it's decided. Just come with me.
I haven't agreed to anything yet!
I'm so glad we can finally have
a close and personal chat!
Just follow me to my lab!
I remember this girl, she's...
Sion Ogura from Class C.
According to what Anri told me...
Ogura is an oddball who is super
into stuff like devils and magic.
She's always borrowing various rooms and equipment
in the school to do some very suspicious research.
She does a lot of weird stuff, but her grades are so good
that the teachers all just put up with it.
Looking for a home
THIS HAS BEEN RESOLVED
Please take this bird
If you look at the scores
from the final exams that we just had...
FINAL EXAMS: JULY - TOP SCORES
1st) Sion Ogura - 1190 points
2nd) Kumi Shirozaki - 1185 points
3rd) Lilith, the witch who governs over darkness - 1181 points
She's in the top spot!
I was so disappointed.
The only exam I didn't get 100% in was the ethics one.
If you ask me, it's all so far from the actual truth.
I just can't comprehend why
they marked me down in the first place.
I am Ruv - 1/2gauR = kTuv!
This girl is clearly lacking something
in the morals department.
Isn't she exactly the type of person we should avoid?
This reminds me, I think I remember seeing her
watching Shamiko from the shadows pretty frequently.
That's terrifying...
But the first time I was able to transform
was after Ogura gave me an elixir to drink,
so she might actually be pretty amazing.
I've always wanted
to get to know more about you, Shamiko.
You're a Demon Girl, aren't you?
Huh?
I think you'd be a perfect fit for my research!
I want us to become really close friends, Shamiko.
Then I can do all sorts of experiments together with you!
That doesn't sound like the idea of friendship
that I'm familiar with...
Black Magic
Studies Club
FWOOOSH!
This is where I've set up my lab!
It's okay. You've got me with you right now.
In the worst-case scenario,
we'll just take whatever seems useful
then seal away all her memories of today
and make a run for it.
Is that really how a Magical Girl
should be handling things?!
Without further ado, I welcome you...
...to my lab, the Black Magic Studies Club!
PANDORA
SEAL
Nope.
Momo, put the wand away!
I want to get data by doing some experiments on you.
And you want to become stronger as a Demon Girl.
That means our interests line up perfectly, no?
It's a great opportunity!
Let's gaze into the abyss together!
Hold on, Ogura.
I get that you're enthusiastic to move things forward,
but just calm down for a minute.
You're scaring Shamiko.
Right now, Shamiko and I are working together.
I can't risk something bad happening
because of your weird experiments on her.
Momo!
At the moment, I'm serving as Shamiko's producer.
If you want to do anything to her,
then you'll have to get my approval first.
You're serving as my what now?
I have lots of ideas!
For one, I want to expose her to an electric current
and gauge the quality of magic inside her!
Rejected.
I want to draw her blood!
I want to transplant bat wings on her!
Impossible. And none of these ideas are even acceptable
from an ethical standpoint.
That's three strikes, which means
you're out and we're done.
Umm...
I don't think Momo has any room to talk
considering what she does to Shamiko.
This must be the Ancestor
who I heard finally became able to speak!
Chiyoda, do you mind if I do
some demonic remodeling on this?
So long as it's nothing that can't be undone.
Oh crap!
I was trying to be inconspicuous
so she didn't find me, but my voice slipped out!
You can't! Please leave my Ancestor alone!
It's fine, Shamiko.
I'll agree to be her specimen.
Huh?
Lately, my feelings have started to change
since I've been watching your progress.
I want to find a way to escape the current cycle
of oppression we're stuck in with no way to resist.
If these experiments can find a way to safely assure us
a bright future, then I'll do whatever they want.
Drip...
Shamiko, if I make it out of here alive, then please
make me a hot bowl of udon when we get home.
Ancestor! All of your dialog is just making it seem
like you're never going to come back!
Don't worry. I promise not to do any experiments
that leave irreparable harm.
WHIRRRRR
That drill in your hand says otherwise!
SEAL
Ta-dah!
So, this statue is kind of like a router
that connects our world
to the sealed space that you currently reside in.
And you can even control Shamiko through it, right?
Indeed. Although, that particular function
was sealed off by the Magical Girl over there.
Then how about I create a new vessel for you
to inherit and move around in?
C-can you actually make something like that?!
I'd like to try, anyway.
Producer Chiyoda, do you mind
if I ran an experiment like that?
Well, I'm not sure since Ms. Lilith
is one of the enemies who is after my blood.
If you agree to it, I'll include this mysterious elixir
that makes Shamiko stronger at no extra cost!
Okay, deal.
So even Magical Girls are susceptible to bribery.
This is raw clay that's used to make homunculi.
It's some leftovers from another of my failed experiments.
My theory is that since you and your ancestor
are blood relatives,
if you infuse the clay with some of magic
to make arms and legs, then they'll work... maybe!
I'll give it a try!
Please let my Ancestor become mobile.
Please let me Ancestor become mobile!
Ugh, y-you know this clay has a really weird smell.
Well that would be because
the base ingredient for homunculi is horse dung.
Horse dung?!
Just how much farther can I fall?
THE SOURCE
I made you some arms and legs, Ancestor!
My hands are really sore from kneading that clay so
much!
And I stink so much it hurts.
Try standing up in your new form, Ancestor!
Oh! It's moving!
It's hard for me to move on just two legs!
The infused magic is too rough around the edges!
H-how about if I try moving around on all fours like this?
It seems like our experiment was a success.
Although it's too weak to be a proper vessel,
so in a few minutes it will go back to being dirt.
Shamiko, be straight with me. How do I look right now?
Uh, well, you... you remind me of the cute
eggplant cow decorations that we make for Obon!
You're lying to me, Shamiko. I can tell.
Just be honest and tell me what you really think.
Do it.
I'm sorry that I'm so clumsy and inexperienced
that you ended up looking so freaky!
I figured that's how you felt. It's okay, Shamiko.
You did your best.
Ah...
Ms. Lilith, after getting the gist of it,
I made a little something for you from the leftover clay.
It's adorable!
I borrowed the clothes from something
that was lying around here.
Please use it.
My magic is stronger than Shamiko's, so you should
be able to control it remotely for a short time.
I created it by using Shamiko as a model.
It's a lot easier to control
than that other body from earlier!
You look super cute, Ancestor!
Why the sudden change of heart, Magical Girl?
I didn't see a problem in letting you move freely
since you don't really pose a threat either way.
Are you sure, Momo?
Do you really want me to be mobile?
You're the one who sealed off the switch
on my statue in the first place.
Plus, if you infused this body with your magic,
doesn't that drain it from you?
Well, I know you wanted a body to move around in,
even if it's just for a brief period.
I don't think it will last for very long,
but I can make more for you occasionally.
You can return the favor by agreeing to set
a good example for Shamiko and help to train her.
You have my deepest gratitude, Magical Girl!
Heh.
As if I'd ever say that!
I'm just playing it friendly so you fall right
into my trap! Thanks for being such a sucker!
Although it's only a limited time,
there's now a chance for me to move freely!
You'll regret writing me off as "posing no threat"!
You cocky little brat!
I did let myself get a little emotional about it,
but you're 5,000 years too young to be pitying me!
The time limit really sucks, but if I can just get Momo
to mass produce me a set of spare bodies then...
"...when her guard is down, I'll make her bow
before me so that I can conquer the world!"
That's the vibe your tail is giving off right now.
Ms. Lilith, sit.
Shake.
What is happening?! My body is moving on its own!
As I figured, it's also possible for me to control that body.
Are you serious?!
STIFF
Ms. Lilith, do a cute dance for us.
Impossible! I can't believe my own magic control
on this body loses out to hers!
Look over this way!
Shamiko! You're on my side, right?!
Ancestor... your inner thoughts
were openly conveyed through telepathy.
No way!
This is mortifying... but my body can't help
but groove to the rhythm!
And it's somehow making me start
to really enjoy all of this nonsense!
Don't...
Don't think this means you've won!
Don't give up, Ancestor! By the way, if you get
into a hot spring with that body it'll melt in a flash!
Goddammit!!
Goddammit!
YOSHIDA
Spin!
Spin, spin, spin!
And then pose.
Your mom has her very own point card
for the Tama Sakura Shopping District!
Tama Sakura
I already knew that, Mom.
But something good happened with it, right?
That's right! Listen to this, Yuko.
An elegant plate
When I earn enough points,
I can get a really elegant plate for free.
Oh! It's quite elegant.
Design
Up until now, I would always go and get a free plate
whenever I built up enough points for it.
However, before I had enough time to get one
for each member of our family, the design changed.
I've always been upset
because I could never get a matching set.
It throws off the balance in the cupboard, too!
That's why this time I waited until I had enough points
to exchange for three plates at once!
A perfect set of elegant plates
That's one elegant set of elegant plates for sure!
It's so exciting!
And so, I'm headed out
to go exchange my points right now.
Have a good time!
Hey, Sis.
The laptop we borrowed from Ms. Momo
has been acting up.
Huh?
It'll start up, but after a few minutes it just stops working.
What should we do?
Maybe a part of it broke?
I don't really know how computers work,
so let's go and ask Momo for advice.
We'll apologize and see if she can fix it.
If it's broken, then I'll find a way to handl-
HERE
LIES
LAPTOP
Shamiko, I can't believe you'd destroy
one of my possessions.
Starting today we'll be doing squats
with a barbell instead of dumbbells.
Come on, let's get started.
BUZZ
There's absolutely nothing for you to worry about, Ryo!
Sis! Your tail!
Momo
Chiyoda
Wow! A fortress!
No, it's just Momo's house.
You just wait here for a minute, Ryo.
I'm already used to this routine.
I take the path of white stones
and clear it with no problems.
Good afternoon, Momo.
Then I get past the security
with "Live Chicks n' Jive Tricks, Wahoo."
The Demon Girl is on your doorstep!
Oh, Shamiko? Come on in.
HIYAH!
Hiyah!
Momo?
Is it okay if I invite my little sister to come in right now?
Ryo? Sure, feel free.
She wanted you to look at the laptop that we borrowed...
Hey! You're eating nothing
but junk food for lunch again!
I can't let my eyes off you for a second!
It's just lunch, does it really matter what I have?
Though if you're going to make me something, I'll eat it.
I am not your personal Demon kitchen maid!
But fine, what type of food do you want to eat?!
Please excuse the intrusion.
Momo, I have a selfish request.
I want you to keep the fact
that you're a Magical Girl secret from Ryo.
Why is that?
Ryo believes that I'm a cool sister
who is waging a war on Magical Girls.
She can't find out that you actually
have a grasp on all of my weaknesses...
SHAKE SHAKE SHAKE
SHAKE SHAKE
Kelp Soup Stock
Sesame Oil
Or even worse, that I come over
to your house to cook for you!
Or that I borrow your purse to go shopping for
ingredients and even charge a point card in your name!
It might send her off the deep end!
You made a point card in my name?
That's how you earn points to get free stuff!
Shamiko, didn't you tell me...
Cooking Shamiko Style
Microwave frozen udon
for 3 minutes on high to defrost it.
For this dish, tuna is substituted
in place of the meat.
...that if you always live in fear
of other people seeing your weaknesses,
The base noodle stock is seasoned
with oyster sauce, sugar, and sake.
Shamiko style also calls for sesame oil
and some ginger paste.
then you'll never be able to make any progress in life?
Yes, but Ryo is my little sister.
I feel like I have to always set a good example
by being a strong sister who lives up to her ideals.
I see.
Um, Ms. Momo?
What is this cute wand for?
Do this, and it makes
the food taste more delicious
This is wand meant for cooking.
If you do this it makes the food taste more delicious.
Momo's going all out to convince her!
I hope she washes that later!
I'm sorry you had to go so far just to help me out.
I don't mind, but...
if you ask me, the one who suffers the most
is the person who keeps secrets from their loved ones.
Huh? Um...
Sis!
The time hath come!
This cat sounds like it can talk
and it shines like a lightbulb!
The time hath come! Time cometh!
It cometh now!
JUST SAY NO!
TO WAND USE!
(Paid for by the Global Frying Pan Association)
Please do not use Magical Girl wands
to stir ingredients in your frying pans at home.
The truth is that Momo is a Magical Girl.
I'm sorry that we've been lying to you for so long.
We're working together right now for various reasons.
I knew.
Huh?
And I knew that you were lying
just to be considerate to me.
It's obvious from the way that Ms. Momo carries herself
that she's trained as a military commander.
Military commander?
As I thought...
Ryo?
WOOOOOW!
As I thought, Ms. Momo is a Magical Girl
who joined the ranks of your army!
What?
You used a dirty scheme not suitable to share
with children to ensnare Ms. Momo into your army,
and that's why you couldn't share
any of the details with me!
I've read about it before! I read lots of books like that!
Ryo...
It's so incredible that you made someone so strong
into one of your subordinates without using force,
and that you've been coming to this fortress
to have strategy meetings!
Ryo, that's not...
And you're even going out of your way to cook
for your subordinate, that's so considerate Sis!
Seeing you in action really moved me!
Wait...
Yeah, that's right.
Momo?!
You hit the nail on the head.
So tell me, how did you
become my sister's subordinate?
Mostly being attacked in my sleep,
and then having my fridge filled with delicious food.
Momo is just sewing an even bigger web of lies.
Hold on, Momo! We were supposed to tell her the truth,
not make things even more complicated!
There are some smiles in the world
that we have to protect... I think.
You're supposed to be the unyielding one here!
I'm home!
I bought some ice cream!
Oh, who's this little girl?
This is bad. She has absolutely no idea what's going on.
I'm Yuko's little sister, Ryoko!
Oh, is that so?
I'm Mikan, another Magical Girl
who was called in to help out.
Would you like some ice cream?
Are you another member
of my sister's legion, Ms. Mikan?
Huh? Legion?
What is that? The name of some new citrus fruit?
Mikan... come with me for a second.
POKE POKE POKE POKE
Stop, don't touch me with the ice cream there!
My curse will act up!
I don't know what's going on,
but I'll be a subordinate! I'll be a subordinate!
Ding...
As of now I am one of your loyal subordinates...
Mikan, I'll make it up to you later!
The Magical Girls both enjoyed their ice cream after this.
Hey, look. What do you think that is?
The time hath come.
Momo... I thought that older sisters
aren't supposed to lie?
For now, I think we should make sure
she keeps that bright smile of hers.
And if you ask me...
I don't think Ryo's analysis of the situation
is that far from the truth, really.
Huh?
If you don't understand, then just forget it.
Jeez.
Are you for real? Can you really accept
being my subordinate?
That look! You're really finding the idea hard to swallow!
I didn't find any problems with the laptop.
You don't have an A/C at home, right?
I think it just got overheated.
Try to only use it in the coolest room,
and if it gets hot, then let it take a break.
You can come use it here, too.
And now I'm even more indebted to you.
Say, Shamiko.
Huh?
If you feel that way, then make some more food for me
next time you come.
One of the duties of a lord is making sure
their subordinates are well fed and healthy.
Okay, Shadow Mistress?
Damn you! It's not fair
if you say it when nobody's around!
I'm so glad that the laptop wasn't broken.
I'll use it more carefully from now on.
It has my journal, my private diary
and a lot of other important data!
Wow, you sure are using the laptop
to do a lot of different things.
Yeah. I had Ms. Momo print them all out for me, too.
That's way more than any ordinary diary or journal.
Ta-dah!
Ta-dah!!
She also taught me how important it is
to keep a variety of backups!
I don't really get it, but I feel like
I'm just piling up the debt at this point!
I'll study really hard and someday
become an advisor to your army!
...I have to
do something
about this fantasy
of hers
I have to do everything that I can...
...to someday make Ryo's fantasies come true
and find a way to surpass Momo.
But how exactly can I do that?
What I know about Momo
When I think about it, I still know very little about Momo.
She likes noodles
Information about Momo...
What I know about Momo
She likes noodles
She prefers soy sauce over regular sauce
Information about Momo...
What I know about Momo
She likes noodles
She prefers soy sauce over regular sauce
She has nice handwriting...
About Momo...
The only information I can think of
is absolutely worthless!
Sis?!
I think I'm going to do some digging into Momo.
I get the feeling that she won't be willing
to tell me very much.
Actually, I think she's keeping
a lot of secrets on purpose.
Simply elegant!
Hey Ryo.
I was really lonely today
because you guys
left me behind.
Hey Ryo. I was really lonely today
because you guys left me behind.
As my future advisor there's something
I'd like to ask you, Ryo.
If you had to seek out information about your enemy
and their weaknesses, what would you do?
Um...
Find a way to get into their good graces
without being suspicious,
and then convince them to open up
and share with me... I guess.
If you do it that way,
then they'll naturally start to share their secrets.
My beloved sister
is far more technical
and much more advanced
than I would have ever thought...!!
My beloved sister is far more technical and much more
advanced than I would have ever thought!
But I should take her advice to heart and do my best.
Huh? What is this picture?
I wonder if Ms. Momo put it in here?
Dear Ryo, This is a picture
of Shamiko's combat attire.
Please enjoy this immortalization
of her strength and bravery.
Dear Ryo, This is a picture of Shamiko's combat attire.
Please enjoy this immortalization
of her strength and bravery.
So this is what you look like in battle, Sis.
Can I take a few pictures of you some time?
Curse you, Magical Girl! THIS MEANS WAR!
I think it looks really cool, Sis!
Don't give up, Shamiko! Become a Demon
who exemplifies a cool lifestyle for your little sister!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Gallantly, I demand a duel
I go at it, but I lose
It's beyond disappointing
Shift away from that grief
Even when I’m feeling curt
I’ll express myself with that tail
There's a party in the neighborhood
Even the dogs are going bow-wow
Each and every last one
For all four seasons
When you fail just laugh it off
Connecting our hearts like that time once before
With the miracle that we met in this town
Grant this wish
Shoulder those tires and go full throttle
Warning, there's still crises to manage, so enjoy
Various blooming colors are spilling off the canvas
Now its sunset, don't bother thinking too much
Just go on!
Come on, our compiled dreams can be any color
So let's play some more
Preview
Ancestor, there's still so much about Momo,
that I don't know.
Please watch, I'm really going
to go all out from now on!
Good! That's the spirit, Shamiko!
Your magic has been slowly growing as of late,
so use it to give Momo a real surprise!
And make it rhythmical!
Diving into Dreams Once Again!! Break Through the Pink Defense Line
The time hath come!
It seems the time has come
to fully explain everything to Yuko.