Yuko... listen, Yuko.
Can you hear me?
My cute little descendant.
This is the second time I've connected with you.
Do you remember me?
Oh... I actually do remember this feeling.
It was uh, um... uh... um...
Ah, perhaps you have forgotten.
No, I remember! It's right here,
on the tip of my stomach!
In other words, it's already been digested.
Uh, I'm too sleepy...
Hold it right there! Don't you dare fall asleep,
you sorry excuse for an heir!
This is the tale of a girl
who received demonic powers overnight,
and must rise up to defeat a Magical Girl
in order to save her family from the grips of poverty.
Or something to that effect.
The Demon Girl Next Door
Nightmare or Forebear?!
The Doorstop of Darkness Descends
I am your great ancestor! The founder of the Dark Clan!
Hiss!
We met once before, on the day you grew
that tail and those horns!
My ancestor...?
That doesn't make sense, you're blonde.
The history of our clan is long and complicated!
We've thrived for thousands of years
through many different lands,
of course your appearance would change!
Thousands of years?! That's amazing!
Um, can I ask you a question?
Anything you wish!
In all those years and different lands,
did you ever actually win a fight with the Light Clan?
It took me half a day to get all these
shiny decorations put up, what do you think?
I take it that means success
is a foreign concept to you, too.
So, I've been wondering... am I still dreaming right now?
To be precise, I'm actually intruding
within the deepest part of your consciousness.
But you can just think of it as a dream.
It's easier to understand that way.
So why did you come all the way
into my dreams, Ms. Ancestor?
Let me explain. This might take a while,
so feel free to take a seat.
Newly Remodeled
I've seen these tables and chairs somewhere before!
And this sign, too!
I pulled them out from among
your most recent memories.
If you've got any complaints,
then you only have only yourself to blame.
Is this thing real?
Ever since your powers awakened
and you became active as a Demon Girl,
I've watched your progress
through the Demon God Statue.
Deep Inner
Tama Station
ONE
HIT
KILL
$35.00
(3,500 YEN)
As a judge, I would give you 5 points!
Huh? Are you sure it's okay to grade me that high?!
WHOAAAAAA
That's 5 out of 100!
Don't look so happy about it!
What kind of scoring system did you think I was using?!
A soccer game...
You dimwit!
Huh? Why am I sitting here in this weird space
surrounded by food court tables
while getting lectured by some half-naked lady?
Ah!
This must be a dream! It's one of those surreal ones!
I just finished explaining that!
I'm heading out.
Are you going to the library again?
Yeah. I'm going to study hard so I can become
a great tactician who can support Sis.
Don't worry about that, just do your best.
I will.
Is Yuko still up there sleeping like a baby?
I have a lot of bones to pick with you,
but the biggest problem is your complete lack of talent!
SHAME
Shame.
Huh?!
It's hard for me to even know where to start!
Your heart is just so damn fragile!
Shame.
Yes, ma'am...
SHAME
Don't start crying!
You have terrible intuition!
SHAME
Shame. Shame.
Build some stamina for God's sake! Eat more!
SHAME
Don't give up so quickly!
Shame. Shame.
SHAME
Yes, ma'am...
I'm thirsty. I'll take something to drink
from within the depths of your consciousness.
Oh, please help yourself.
Burp... Burp... Burp...!
Burp... Burp...!
Burp...
What the hell is this?! Poison?!
It's a carbonated beverage.
Well, anyway... this is the first time
that you and I have been properly connected.
Huh?
Our clan has the ability to dive into
other people's dreams and manipulate them freely.
COLA
Dive into dreams?!
Th-that's amazing!
I'm really... starting to think
that you're super cool, Ms. Ancestor!
Wonderful, feel free to sing my praises
as much as you want!
Have you ever been able to use that power
to win against our enemies?!
You know, after drinking this weird stuff
I get the feeling it's pretty addictive.
It does that.
Since the Light Clan's seal has started to fade from age,
reaching out to the consciousness of my descendants
should be a trivial task for me.
But for some reason connecting with you
was a HUGE pain in the ass!
Your soul is too weak to pick up
on my sensor! It's pathetic!
Huh?!
Yuko Sensor
In terms of your modern-day wireless signals,
it's absolutely horrid!
Even at its best, I can only get one bar!
Did you put your heart into airplane mode or what?!
Wow, you really know a lot
about our technology, Ms. Ancestor!
YUKOTENNA MK. I
You need to make a bedside antenna
so that my signal can reach!
If I leave something like that lying around,
my mom is gonna be worried!
Yuko? It's already past noon, are you not getting up?
That's my mom's voice.
Ah, yes, Seiko.
Do you know my mom?
There's still... more for us to talk about... lots more...
Oh no, the signal is...
My ancestor is slowly starting to disappear!
Mom...
Just one more hour...
My body on the outside still wants to sleep, I guess!
We can keep talking!
That's kind of pitiful, but good job!
Yuko, are you really not going to get up?
We don't have much time left,
so I'll cut straight to the chase!
When you eventually wake up from this dream,
your memory will be mostly unstable.
So when you get up, write all of this down ASAP!
Roger that!
Even though I'm still sealed away, I can enjoy
anything that you offer to the Ancestor Statue.
So leave some delicious treats
and magazines as offerings!
Also, I don't care how perfect the size is,
stop using it to cover your cup noodles while they cook!
When I'm sealed away
Leave offerings
To the Ancestor Statue
Things I can enjoy
Prepare delicious treats
And magazines!
But even though
It's the perfect size
Don't use it
To cover the Cup Noodles
While they cook!
Yes, ma'am!
I can tell you more about your father, about your
hidden power and about the device in the statue, but...
Yuko? Today's breakfast is pancakes, you know.
If you don't hurry and wake up,
they'll be all cold and soggy.
Um, Ms. Ancestor?
SMILE!!
The power of pancakes
is not to be trifled with! Get going!
Remember, the pride and hopes
of our clan rest with you!
Ah... you truly are my ancestor!
When you eventually wake up from this dream,
your memory will be mostly unstable.
So when you get up, write all of this down ASAP!
Mom, I need a notebook!
Where's there a notebook?! I'm going to forget!
I saw one next to the phone.
I'm gonna write it all down!
Before I forget!
Are you writing something? Could you
write down a few things for me while you're at it?
Squeeze
My hands are wet, so I can't do it myself.
Huh? But I have to record these memories...!
Sugar, paper towels, seaweed, sweet rice wine,
bean sprouts, chicken breasts, green onions, carrots,
alcohol on sale for $1.78 and eggs on sale
for $0.88 starting at 3 pm.
Crap... I forgot....
Sugar, Paper Towels
Green Onions, Carrots
Onions
Chicken
Eggs on sale Wednesday at 10am for $1.78
I was woken up by an ancestor
or something in my dream-
I know whatever happened in that dream
was really important, too!
What's wrong? Your pancakes are going
to get cold if you keep waiting.
Oh, that's right! The pancakes! That's why I woke up!
Time to dig in!
Chew, chew... Chew, chew...
UMM...
Are these really pancakes...?
They don't taste bad or anything,
but they're really spongey.
I made them from leftover rice and tofu!
I know that dream I had was super important.
What's wrong?!
I should have just stayed in bed.
Chew, chew...
Sakuragaoka Library
I see.
Don't want to be caught off guard.
Mom, are you doing laundry?
That's my one and only uniform for school.
I'll do it myself.
It's rare that you want to help. Well, go ahead.
This is my first step to maturing into a great demon!
This is that cola stain from the other day.
Burp, burp, burp...!
Oh, that made me remember,
I met with an ancestor person in my dream!
Huh?
I vaguely remember that whoever they were,
they seemed to know you, Mom.
Did they ask you anything?
No, they mostly just got mad at me for stuff.
There was cola and chairs from the food court
Scrub
and the whole thing felt really surreal...
I wonder if it really was only a dream?
Scrub
Maybe it was one of those dreams that wasn't a dream?!
I don't really understand what you mean,
but don't scrub the stain so hard you tear a hole!
Huh?
I don't think I'll be able to fool her for much longer.
Oh honey, our little girl has grown so much.
I'll set them out to dry!
We have to be sure to have no regrets,
no matter how things turn out.
Yuko...
If you don't wash wool properly, then it will shrink.
Huh?
Don't give up, Shamiko!
Learn how to do laundry through experience.
And don't misread what's on the tag!
Monday
G'morning, Shami!
Huh?
Why the gym clothes? We don't have gym today.
My uniform became unusable.
I'll be wearing these for the time being.
I have a spare uniform. Do you want to borrow it?
I have so many questions for you right now!
But thank you very much!
Okay, I'm going to get changed right away!
Poof
Uh.... well...
I think...
...it makes you cute, like a fairy that lives in the forest.
I don't need your awkward comments to back me up.
I'm just fine.
When my new uniform comes,
I'll wash this one and return it to you!
You don't have to, I always
send my laundry out to the cleaners.
But if you insist on doing it yourself, then I'd like that.
Smile
You seem like you'd be good at doing household chores,
so I have high expectations, Shamiko.
Smile
Uh.... sure...
Handwash
30 degrees Celsius
(85 degrees Fahrenheit)
Gently ring dry
This number means I should handwash by splashing it
in hot water that's over 85 degrees, right?
Splash, splash, splash...
Then I should leave it spin dry
for about 10 minutes, I guess?
Well, the longer it goes, the better chance
the stain has of coming out!
A reminder of yesterday's failure.
You're really daring, Magical Girl!
I hope you don't come to regret those words!
Sure.
I'll make sure it's silky and soft!
Handwash
Gently ring dry
Don't give up, Shamiko!
Laundry is all about knowledge and experience!
Don't misread what's on the tag!
I'll make sure it's silky and soft!
Take this, and take that!
I'm going to get you! Just wait! Take this!
Bam! BAM! Are you prepared to die?
If not, you better be!
She really has no...
Were you about to say something just now, Mom?
No, nothing at all. Please continue.
Am I doing all right?
As a mother, the one thing I must never do
is admit that my daughter has no talent!
Is that what you were trying to say?!
This doll is really adorable!
Hm, but... close-quarters combat against Momo
would put me at a disadvantage.
I thought it might be a good idea to find something
that I could throw at her...
You mean a projectile.
Huh?
Ryo?
I think the best strategy is to rely on everything you can
aside from your physical strength, Sis.
Bow & arrow, rifle, cannon, rocket.
There are a lot of options.
But you should stick to what suits you.
The modern era is all about projectile weapons.
I think I'm getting the picture!
You're really smart, Ryo.
Do your best, Sis.
The modern era is all about projectiles!
What's gotten into you?
You look cute in that, Shamiko.
Just like a kindergartener with a smock.
I'm a high schooler.
Anyway, I've come to a very important revelation.
If I even get close to Momo, she'll work her wiles
and trap me in some crazy situation again!
Wassup?
The instant I let myself get sucked into her world,
then everything will be over!
What are you doing?!
The length of the uniform was bothering me,
so I thought I might shorten it.
You realize I borrowed this from YOU, right?!
But I'm only going to shorten it a little bit.
If you're going to wear it, you'd prefer that it fit, right?
Well...
Come on, take a seat.
Sewing set
Convenient
to have on hand!
Prick
Are you studying up on projectiles?
Th-that's none of your business, Momo!
It is.
I mean, I'm going to be your victim
after it's complete right?
I have the right to offer my opinion.
Prick
In fact, I'm certain that my input will be
what makes it into a really great weapon.
W-well... I'm not so sure.
You want to make an awesome projectile, right?
Then come with me after school.
Okay...
Great, then I'll fix the lining
at the bottom of the uniform later.
Right.
You just fall for her ploys each and every time.
It's really adorable, Shamiko.
Huh?!
Shamiko... she got the better of you again today, huh?
Please stop making the assumption
that I'm destined to lose no matter what I do!
Prick
Owie!
I can't keep the needle from hitting you
if you move around so much.
Oh, sorry.
Prick
You're really good at sewing.
Yeah. Some damage that my Magical Girl outfit
takes lasts even after I cancel my transformation.
It would be a waste to buy new clothes
every time they frayed a little,
Prick
It came
loose...
Prick
so I thought it was a good skill to develop.
That's a surprise to me.
So, are you a really good chef, too?
People often told me that my cooking
could be used as a weapon.
Wow, so it's one of those things
that can destroy a person's stomach, huh?
This is...
An abandoned factory I own.
You OWN?!
A while back, I kind of blew it up
and then ended up buying it.
The mysteries surrounding Momo
only get deeper and deeper.
Um...
What's up with this strangely shaped wall?
That's a storehouse.
Storehouse?
It used to be, anyway.
Let's start practicing how to use projectiles.
I have a bad feeling about this...
I'm going home!
First of all, you have the wrong idea
about projectile attacks.
Things like rubber bands aren't going to help,
you have to summon your magic and project that out.
Magic?!
Let me go home, I wanna go home!
I'm going to keep this with me. It's dangerous.
YOUR WEAPON WAS STOLEN!!
I know I made it myself,
but there's absolutely no way
that rubber band is more dangerous
than whatever made that hole you showed me!
Right...
You're not going home until you shoot something.
I can't do it, no way, it's impossible!
There is no can or cannot, you just have to do it.
So let's do it.
What are you even talking about?!
No matter what you unleash over here,
it won't cause any problems.
So just let yourself go crazy.
You've grown horns and a tail, which means...
...you have more than enough potential
to produce some magic.
No way. The only thing I can produce is eye juice!
Everyone's like that at first.
Let's start by practicing form.
You'll need a target.
Something the right size should do...
Perfect.
You can't! The poor thing!
DEMON GOD STATUE
A wicked stone statue that harbors
the banished souls of the Dark Clan!
It's super sinister!
Looks like it might fall apart
Demon God Statue!
Lately it's been called the Ancestor Statue
or "Ancestue" for short.
JUST STOP IT
Don't use the poor thing as a target.
I don't think you're focused enough yet.
Maybe you need a wand or something.
But I'd hate to break off a tree branch over this.
Do you feel nothing for the poor statue?
There it is!
Whoa!
For now, will you use this wand?
I get the feeling something this amazing
is wasted on me!
It's fine, there's nothing else around here
that fits well enough.
I'm a Demon Girl so stuff like this doesn't really suit me...
What about my rubber band gun?
That won't work. Use this.
Wah! I grabbed it without thinking!
It feels a little warm.
Forget about all that and let's get to work.
Do you feel anything coming out?
I've got buckets of sweat coming out,
if that's what you mean.
Oorah!
You might have better luck if you yell something out.
Do you have any strong feelings
about the world in general?
Huh?
Something like, "I want to crush everything!"
or "This world should be plunged into darkness!"
B-but I don't feel anything like that.
Everyone around here is really nice...
Is that so?
Well, then anything is fine.
Just shout whatever comes to mind.
Um... well...
Tonight I want to have a big feast!
That's not what I meant.
Sorry, I realize I shouldn't have said "anything."
The way that wand works is when the innate feelings
in your heart resound strongly with it,
you'll discover a keyword that
will unlock all of your magical power.
In my case it was...
"Fresh Peach Heart Shower!"
Like that.
"Fresh"...?
Huh? What did you say?
You don't have to memorize it. Just forget it.
What? I wanna see it! Fresh Peach Heart Shower!
Use this! Here! Show me, show me!
I don't want you to see it.
Limited time sale
Eggs for 88 cents!
Up to 2 packs per 1 customer
WOW!
Whoa!
Yahoo!
WOW
WHOA
OH!
WOW!
WHOA!
YAHOO!
The last one! That was close!
WOW!
OH!
WHOA!
YAHOO!
The 3 pm sale of 1 pack of eggs
for $0.88 has now ended.
OH!
WHOA!
NO WAY!
NO KIDDING?!
WOW!
OH!
WHOA!
YAHOO!
OH!
WOW!
WHOA!
YAHOO!
Thank you for your continued patronage.
Sugar, Paper Towels
Onions, Green Onions, Carrots
Chicken
Eggs on sale Wednesday at 10am for $1.78
I was woken up by an ancestor or something in my dream-
There's quite a number of things
missing from the list Yuko made for me...
Sugar, paper towels, seaweed, sweet rice wine,
bean sprouts, chicken breasts, green onions, carrots...
Close!
...alcohol on sale for $1.78
and eggs on sale for $0.88 starting at 3 pm.
Mixed it up!
Limited Time Sale
in 15 minutes
But, thanks to her I was able
to remember what time today's sale was.
Sugar, Paper Towels
Onions, Green Onions, Carrots
Chicken
Eggs on sale Wednesday at 10am for $1.78
I was woken up by an ancestor or something in my dream-
When all is said and done,
I got my hands on 2 packs of eggs!
She
did
it!
Since you awakened your demonic power,
you should have one or two offensive attacks.
That's the whole reason I was watching over you,
to make sure you didn't lose control.
Huh? You were watching over me?!
Don't let that distract you.
For right now, just focus on turning your desires
into some sort of attack name.
Uh, um... then how about...
Applepeas!
Subray!
Syneed!
Okay, I get that you want to go eat at a restaurant!
Those didn't work? Then...
Panda Excess!
They do sound like attacks, but that's not what I meant!
You dummy! Are you even
taking this seriously, Shamiko?!
I... I am...
Then you have to focus on getting stronger!
You know, not every Magical Girl out there
is the cunning type like I am!
Most of them show absolutely no mercy!
If you come across one like that,
they're going to boil you alive in an instant!
SOFTLY BOILED
YUKO SOUP MIX
SEAWEED FLAVOR
SALT FLAVOR
Boiled alive?!
By the way, did you just call me a dummy?!
I didn't call you that! Dummy!
W-we only just met each other,
so why are being so supportive of me?
You seem oddly passionate about it, too.
Don't get hung up on details like that.
It's only natural to get hung up on details like that!
Shamiko, the sun is gonna set soon.
N-now that you mention it, I'm pretty hungry.
If you manage to shoot something,
I'll make you a hamburg steak from 100% beef.
And I'll carefully simmer the demi-glace sauce
with a hint of red wine.
Delicious
Is there really such a thing as 100% beef in this world?!
Obviously.
Then what about 120%?!
Alright, let's get back to it!
Roger that!
Before the sun sets, you should just focus on shouting
whatever phrases pop into your head.
I want to go to Atami City!
I want to be covered in cats!
The wireless signal in my room is too weak!
Broccoli is delicious!
Natto, egg and rice!
Uh, um...
I hope that everyone will become friends!
Whoa!
Something came out!
It's moving super slow, but I shot something!
It's tiny and adorable!
Is that really all you've got?
Um? Is it just me, or is it headed my way now?
It's going straight towards you.
My master!
I think it lacks enough propulsion
My Master!!
and is trying to make its way back into your body.
What happens if it hits me?
I think it will probably hurt a little.
About the same as an intramuscular injection?
That's one of those injections that hurts a lot, isn't it?
Here, I'm returning this.
Sure.
I'll make you regret this, Magical Girl!
It'll probably disappear if you can keep running
for between 20 and 30 minutes.
You're going that way?
I guess I'll run with you.
Why would you do that?!
You realize I'm not running because I want to!
"I hope that everyone will become friends"...
was that what you said?
I think I'm going to keep training you
for a while, Shamiko.
Why would you do that?!
Hey there!
Gah! It's starting to catch up!
I'm back!
Don't think this means you've- OWIE!
Ugh... it hurts as bad as an intramuscular injection.
Okay, let's keep running to the next bridge.
Why? There's no reason for me
to keep running anymore...
Don't give up, Shamiko!
Even if you get pricked, don't stop running!
The Demon Girl Next Door
Preview
I ended up running so much today, all because of Momo.
You did good work out there.
Anyway, this is the next episode preview.
I suddenly find myself at a health spa,
and fall even deeper in debt to Momo.
Shamiko, you're a real snowball when it comes to debt,
Sharpen Your Mind!! The Newly Awakened Powers of the Magical Girl
so I'll hook you up with a job.
Anri, are you sure this job is gonna be okay?